<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2019-08-11T13:12:02+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>How to Find a Perfect Developer for you Company</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-find-a-perfect-developer-for-you-company.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-find-a-perfect-developer-for-you-company.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-11T13:08:06+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="" />
                    An ideal candidate should have a deep knowledge of the required programming language. However, it would be more valuable if he or she knew other coding languages to become more&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>An ideal candidate should have a deep knowledge of the required programming language. However, it would be more valuable if he or she knew other coding languages to become more flexible and be able to work in future projects. It is also essential that developers have the ability to communicate effectively with all the members of the team and, in particular, with the customer to make sure that all the needs are understood at the beginning of each project thus saving development time and later changes. The software world is a fast paced, ever evolving environment and thus it is necessary to be able to meet very strict deadlines, be flexible and be creative. Furthermore, requirements often change during the course of large projects, thus having experience in lean programming is essential. While establishing which are the desired skills of candidates is a relatively simple task, finding and especially evaluating such candidates before hiring them is particularly complex. It is easy to imagine how time consuming it would be to carry out some interviews and then perform technical tests where candidates show their qualities. In particular, this could become complicated because candidates may not be willing to code unpaid during an interview and evaluating some soft skills like team work is can be complicated unless certain people are in the interview. This can be difficult when everybody is busy with his or her own work.</p>
<p>Therefore, traditional methods to recruit candidates such as adverts in websites might be inadequate because it difficult or impossible to determine whether a candidate has the expertise and talent. It would appear interesting to be able to evaluate these important skills. As a result, hackathons have become an attractive option.</p>
<p>What is hackathon? Hackathons are an original and effective way to find candidates for open tech positions by engaging hidden talents with coding competitions. During online challenges professionals can show off their skills and get hired. This way, organisations can discover &amp; recruit new talents, assess programming skills, improve time-to-hire, and source innovations.</p>
<p>Hackathons offer a unique environment for both recruiters and job seekers. Why? Recruiters can prepare specific problems of interest to different companies. For instance a group of companies could be interested in SAP or maybe in C++ whereas companies looking for web developers may prefer problems based on PHP.</p>
<p>Check also: Hackathon Ideas (upcoming hackathon)</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1749" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/How-to-Find-a-Perfect-Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="How to Find a Perfect Developer for you Company" width="1709" height="803"></p>
<p>Why would candidates attend to such an event? Hackathons, or coding competitions, are popular because of the rewards, which may or may not include a financial price. But usually, it is the prestige that attracts the most brilliant professionals, thus becoming a win-win situation for both recruiters and job-seekers.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Small and Medium Business Insurance</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/small-and-medium-business-insurance.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/small-and-medium-business-insurance.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-11T12:38:56+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/164/Screenshot_4-1.png" alt="" />
                    [Hello, dear readers. In this article, we will tell you about business insurance. Today you will learn: Business insurance is a product through which you can save your capital and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/164/Screenshot_4-1.png" alt="" />
                <p>[Hello, dear readers. In this article, we will tell you about business insurance.</p>
<p><strong>Today you will learn:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>For what it is necessary to insurance business;</li>
<li>Types of risks in business;</li>
<li>Which company provide risk-free business insurance services and how much does it cost?</li>
</ol>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn980">What is Business Insurance?</h2>
<p>Business insurance is a product through which you can save your capital and continue working without financial loss.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn991">Why insure your business?</h2>
<p>This question may arise in those who are just starting their own business, sometimes by trial and error.</p>
<p>If you have created the whole business of your life, have a good client base and create competition to other companies, then you should take care that it does not collapse in a single moment because of unforeseen circumstances.</p>
<p><strong>Of course</strong>, many young entrepreneurs are trying to save their own money and do not believe that there can be a fire, an accident, or that someone will fail or someone will "throw" on the money. But you will agree, it is pleasant to work and know that at any moment everything can be restored, at the expense of the received insurance payment.</p>
<p>It can be concluded that insurance for your business is an additional "safety cushion" for your business. The main thing is to evaluate the business and choose the right insurance product.</p>
<p><strong>Therefore,</strong> if you are just starting to develop, do not negatively react to proposals from insurance companies. It is better to carefully study the commercial proposals of several insurers and purchase a lucrative contract.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn992">Advantages of business insurance.</h2>
<p>Advantages of business insurance are obvious:</p>
<p><strong>Protection against financial losses and bankruptcy.</strong> In a market economy, opening a business is a risky business. The customer base will not be accumulated in one day. To reduce the losses that may arise as a result of commercial activities, it is worth buying insurance protection.</p>
<p><strong>Protection of real estate.</strong> The room in which you operate may be affected by a fire, explosion or natural disasters. The cost of restoration can be large. It is through insurance that you can repair the property.</p>
<p><strong>Staff insurance.</strong> The availability of experienced and qualified personnel is the key to the introduction of a successful business. The protected team feels calmer and loyal to the company's management.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn993">Entrepreneurial risks.</h2>
<p>Every business activity involves high risks. The best way to protect yourself against possible losses is to purchase a business insurance agreement.</p>
<p><strong>The main types of risks:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>External</strong>. This type of risk does not depend on the activities of the company. This includes inflation and changing demand in the market.</li>
<li><strong>Internal.</strong> These are risks that arise solely through the fault of the enterprise itself. Here it is possible to single out a strike or an incorrectly drawn up business plan for the development of one's own business.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>By the factor of occurrence,</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Political,</strong> connected and changing the political situation in the country;</li>
<li><strong>Economic</strong>, arising due to adverse changes in the economy.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Classification of risks in the area of occurrence:</strong></p>
<p>Production risk associated with non-fulfillment of obligations to produce goods or services;</p>
<ul>
<li>Commercial risk arising from the sale of goods and services;</li>
<li>Financial risk is related to non-fulfillment of financial obligations;</li>
<li>Insurance risk is associated with possible losses that will arise as a result of the occurrence of the insured event.</li>
<li>An innovative risk is associated with the emergence of new technologies and the emergence of a new, more sophisticated product on the market.</li>
</ul>
<p>For the correct choice of insurance protection it is worth taking into account:</p>
<ul>
<li>What risks can be at the enterprise?</li>
<li>The probability of occurrence of each risk;</li>
<li>Losses that you incur as a result of each risk.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The assessment of future damage is based on the following methods:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Analysis of all company activities;</li>
<li>Comparison of own forecasts and data obtained from the involved specialists;</li>
<li>The use of the experience of other enterprises that work in a similar industry.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn994">Types of business insurance.</h2>
<p>Even the most courageous entrepreneurs, who are not the first day in business, do not forget to "make themselves straws." Business insurance is an obligatory process that can not be neglected and postponed for later.</p>
<p>There are several types of risk insurance:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Property insurance.</strong> In this case, the products, equipment, and premises are subject to insurance;</li>
<li><strong>From the production break.</strong> For example, you have a fire in the company. You will not be able to quickly restore the workflow. It is necessary to spend time on repair work, purchase of new equipment. Do not forget about the wages of employees, which no one has canceled and all mandatory tax deductions. Insurance will be able to compensate for all the expenses that you incur in such a situation;</li>
<li><strong>Insurance of business liability to third parties</strong>. Under this agreement, all liabilities to partners will be insured. For example, also in the event of a fire, you will not be able to fulfill the obligations in full. The insurance company compensates all penalties, which will be exposed as a result of the occurrence of the insured event.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn995">Property insurance</h2>
<p>Let's say that you opened a business, rented an office or bought your own premises. In addition to the premises, you had to buy the necessary equipment and furniture. If it is a question of big business and production of goods, then the expensive equipment is needed. Here all the acquired property can suffer at any moment.</p>
<p>Under the contract, you can ensure:</p>
<ul>
<li>The building itself and the buildings and buildings attached to it;</li>
<li>Material values;</li>
<li>Money in the vault or safe;</li>
<li>Techniques: computers, telephones, fax machines, printers, scanners, etc .;</li>
<li>Interior items.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn996">Insurance against production interruption.</h2>
<p>Business can not work around the clock. There can be scheduled days for rest - these are weekends and holidays. But what to do with unplanned work days, which can appear due to force majeure circumstances?</p>
<p>As a result of downtime, you:</p>
<ul>
<li>Losses in the form of lost profits;</li>
<li>You will have to spend money on damages, and this is unplanned expenses;</li>
<li>Have to pay salaries to their employees, taxes, and rents.</li>
</ul>
<p>Compensate for all costs will help the insurance company.</p>
<p>Also, it is worth remembering about an additional useful insurance package:</p>
<ul>
<li>Voluntary insurance of employees ;</li>
<li>Civil liability to third parties;</li>
<li>Vehicle insurance company;</li>
<li>Insurance of goods during transportation.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn997">Liability Insurance.</h2>
<p>This is an excellent protection, if, due to unforeseen circumstances, you have caused harm to the customer and he has a complaint.</p>
<p>Let's say you decided to open a beauty salon. Your employee, when applying a mask to the client, incorrectly mixed the cosmetic substances and the client appeared redness and burns on the face. Agree, a very unpleasant situation.</p>
<p>If the injured customer makes a claim to the salon, you will have to pay compensation. But you will not be paid, but the insurance company, within the insured amount.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn998">Small Business Insurance.</h2>
<p>For a small business, any unforeseen situation can turn into a great tragedy. In most cases, there are no reserve funds for small businesses, and due to working capital, the damage cannot be compensated. In such a situation, insurance protection will help to minimize possible losses.</p>
<p>At the moment, small business insurance includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Business Liability Insurance;</li>
<li>Property insurance;</li>
<li>Possible losses in production.</li>
</ul>
<p>It is also worth knowing that if a novice businessman wants to take a loan from a bank to open a business, the bank will take care of the security of assets that will serve as collateral. In this case, the registration of a business insurance agreement will become a prerequisite.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn999">Medium Business Insurance.</h2>
<p>Today, economic conditions cannot be called stable. This applies to the whole world. Every day you can hear about financial crises, which can affect the activities of large companies. But how to survive afloat representatives of medium-sized businesses? This business is in a special risk zone.</p>
<p>Experienced insurance consultants advise to acquire protection against force majeure, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fires;</li>
<li>Accidents, including utilities;</li>
<li>Change or illness of employees;</li>
<li>Official crimes;</li>
<li>Equipment failure.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cost of business insurance services.</strong></p>
<p>Insurance companies offer several business insurance programs. You can make a calculation even on the official website of the insurance company <a href="https://www.roseboroughinsurance.com/business-insurance-tulsa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.roseboroughinsurance.com/business-insurance-tulsa/</a>, or by calling the operator on a toll-free customer support phone.</p>
<p>The listed companies have a comprehensive business insurance program that guarantees full protection in the event of an insured event.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Types of Credit / Debit Cards - How to Get Prepaid VISA &amp; MasterCard Cards</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/types-of-credit-debit-cards-how-to-get-prepaid-visa-and-mastercard-cards.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/types-of-credit-debit-cards-how-to-get-prepaid-visa-and-mastercard-cards.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-11T12:40:25+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/163/Screenshot_4.png" alt="" />
                     In this article, I am reviewing the TBF Finance https://tbffinance.com/visa-cards.php. TBF Finance Payment cards proved to be the safest way to keep your funds and use them all across&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/163/Screenshot_4.png" alt="" />
                <p> </p>
<p>In this article, I am reviewing the TBF Finance https://tbffinance.com/visa-cards.php. TBF Finance Payment cards proved to be the safest way to keep your funds and use them all across the real and electronic world. TBF Finance provides easy, safe and convenient opportunity to make purchases both off and online, travel worldwide, buy tickets, book hotel or rent a car on the internet.</p>
<p><strong>Visa</strong><br> <strong>Visa</strong> Inc. American multinational corporation for financial services. The head office is in San Francisco, California, USA. Visa is a global payment company that provides the ability to make money transfers around the world, most often with Visa's proprietary debit and credit cards. Visa Inc. was founded in 1976.</p>
<p><strong>Visa Inc.</strong> provides financial centers with Visa corporate identity products, which they use to offer debit, credit, prepaid and cash access programs to their customers. Visa does not ensure the issuance of cards, the provision of loans or the establishment of tariffs and commissions for customers. One of Visa's branded payment products is well-known cards.</p>
<p>The volume of processed operations and the number of customers is impressive with an incredibly increased volume. In 2010, Visa Inc. a global network (known as VisaNet) processed 67 billion transfers for a total of $ 5.2 trillion.</p>
<p>Visa operates in Central and South America, the Caribbean, North America, the Asia-Pacific region, Central and Eastern Europe, the Middle East and Africa, in more than 200 countries, people can use virtual currency instead of cash and checks. Since 1986 Visa Inc. was the worldwide sponsor of the Olympic Games and the only card that is accepted in all Olympic venues.</p>
<p>Read: Amazing Andalusia Tour Guide &amp;#038; Its Good Services for Booking Taxi Marbella in Andalucia Tours</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvprigi0">Visa offers 3 types of cards: credit, debit and prepaid.</h2>
<p><strong>Credit cards</strong><br> With Visa credit cards you can quickly, conveniently and safely make purchases, they give you the opportunity to pay bills, travel around the world and withdraw cash anywhere in the world. Cards are accepted in more than 200 countries.</p>
<p>In addition, the Visa card is widely used on the Internet. It meets all the necessary security requirements and enables its users to use a wide range of additional services.</p>
<p><strong>Visa</strong> card is accepted in millions of outlets, so for credit cards, you will find a wide application, including restaurants and entertainment, paying bills, online books, music, movies, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Debit cards</strong><br> A <strong>Visa debit card</strong> helps its owner to make purchases, pay bills and buy on the Internet simply, quickly and reliably, as with credit cards. A Visa debit card is ideal for those who first encounter a payment card and who do not have a banking history. You can apply</p>
<p>A debit card, which is attached to a debit account, allows the holder to track the completed transfers, usually indicated in the bank's monthly report, as well as allow for better control of expenses.</p>
<p><strong>Prepaid Cards</strong><br> Visa issuer banks have the opportunity to offer prepaid Visa cards with prepaid limits to their customers. This type does not imply the presence of a constantly updated bank account and is usually intended for small daily purchases. Prepaid cards can be virtual, with a magnetic strip and with a built-in chip. As for the Virtual Visa card: it is a virtual card, designed exclusively for use on the Internet.</p>
<p>The first virtual card was released in 1999, in Kuwait. The virtual Visa card has its own number and the effective date. It can not be used in a regular store. on it, there are no features of the usual card, magnetic stripe, the trademark of the payment system and the place for the signature. Thus, a Virtual Visa card is an excellent addition to an existing debit or credit card Visa.</p>
<p><strong>Mastercard</strong><br> <strong>MasterCard</strong> is an international financial services corporation. The central office is in New York, USA. <strong>MasterCard</strong> Inc. was founded in 1966, now the service of electronic money transfers operates all over the world. <strong>MasterCard</strong>, inherently known as Master Charge.</p>
<p>The company was created from several banks in California. <strong>MasterCard</strong>'s main business is to process payments between merchant banks and cards of issuing banks or credit communities of buyers that use proprietary "MasterCard" debit and credit cards to make purchases.</p>
<p><strong>MasterCard</strong> Worldwide has been a public company since 2006. Mastercard is the sponsor of most world sporting events, such as the UEFA Champions League, the Canadian Hockey League Memorial Cup and many others.</p>
<p>From the first days of the existence of credit cards to wireless payment functions these days, MasterCard Worldwide has stimulated the industry by directing this evolution. Being in the center of commerce, MasterCard makes it easier, smoother, faster and more secure, introducing understanding and innovation in the payment process.</p>
<p>In 2001,<strong> MasterCard</strong> introduced new changes in the structure, which showed a new hope for the company. In 2002 MasterCard Worldwide merged with Europay International, which allowed creating a single global corporate structure. After the merger, the company became a private joint-stock corporation.</p>
<p><strong>MasterCard</strong> also offers its customers debit, credit, and prepaid cards. They are divided into types, for example, standard, gold, platinum, worldwide credit MasterCards, gift cards or tourist cards.</p>
<p>MasterCard Worldwide continues to provide a unique mix of competence and the use of global resources used by the company in order to provide a quality product to users who choose MasterCard. MasterCard always brings innovation and a growing number of products/services.</p>
<p>Next: <a href="http://Why You Should Join TEFL Programs in Spain" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Why You Should Join TEFL Programs in Spain</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Get The Most Suitable Event Wifi Solutions From Trade Show Internet</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/get-the-most-suitable-event-wifi-solutions-from-trade-show-internet.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/get-the-most-suitable-event-wifi-solutions-from-trade-show-internet.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/162/NEW_TSI_LOGO.png" alt="" />
                    If you are hosting an exhibit, a fashion show or any automotive event, reliable and fast internet connectivity is required. For all events, this is a major requirement in order&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/162/NEW_TSI_LOGO.png" alt="" />
                <p>If you are hosting an exhibit, a fashion show or any automotive event, reliable and fast internet connectivity is required. For all events, this is a major requirement in order to enhance the attendee experience. If you are looking <a href="https://tradeshowinternet.com/services/event-WiFi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for the most suitable event wifi solutions</a>, then Trade Show Internet is your best option. They provide internet solutions for both indoor and outdoor events. It does not matter the venue; they have customized solutions for their clients to ensure that they get flawless internet.</p>
<p>During New York art fair and the release of Warner Bros movie wonder woman, Trade Show Internet provided internet solutions. They also provided IT solutions during Footwear show this year as well as Uber summit event. These are some of their clients who rely on Trade Show Internet for event IT during their major events.</p>
<p>The most important thing to bear in mind when looking for internet service provider when hosting the event is the options they have. Check for service level guarantee as well as network design, bandwidth, and the on-site event IT management during the event. If you do so, then you will not be disappointed. Trade Show Internet ensures that you get the best wifi solutions suitable for the event.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>3 key Tips to Make Your Website User-friendly</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-key-tips-to-make-your-website-user-friendly.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-key-tips-to-make-your-website-user-friendly.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:56+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Firstly, meet your target audienceTo make something works well, you should know who you design it for. So, the first step in creating a user-friendly website is analyzing your target group. Ask yourself&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Firstly, meet your target audience</h2>
<p>To make something works well, you should know who you design it for. So, the first step in creating a user-friendly website is <strong>analyzing your target group</strong>. Ask yourself some questions referring to your readers, for example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Why do they visit your page and what do they expect to find there?</li>
<li>In which circumstances do they visit your page?</li>
<li>What is the problem that your website can solve?</li>
<li>Who are your users? What’s the way they use an Internet?</li>
<li>Are they people with any disabilities?</li>
</ul>
<p>A user-friendly design usually uses so-called Personas. They are 2-3 representatives of your target group and they can help you understand your users better. <strong>Describe your Personas as detailed as possible and then plan the page for the sake of their needs, lifestyles, and qualities</strong>. It will increase your chance of creating a highly user-friendly website.</p>
<h2>Secondly, take care of UX best practices</h2>
<p>The essence of so-called <em>User Experience</em> is to make the product as easy for users as possible. In case of web design, <em>Usability</em> means <strong>making your readers experience intuitive</strong>. It should be so seamless and problem-free for users that almost invisible. <strong>There are some best practices that will help you make your page intuitive</strong>. The list of basic tips includes, for example, what follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>Name the elements of your page’s menus accurately to their content.</li>
<li>Add to your page a navigation bar. It will help your users stay oriented about their location on a page. It will also enable them to come back to any previous step of their web journey.</li>
<li>Make sure your page is responsive and looks good at any devices: smartphones, tablets, desktops.</li>
<li>Take care of your page load time. Check if there is no surplus of the website’s code and then make sure your page loads as fast as possible.</li>
<li>Do UX audits for your page regularly. Check the possible users’ journey and make sure there are no so-calls dead ends, for example.</li>
<li>Make sure there is a home button on your page. It is good to place it as a link under your logo. It helps users come back to the home page in case they get lost.</li>
<li>Keep a weather eye on how your website looks like. Make sure about the font readability, the usage of colors, the quality of graphics.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Thirdly, follow the trends</h2>
<p>If you want to create a <a href="https://cut2code.com/3-key-tips-on-how-to-make-your-website-user-friendly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">user-friendly website</a>, be up to date with UX trends. If more and more pages use, for example, face recognition or gesture-based interactions, after some time these trends can become standards. Of course, sometimes it is not rational to keep up with the Joneses blindly. But, <strong>some trends can be related to your industry and not respecting them may be a sign of the backwardness of your brand</strong>. So, keep your finger on the heartbeat.</p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://cut2code.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">How to cut PSD to HTML</a></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Amazing Andalusia Tour Guide &amp; Its Good Services for Booking Taxi Marbella in Andalucia Tours</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/amazing-andalusia-tour-guide-and-its-good-services-for-booking-taxi-marbella-in-andalucia-tours.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/amazing-andalusia-tour-guide-and-its-good-services-for-booking-taxi-marbella-in-andalucia-tours.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:54+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="" />
                    Those who have never been to Andalusia, and only heard from friends about the beauty of this place in the south of Spain. The edge of sun and joy, magnificent&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="" />
                <p>Those who have never been to Andalusia, and only heard from friends about the beauty of this place in the south of Spain. The edge of sun and joy, magnificent nature and unusual man-made beauties will undoubtedly fascinate you and will not let go without a desire to visit it again.</p>
<h2>AMAZING ANDALUSIA - A PLACE WHERE YOU WANT TO COME BACK</h2>
<p>From the first moments of the stay, the travelers are surprised by the positiveness and friendliness of the local population. Growing up under the rays of the southern sun Andalusians, absorbed his energy and cheerfulness, and therefore generously share it with their numerous guests. And the guests come to Andalusia a lot because there are really many opportunities for a variety of recreation.</p>
<p>Nobody is indifferent to the magnificent cities of the province: Seville, Granada, Malaga ( Marbella is its city visit once in your life) and Ronda and others, managing to harmoniously combine the precious heritage of the past and the rhythms of modern life. It is these cities that make up the so-called Heart of Andalusia and best characterize its unusually passionate and quivering temperament.</p>
<p>Surprisingly beautiful against the backdrop of the hills and valleys are the white villages of Andalusia, attracting the attention of tourists to<a href="https://bookingtaximarbella.com/tours-booking-taxi-marbella/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> tour in Taxi of Andalucia</a> and admiring their unusual.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1712" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="Andalucía Tours in taxi" width="1834" height="812" /></p>
<p>Traveling along this edge, be sure to check at least one of them - each has its own charm. If you are looking for a good service for booking taxi Marbella in Andalucia tours or Malaga airport to Marbella, here is<a href="https://bookingtaximarbella.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> a good service for booking taxi Marbella in Andalucia tours</a>.</p>
<p>The coast of Andalusia is ideal for beach holidays, and therefore its famous resorts from the Atlantic and from the Mediterranean Sea are never empty during the season. Small beaches in numerous coves near the cities are always filled with vacationers, so for a rest in peace, it is worthwhile to get out or rent yachts, and pleasure boats.<br />
The city beaches are clean and equipped with everything necessary, and also have reputable fun on the water. Do not be bored and lovers of outdoor activities, come with or without children: water parks and entertainment centers, zoos and aquariums, a safari park and numerous protected areas guarantee a full and out of boring holiday at any time of the year. From the first spring months to the end of the harvest season, numerous festivals take place in the provinces.</p>
<p>Andalusia is famous for its splendid weather - sunny days on its territory are rarely replaced by foul weather, and even during the winter months, it offers tourists many interesting activities. Before the New Year holidays in the cities of the province, there are numerous sales, so that rest at this time can be successfully combined with a successful shopping.</p>
<p>Unforgettable experiences await the visitors to the unique mountain resort of Sierra Nevada - from December to April its slopes accept everyone who wants to go, and from the highest peaks, one can see the sunny beaches of the Costa del Sol. The resort pays much attention to the beginners: in addition to numerous special trails and instructors, there are also good services for booking the taxi from Malaga airport to Costa del Sol.</p>
<p>The tourist industry in Andalusia is thriving, and numerous hotels on the coastal resorts are always ready to welcome guests. Depending on the composition of the group, age, and interests, you can choose different places: near the beaches or from the historical part, on the outskirts or in the city center.</p>
<p>There is also an exotic tour booking taxi Marbella, allowing to combine accommodation with travel - train-hotel Al Andalus, which is often called a palace on wheels. With comfort and convenience, the tour participants visit all the important cities of the provinces and inspect most of the sights, enjoying in between gorgeous restaurant dishes and a pleasant stay in the tea rooms.</p>
<p>Rest in Andalusia is sure to please all members of the family because interesting activities can be found here for everyone. The charm of the ancient East and the energy of the modern West wonderfully intertwined in this wonderful corner of the world, and the chic nature and the dazzling sun only underline his magical aura.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>SSL certificate – make your website secure and don’t fall into Google’s disfavour</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/ssl-certificate-make-your-website-secure-and-dont-fall-into-googles-disfavour.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/ssl-certificate-make-your-website-secure-and-dont-fall-into-googles-disfavour.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:52+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/159/images.jpg" alt="" />
                    The year 2018 is marked by the safety of Internet users. SSL certificate will soon become Google's ranking factor, but its possession will also be enforced by GDPR controls. Check how to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/159/images.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The year 2018 is marked by the safety of Internet users. SSL certificate will soon become Google's ranking factor, but its possession will also be enforced by GDPR controls. Check how to make your website secure and not to expose your business to losses.</p>
<h2>How to make your website secure with an SSL certificate?</h2>
<p>An <a href="https://fixmakers.com/blog/ssl-certificate-on-your-website/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">SSL certificate</a> (<em>Secure Socket Layer</em>) is an Internet protocol that <strong>encrypts the connection between the browser (your user) and your website server</strong>. After implementing the SSL certificate on your website, the HTTP protocol will turn into a secure <strong>HTTPS protocol</strong>. When connecting the browser and server, this protocol uses an AES key (for example 256-bit) to encrypt the data. Such an algorithm cannot be deciphered by hackers. This means that <strong>the data that the user sends to your website, e.g. credit card details, is fully protected and there is no risk of being stolen</strong>.</p>
<h3>What threatens pages lacking HTTPS protocol?</h3>
<p>Users can easily recognize if your site is secured with an SSL certificate and, as a result, whether the data they send is protected. They can get to know it by <strong>the address bar of your site</strong>. It starts with the HTTPS protocol, has an additional padlock icon on the left side of the address or is all marked in green.</p>
<p>Even if any of the users overlook the lack of SSL on your site, Google will eagerly remind them about it. <strong>Google announced that from July 2018, it will mark websites without HTTPS as </strong><strong><em>Not Secure</em></strong>. This notification will be displayed to users before they enter your site. In this case, you are exposed to a decrease in Internet users' trust in your site and, as a result, a drop in traffic. What’s important, SSL certificate will soon become an important Google’s ranking factor which means that <strong>secure websites will reach high positions and vice versa</strong>.</p>
<p>Do you think that's everything? Nothing more wrong. <strong>In May 2018, the so-called GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), will impose an obligation on websites that collect/process users' personal data to secure such data with an </strong><strong>SSL certificate</strong>. If you do not comply with the new law, you are threatened with high financial penalties.</p>
<h2>What to remember when buying SSL?</h2>
<p>Above all, <strong>take care of the confidentiality of your private key</strong>. You will get it in the package with the SSL certificate purchased, and <strong>it will be stored on the secure server of your site</strong>. Remember that if you disclose your private key to anyone, you increase the risk of breaking the encryption. <strong>The disclosure may occur, for example, in the situation of sending a private key by e-mail to your employee</strong>. When the private key is revealed, you will not be able to generate a new private key for the current SSL certificate. You will need to buy a new certificate.</p>
<p><strong>Remember:</strong> After any encryption component has leaked, you must immediately revoke the certificates and keys, and then buy, generate and install them again.</p>
<p>When purchasing an SSL certificate, <strong>do research on the certification authorities that you want to buy the certificate from</strong>. In the history of the Internet, there were situations when some offices were thrown from browsers, and the SSL certificates issued by them were revoked. The company named <em>Symantec</em> and its products may serve as the most recent example of such situation. The company employees have sent clients' private keys via e-mail. After this incident, Symantec’s clients were informed about the situation and warned that their SSL certificates would cease to be active within 24 hours.</p>
<p><strong>Remember:</strong> Before choosing an institution that issues you with an SSL certificate, familiarize yourself with its history and reputation.</p>
<h2>Be aware of possible implementation errors</h2>
<p>You are already aware of threats more or less dependent on you. So, it's time to make you sensitive to errors that may arise from technical omissions when implementing the certificate. For some of them, you may need an<a href="https://fixmakers.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> HTML help</a>. The most common omissions when implementing SSL certificate include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Forgetting about 301 redirects</strong>. After implementing the SSL certificate, you create a second version of the page. If you do not take care of <strong>redirects from the HTTP version to the HTTPS one</strong>, for Google it will be a signal that you have duplicated the content. And a duplicate content may sometimes impact search engine rankings. Negatively, of course.</li>
<li><strong>Forgetting about page indexing</strong>. After implementing the SSL certificate, check if Google's robots can see your HTTPS subpages. It may turn out that they are invisible to Google's robots, and as a result – <strong>your subpages are not visible to users in the search results</strong>.</li>
<li><strong>Forgetting about testing</strong>. After implementing SSL on your website, <strong>make sure that there are no gaps in the implementation</strong>. The tool that will help you verify this is, for example, <em>ssllabs.com</em>. The site will do the SSL implementation audit and will give you the appropriate rating. If it's lower than A, you'll get information on what needs to be corrected and how to do it.</li>
</ul>
<p>The above errors are just a parcel of this, which is often overlooked when implementing SSL on the site. This is especially true of small websites that do it on their own and do not have access to professional support in this area. It is important, however, <strong>not to avoid using the help of IT companies offering </strong><strong>HTML help</strong>. Especially that incorrect implementation of SSL may put your business at risk.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why You Should Join TEFL Programs in Spain</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/why-you-should-join-tefl-programs-in-spain.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/why-you-should-join-tefl-programs-in-spain.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:50+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/158/TEFL-programs-in-Spain.png" alt="" />
                    Do you want to be an English teacher with an official degree? Do you want to work up to 30 hours a week on your own, earning from 15 Euros&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/158/TEFL-programs-in-Spain.png" alt="" />
                <p>Do you want to be an English teacher with an official degree?</p>
<p>Do you want to work up to 30 hours a week on your own, earning from 15 Euros per hour?</p>
<p>Do you want to work in a sector where the demand for workers NEVER fails?</p>
<p>If you are interested or know someone who may have an interest in teacher training in order to have a decent job, you are in the right place.</p>
<p>Nowadays, learning foreign languages is an inescapable necessity for human beings, since the level of development achieved by the societies of the third millennium as a result of their economic and cultural integration demands the mastery of them. This linguistic reality imposes great challenges to the apprentices since in addition to the mastery of their mother tongue they must develop their communicative competence in a certain Foreign Language and in different communicative contexts.</p>
<p>The teaching of foreign languages is a complex process since it involves defining an appropriate methodology, a conception of language and the application of a didactic strategy that facilitates the learner's development of their linguistic abilities according to their communicative needs. In addition, the way of teaching foreign languages is related to the predominant linguistic approach, this means that there is a close relationship between the current linguistic theory and the methodology applied in the foreign language classroom.</p>
<p>For example, in some manuals of teaching English as a foreign language, we find guidelines where learners are asked to memorize linguistic structures, repeat long dialogues and try to imitate the accent of native speakers, activities typical of a structuralist - behavioral methodology, which conceives learning as a set of habits.</p>
<p>In the TEFL Madrid Academy, many young people and teenagers have had the opportunity to learn foreign languages in academies. In some way, the learning of foreign languages has developed constantly for various purposes. Let's see the following cases:</p>
<p>The need to learn English to work in a Call Center, a space where young people with English skills are required and an adequate development of language skills, specifically oral expression. Since during their educational period they will have the possibility of traveling to France to teach Spanish in middle schools, so they need an advanced knowledge of their Language Object of Study.</p>
<p>TEFL course Madrid Spain - Approved course that complies with the regulations of the TEFL courses.</p>
<p>If you want to be an English teacher with official qualifications, working up to 30 hours a week on your own, earning from 15 Euros an hour and employed within a sector where NEVER fails the demand for workers, this is the essential course for you. Join TEFL programs in Spain here.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What is Pakcoin - The First Pakistani Cryptocurrency</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-is-pakcoin-the-first-pakistani-cryptocurrency.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-is-pakcoin-the-first-pakistani-cryptocurrency.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:47+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/157/what-is-pakcoincrypto.jpg" alt="" />
                    Introduction Of Pakcoin - The First Pakistani CryptocurrencyPakcoin is a Pakistani cryptocurrency. However, this is not a government currency. It was created primarily for Pakistanis at home and abroad. A&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/157/what-is-pakcoincrypto.jpg" alt="" />
                <h2>Introduction Of Pakcoin - The First Pakistani Cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>Pakcoin is a Pakistani cryptocurrency. However, this is not a government currency. It was created primarily for Pakistanis at home and abroad. A PakCoin is currently worth $ 0.03. Total market capitalization is $ 1.6 million, of which approximately $ 26,000 is traded daily. (As of 10.01.2018)</p>
<h2>Pakcoin - The Cryptocurrency</h2>
<p>The coin was officially announced on June 22, 2015. It was specially designed for Pakistani to be used at home and abroad. Nevertheless, anyone who is interested in the cryptocurrency has PAK mines and act. In total there should be 182 million PAHs. The blocking time for mining is one minute. Miners get a reward of 50 PAK for each block found. Every three years, the reward per block is halved. The developer of PakCoin, Mr. Shaheer, also established the Gravity Well algorithm, which means that the Difficulty is readjusted after each block. Overall, 10% was premined, which equates to approximately 18.2 million PACs. The cryptocurrency works with the Scrypt algorithm and is based on the Litecoin. All in all, the cryptocurrency is a simple peer-to-peer currency, which is organized in a decentralized manner. A peculiarity of the cryptocurrency is that the first 150,000 Pakistani receive 50 PAHs for free when they register.</p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KOx6h-7A0-I?rel=0&amp;controls=0&amp;showinfo=0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<h2>Pakcoin - The Roadmap</h2>
<p>In the founding year of Pakcoin, the cryptocurrency was already on two crypto exchanges registered. In 2016, three more crypto exchanges and two private hospitals followed, accepting the coin as a means of payment. In 2017, an initiative was taken by the developer to use the Pakcoin in other Pakistani stores. In addition, the website was established and international marketing initiated. For the year 2018, the developer plans a payment gateway. In addition, the cryptocurrency is to be accepted as a means of payment in several online shops. Another feature is smart contracts, which are to be integrated into the concept of the Pakcoin. Next year, the PAKPAY Card will be launched, a type of credit card. Furthermore, a further education campaign is to be started, whereby interested parties can inform themselves about the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Where can Pakcoin be bought?</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency can be purchased and traded on the crypto exchanges Cryptopia, NovaExchange, and Yobit. The cryptocurrency developer also provides wallets for Linux, Windows, Android, and iOS. There is also an eWallet and a Paper Wallet. The PAH is to be accepted in several stores in Pakistan in the long term. The cryptocurrency is said to become the most popular and widely used in Pakistan. Fundamentally, people in Pakistan should be able to decide for themselves how to handle their finances, independent of banks in Pakistan.</p>
<h3>Conclusion</h3>
<p>The cryptocurrency Pakcoin is not an official national cryptocurrency in Pakistan. However, it has been established for Pakistanis so that they can pay easily at home and abroad. The focus is on financial independence. Nevertheless, anyone interested can mine and trade PAHs at any time.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to Use Viber for Windows - Featured Some Interesting Updates, Including Video Chats</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-viber-for-windows-featured-some-interesting-updates-including-video-chats.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-viber-for-windows-featured-some-interesting-updates-including-video-chats.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:45+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/156/How-to-Use-Viber-For-Windows.jpg" alt="" />
                    After the recent update of Viber for the desktop and mobile platform, we thought that it would be nice to give our readers a complete guide to using Viber on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/156/How-to-Use-Viber-For-Windows.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>After the recent update of Viber for the desktop and mobile platform, we thought that it would be nice to give our readers a complete guide to using Viber on various devices. This guide will focus on Viber for Windows, which featured some interesting updates, including video chats.</p>
<h2>How effective Viber for windows?</h2>
<p><strong>Viber</strong> is fast and easy to use, which makes it another convenient way to stay in touch with users, regardless of where you need to communicate. Using Viber on the move and on the desktop of your PC, you can always stay in touch. If you are looking for a new messaging program, Viber is the application that you should definitely try. Viber for Windows has many features, Some of them are:</p>
<p><strong>1</strong>. Make best Quality HD Voice call from Windows.<br />
<strong>2</strong>. Make text, photo and sticker messages from Windows.<br />
<strong>3</strong>. Give you full sync between your mobile and Windows.<br />
4. Transfer ongoing calls between Smartphone and Windows.<br />
Since Viber is available on almost all platforms, you have no reason not to use it.</p>
<p>Read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-fb-messenger-in-web-browser/">How to Use FB Messenger in Web Browser</a></p>
<h2>How to get started with Viber for Windows?</h2>
<p>To get started with the Viber application for your desktop PC, you must use a mobile account. You can not use the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/you-can-try-the-explore-section-in-the-web-version-of-facebook/">desktop version</a> of Viber without it. Read the Viber version guide for Android and iOS to set up your mobile account. When you are ready, go to the Viber site and <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/recommends/here-to-download-google-chrome-facebook-video-downloader/">download the version for Windows</a>. It may be more convenient to download Viber from the Viber site.</p>
<p><strong>Installation is simple</strong>, after completion, Viber will start to prepare you for using the service. Here you will need to set up your mobile account and, now, everything is ready to go. Click <strong>"Yes"</strong> to continue. Enter "Phone number", then click "Continue". You will be sent a Viber activation code to your phone.</p>
<p><strong>Enter this activation code</strong>, and then agree to the User License Agreement and press Enter. Now you are ready to start next<br />
step to using <strong>Viber for Windows</strong>.</p>
<p><strong>How to use desktop Viber - Viber for Windows?</strong></p>
<p>To simplify sending messages and making calls from a desktop computer, Viber for the desktop uses a very simple user interface:<br />
Click the icon in the lower-left corner of Viber. This will open the Viber settings, allowing you to adapt the service to your needs.</p>
<p>On the first <strong>"Basics"</strong> tab, the user can determine whether he wants to start Viber on startup and save messages when leaving the conversation. The audio and video settings allow you to specify which equipment to use for each of the functions in Viber.</p>
<p><strong>Notification settings</strong> allow you to choose whether to display notifications when new messages and calls appear. Account settings allow you to deactivate the Viber account on your computer if you feel it is necessary.</p>
<p><strong>Another section</strong> of the Viber settings allows you to <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/google-and-facebook-kings-of-internet/">connect your account to Facebook</a>, and share with others the fact that you use the service in social networks or by email. When you are ready, go back to the main Viber screen and click "Help". Whenever you want to learn more about Viber for a desktop PC or you need help with something specific, you can open the "Help" section to get it.</p>
<p>Now click on <strong>"Tools"</strong>. Here you can change the audio and video settings.</p>
<p><strong>Then click "Call"</strong>. You can use this functionality to interact with your contacts, for example, to initiate calls, answer calls, translate calls and even mute the sound or launch a video chat.</p>
<p><strong>Click "Conversation"</strong>. Use this option to interact with your contacts, for example, start a new chat, send photos or delete a conversation entry.</p>
<p><strong>Click "View"</strong>. This will show you various Viber elements, such as contacts, conversations, recent calls or messages and dialer.</p>
<p><strong>Now click the</strong> "Chat" icon in the menu on the left. This will show you all active and inactive chats, if they are available, you can also click "Create" to start a chat with someone.</p>
<p><strong>Click the People icon</strong>. It will show you those of your contacts on the phone that use Viber. You can also search for users and even invite people to join you in Viber.</p>
<p><strong>Click "Clock icon"</strong>. This will display your recent activity in Viber. This can be useful for viewing when you last spoke with someone, the details of a call or conversation.</p>
<p><strong>Now click "Phone icon"</strong>. This will open the dialer. You can manually dial the number to call if your contact uses Viber. You can also start a chat conversation this way.</p>
<p><strong>You can click on</strong> any contact at any time to start a conversation or chat with a friend in Viber. Even when you communicate in a traditional way, you can also use text chat.</p>
<p><strong>If you hover over</strong> a picture of a contact, you can change various settings even at the time of the call. You can start a video chat, mute the sound, end a call, change the volume, or switch to full-screen mode.</p>
<p><strong>If you press</strong> "Transfer a call", you can transfer the call to your mobile phone and vice versa. This is one of the coolest features offered by Viber, you can continue your calls no matter where you need to go.</p>
<p><strong>If you click "Video"</strong>, you can start a video chat with someone while they support it, and use the desktop version of Viber.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
