<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2019-11-19T07:46:05+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/personal-digital-assistant-cortana-will-leave-from-android-and-ios-beginning-2020.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/personal-digital-assistant-cortana-will-leave-from-android-and-ios-beginning-2020.html</id>

        <updated>2019-11-19T07:43:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." />
                    Cortana has been present in the form of applications for Android and iOS users in several countries. However, soon the digital assistant software will leave from both platforms. Cortana services&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." />
                <p><strong>Cortana</strong> has been present in the form of applications for <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/smartphones-2/" title="More Articles About SmartPhones ">Android</a> and iOS users in several countries. However, soon the digital assistant software will leave from both platforms. Cortana services for Android and iOS will be stopped from January 31, 2020.</p>
<p>The reason was revealed by Microsoft as the maker of Cortana in a statement on an <a href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/4531683" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">official website</a>. "To make Cortana useful, we integrate Cortana into Microsoft 365 and part of this change is to stop supporting Cortana applications on Android and iOS," Microsoft wrote.</p>
<p><img class="post__image align-right" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." width="568" height="335"></p>
<p class="msg msg--info"><em>Image Credit: Flickr: <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dcmot/22786860142" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Bolly Holly Baba</a></em></p>
<p><strong>Cortana</strong> for Android and iOS will be deactivated in a number of countries, including the United Kingdom, Canada, and Australia. Later it was known that Germany, Mexico, China, and Spain would be affected. Nevertheless, it is still unclear what about Cortana's fate on Android and iOS devices in other regions, such as the United States. It is also not certain whether Cortana will also be turned off completely on Android and iOS or will continue to be used after January 31, 2020.</p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">How to use WhatsApp without phone Number.</a><br><br>In addition, Cortana will also disappear from Microsoft's Android Launcher after the end of January next year in the countries mentioned above.</p>
<p><br>Microsoft first introduced Cortana for iOS and Android in 2015 to connect Windows 10 PCs with smartphones. Unfortunately, despite a number of an overhaul, Cortana still can not compete with competitors' digital assistants, such as Alexa or Google Assistant.</p>
<p>Read next: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html">5 Important Reasons to use Android Emularor</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-22T08:46:37+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/168/5-Important-Reasons-to-use-Android-Emulator.jpg" alt="5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator" />
                    Nowadays, users have preferred to use mobile devices to desktop PCs. Surfing on the Internet is one of the most popular activities for which it is not necessary to sit&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/168/5-Important-Reasons-to-use-Android-Emulator.jpg" alt="5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator" />
                <p><span >Nowadays, users have preferred to use mobile devices to desktop PCs. Surfing on the Internet is one of the most popular activities for which it is not necessary to sit in front of a computer or laptop. People publish status on social networks and launch games through their phone.</span></p>
<p><span >In this context, using Android emulators to play mobile games or run an application on a computer may seem counterintuitive. But in fact, the number of people using Android emulators is increasing. Why? Let's look at <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-factors-to-consider-before-buying-a-speaker.html">5 reasons</a> why a user may need to use an Android Emulator on their PC.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln70"><span >1. Android emulator gives you a bigger screen</span></h2>
<p><span >Keeping a close eye on your phone harms your eye. This is certainly not very good for your health. Moving from a small screen of a telephone to a large screen of a computer raises its head, also, the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-fix-blue-screen-problem-of-microsoft-windows.html">large screen has a better display</a>. This greatly improves your accuracy when pressed in games.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln81"><span >2. Saving the mobile phone battery</span></h2>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/take-photo-from-your-smartphone-and-earn-money.html">Cell phone</a> batteries are small and lightweight for portability, but this also means that they cannot last very long. Powerful games heat-up your phone and the battery runs down very quickly. No one wants to lose the battle because your phone is down and disconnected at the very last moment. Using the Android emulator, you never have to worry about power. You can watch videos or stay <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-best-smartphone-to-optimize-your-gaming-experience.html">connected in your favorite game</a> for as long as you need.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln92"><span >3. Launch multiple applications or use multiple accounts at the same time.</span></h2>
<p><span >Imagine that you could watch a video in any video sharing application without interrupting your <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">conversation on WhatsApp</a> or using multiple accounts for the game at the same time. That's fine, isn't it? Although not all Android emulators have this feature, with Nox App Player you can simultaneously run multiple instances of Android on your PC screen. Control your game in one of them, watch the video on the other and watch the conversation on WhatsApp on one big screen! </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln93"><span >4. The emulator allows you to replace the top-end Android phone</span></h2>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/tips-on-choosing-a-tablet-and-smartphone-to-play-games.html">Mobile games</a> are not just casual games. More and more hardcore games appear with a deep plot and complex gameplay. Accordingly, for a smooth and fast game, the graphics and display of the top device are required. The Android emulator will save you the budget to replace your phone since you can get for free this most “virtual, top-end Android phone” on your PC.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln94"><span >5. Access to mobile applications from a PC</span></h2>
<p><span >With the growing number of smartphones and mobile networks, many applications meet the specific needs of people. However, some of them, such as Instagram, are designed to work only on mobile devices. For people who would like to access these services in a more “traditional” way from a PC, an Android emulator is a great solution.</span></p>
<p><span >So you want to try the Android emulator? Download Nox App Player to take full advantage of the benefits mentioned above.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Important Factors to Consider Before Buying a Speaker</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-factors-to-consider-before-buying-a-speaker.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-factors-to-consider-before-buying-a-speaker.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-29T11:16:43+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/167/5-Important-Factors-to-Consider-Before-Buying-a-Speaker.jpg" alt="Buying a Speaker" />
                     Buying a speaker is certainly not the same as buying a smartphone. Why did it happen? The reason is simple because in buying speakers, we must pay attention to several&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/167/5-Important-Factors-to-Consider-Before-Buying-a-Speaker.jpg" alt="Buying a Speaker" />
                <h1 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vt0"> </h1>
<p><strong>Buying a speaker is certainly not the same as buying a smartphone.</strong></p>
<p><em>Why did it happen?</em></p>
<p><span >The reason is simple because in buying speakers, we must pay attention to <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/top-seven-tips-for-buying-a-gaming-computer.html">several important factors </a>such as the original sound quality of the speaker, type of speaker, and so on.</span></p>
<p><span >So, Today I am going to suggest you at least <strong>5 factors that are usually used by many experts before buying a speaker.</strong></span></p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vu1"><strong><span >1. Listen Sound Quality</span></strong></h4>
<p><span >Don't trust other people if the A or B speaker sounds good. Regardless of the popularity of those who say that the sound of a good speaker is different in every ear that hears it. Or in other words, the sound of the speaker is each individual's taste.</span></p>
<p><span >Therefore, when we want to buy a speaker, we have to directly listen to the sound produced by the speaker. </span></p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vv2"><strong><span >2. Pay Attention to Types of Speakers</span></strong></h4>
<p><span >Nowadays, there are many types of speakers that we can choose from various brands. </span></p>
<p><span >For the types of speakers, We know that there are several types such as </span><em><span >bookshelf speakers, soundbar speakers, floor-standing speakers, subwoofers</span></em><span > and many more. Here we must choose which one is suitable for us to use.</span></p>
<p><span >Suppose we want to use speakers on our PC or computer, then the type of speaker that usually matches a PC or computer is the type of </span><em><span >bookshelf speaker</span></em><span > or </span><em><span >soundbar speaker.</span></em></p>
<p><span >Then when we want to use the speakers on our television for entertainment purposes such as watching movies or karaoke with the family, the </span><em><span >floor-standing speaker</span></em><span > is the most appropriate.</span></p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vv3"><strong><span >3. The Room where the Speaker is used. </span></strong></h4>
<p><span >Not only the type of speaker and the sound of the speaker that must be considered, but the room where the speaker is used should also be taken into consideration. For example, a narrow room with an area of ​​6 x 5 square meters is not possible to use speakers with large sizes.</span></p>
<p><span >Similarly, in a room such as an auditorium, it is certainly not possible to use small </span><em><span >speakers</span></em><span > such as </span><em><span >bookshelf speakers</span></em><span > or </span><em><span >portable speakers.</span></em></p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vv4"><strong><span >4. Adjust to the Right Device</span></strong></h4>
<p><span >To present the maximum sound, a speaker must be paired with an </span><em><span >amplifier</span></em><span > or </span><em><span >receiver</span></em><span > that can deliver the appropriate </span><em><span >power.</span></em><span > For example, a speaker needs 30 - 100 Watts power to be able to work smoothly, the amplifier used must adjust to the speaker power.</span></p>
<p><span >Then when we want to make the speakers that we have </span><em><span >multi-channel</span></em><span > so that it can produce better sound. My recommendation is to pair the speakers that we have with other speakers of the same type and brand. Or if you want to be different, that's fine, but with my experience, it is best to pair the same brands. </span></p>
<p>Read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/review-the-5-most-effective-windows-backup-softwares.html">Review of the 5 Most Effective Windows Backup Softawares. </a></p>
<h4 id="mcetoc_1djdvj4vv5"><strong><span >5. Speaker Optimization</span></strong></h4>
<p><span >This one might only be done after we install the speakers in the room. The first is to optimize the sound released by making arrangements such as </span><em><span >treble, bass,</span></em><span > and others.</span></p>
<p><span >Then the next is the position of the speakers that are placed is safe, comfortable and can guarantee to provide maximum performance? If not, it's better to reposition again. So, have a nice day. </span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">How to use WhatsApp Without Phone Number? </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to use WhatsApp without a phone number</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-17T19:17:45+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/166/How-to-use-WhatsApp-without-a-phone-number.jpg" alt="How to use WhatsApp without a phone number" />
                    WhatsApp is a widespread text messaging, voice call and chat application used by many users around the world. WhatsApp Messenger is a complete messaging application that allows us to send&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/166/How-to-use-WhatsApp-without-a-phone-number.jpg" alt="How to use WhatsApp without a phone number" />
                <p>WhatsApp is a widespread text messaging, voice call and chat application used by many users around the world. WhatsApp Messenger is a complete messaging application that allows us to send text messages, photos, and media files for free. There are versions of WhatsApp for iPhone, BlackBerry, Android, <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-viber-for-windows-featured-some-interesting-updates-including-video-chats.html">Windows</a> Phone and Nokia, and these phones can save all your contact and chat data! WhatsApp uses the same Internet data transfer scheme that you use for email and web browsing. This allows you not to spend money on messages and stay in touch with friends.<br><br>Since many users use devices that do not have a SIM card like a mobile phone (such as a tablet or desktop PC), the problem is that in order to use WhatsApp without a phone number, you need to use one trick. It happens that you can not use your smartphone because of a breakdown. And although some service centers repair mobile phones at the client, troubleshooting can be delayed.<br><br><strong>Today we are going to show you how to use WhatsApp without a phone</strong> so that you can install and configure WhatsApp on a tablet or other device without a SIM card. Follow the manual to use this trick.<br><strong>Set up WhatsApp without using a phone number</strong><br>First, download the latest version of WhatsApp from the mobile app store. If you’re an old user, you can later restore WhatsApp chats to Google Drive. After the download is complete, install WhatsApp on your smartphone, tablet or PC, and then close it. Do not proceed to the next step.<br><br>Now you will need to enter a mobile phone number to which the application will send an SMS message with a verification code. On the Internet, there are several free <strong><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/pinc-or-virtual-reality-for-your-iphone.html">virtual number registration services</a></strong> for verification in various online services. We note right away that most of them, in our case, will not work. Firstly, some services use the same number for everyone, and secondly, WhatsApp itself checks the validity of the number you enter. It is difficult to say exactly which parameters are evaluated by the messenger algorithm, but out of the few we entered, it accepted only the one that was obtained using the method described below.</p>
<p>So, in order to successfully verify the mobile phone number, you need to install an application called<strong> "Virtual SIM"</strong>. This must be done because the program will provide you with a virtual mobile phone number to which WhatsApp will send a confirmation code. After registering with WhatsApp, you can delete it. As a bonus, after installing Virtual SIM, you will receive 0.50 euros into your account, which you can use to make calls to any landline phones around the world.</p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-disable-the-built-in-browser-in-the-facebook-app-for-android.html">How disable built-in Facebook Browser in Smartphone</a>. <br><br>Further, everything is very simple. Open the WhatsApp application and as a phone number for verification, enter the number received in Virtual SIM and click continue. Now wait a few seconds and you will receive a verification code in the Virtual SIM application. Next, copy this code into WhatsApp.<br><br>After that, you can log into WhatsApp without a phone number.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to Find a Perfect Developer for you Company</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-find-a-perfect-developer-for-you-company.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-find-a-perfect-developer-for-you-company.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-17T19:26:07+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="" />
                    An ideal candidate should have a deep knowledge of the required programming language. However, it would be more valuable if he or she knew other coding languages to become more&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>An ideal candidate should have a deep knowledge of the required <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/why-you-should-join-tefl-programs-in-spain.html">programming</a> language. However, it would be more valuable if he or she knew other coding languages to become more flexible and be able to work in future projects. It is also essential that developers have the ability to communicate effectively with all the members of the team and, in particular, with the customer to make sure that all the needs are understood at the beginning of each project thus saving development time and later changes. The software world is a fast paced, ever evolving environment and thus it is necessary to be able to meet very strict deadlines, be flexible and be creative. Furthermore, requirements often change during the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-important-tips-to-place-a-good-web-design-course.html">course of large projects</a>, thus having experience in lean programming is essential. While establishing which are the desired skills of candidates is a relatively simple task, finding and especially evaluating such candidates before hiring them is particularly complex. It is easy to imagine how time consuming it would be to carry out some interviews and then perform technical tests where candidates show their qualities. In particular, this could become complicated because candidates may not be willing to code unpaid during an interview and evaluating some soft skills like team work is can be complicated unless certain people are in the interview. This can be difficult when everybody is busy with his or her own work.</p>
<p>Therefore, traditional methods to recruit candidates such as adverts in websites might be inadequate because it difficult or impossible to determine whether a candidate has the expertise and talent. It would appear interesting to be able to evaluate these important skills. As a result, hackathons have become an attractive option.</p>
<p><strong>What is hackathon?</strong> Hackathons are an original and effective way to find candidates for open tech positions by engaging hidden talents with coding competitions. During online challenges professionals can show off their skills and get hired. This way, organisations can discover &amp; recruit new talents, assess programming skills, improve time-to-hire, and source innovations.</p>
<p>Hackathons offer a unique environment for both recruiters and job seekers. Why? Recruiters can prepare specific problems of interest to different companies. For instance a group of companies could be interested in SAP or maybe in C++ whereas companies looking for web developers may prefer problems based on PHP.</p>
<p>Check also: Hackathon Ideas (upcoming hackathon)</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1749" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/165/How-to-Find-a-Perfect-Developer-for-you-Company.jpg" alt="How to Find a Perfect Developer for you Company" width="1709" height="803"></p>
<p>Why would candidates attend to such an event? Hackathons, or coding competitions, are popular because of the rewards, which may or may not include a financial price. But usually, it is the prestige that attracts the most brilliant professionals, thus becoming a win-win situation for both recruiters and job-seekers.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Small and Medium Business Insurance</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/small-and-medium-business-insurance.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/small-and-medium-business-insurance.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-11T22:38:00+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/164/Screenshot_4-1.png" alt="" />
                    Hello, dear readers. In this article, we will tell you about business insurance. Today you will learn: Business insurance is a product through which you can save your capital and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/164/Screenshot_4-1.png" alt="" />
                <p>Hello, dear readers. In this article, we will tell you about business insurance.</p>
<p><strong>Today you will learn:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>For what it is necessary to insurance business;</li>
<li>Types of risks in business;</li>
<li>Which company provide risk-free business insurance services and how much does it cost?</li>
</ol>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn980">What is Business Insurance?</h2>
<p>Business insurance is a product through which you can save your capital and continue working without financial loss.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn991">Why insure your business?</h2>
<p>This question may arise in those who are just starting their own business, sometimes by trial and error.</p>
<p>If you have created the whole business of your life, have a good client base and create competition to other companies, then you should take care that it does not collapse in a single moment because of unforeseen circumstances.</p>
<p><strong>Of course</strong>, many young entrepreneurs are trying to save their own money and do not believe that there can be a fire, an accident, or that someone will fail or someone will "throw" on the money. But you will agree, it is pleasant to work and know that at any moment everything can be restored, at the expense of the received insurance payment.</p>
<p>It can be concluded that insurance for your business is an additional "safety cushion" for your business. The main thing is to evaluate the business and choose the right insurance product.</p>
<p><strong>Therefore,</strong> if you are just starting to develop, do not negatively react to proposals from insurance companies. It is better to carefully study the commercial proposals of several insurers and purchase a lucrative contract.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn992">Advantages of business insurance.</h2>
<p>Advantages of business insurance are obvious:</p>
<p><strong>Protection against financial losses and bankruptcy.</strong> In a market economy, opening a business is a risky business. The customer base will not be accumulated in one day. To reduce the losses that may arise as a result of commercial activities, it is worth buying insurance protection.</p>
<p><strong>Protection of real estate.</strong> The room in which you operate may be affected by a fire, explosion or natural disasters. The cost of restoration can be large. It is through insurance that you can repair the property.</p>
<p><strong>Staff insurance.</strong> The availability of experienced and qualified personnel is the key to the introduction of a successful business. The protected team feels calmer and loyal to the company's management.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn993">Entrepreneurial risks.</h2>
<p>Every business activity involves high risks. The best way to protect yourself against possible losses is to purchase a business insurance agreement.</p>
<p><strong>The main types of risks:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>External</strong>. This type of risk does not depend on the activities of the company. This includes inflation and changing demand in the market.</li>
<li><strong>Internal.</strong> These are risks that arise solely through the fault of the enterprise itself. Here it is possible to single out a strike or an incorrectly drawn up business plan for the development of one's own business.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>By the factor of occurrence,</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Political,</strong> connected and changing the political situation in the country;</li>
<li><strong>Economic</strong>, arising due to adverse changes in the economy.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Classification of risks in the area of occurrence:</strong></p>
<p>Production risk associated with non-fulfillment of obligations to produce goods or services;</p>
<ul>
<li>Commercial risk arising from the sale of goods and services;</li>
<li>Financial risk is related to non-fulfillment of financial obligations;</li>
<li>Insurance risk is associated with possible losses that will arise as a result of the occurrence of the insured event.</li>
<li>An innovative risk is associated with the emergence of new technologies and the emergence of a new, more sophisticated product on the market.</li>
</ul>
<p>For the correct choice of insurance protection it is worth taking into account:</p>
<ul>
<li>What risks can be at the enterprise?</li>
<li>The probability of occurrence of each risk;</li>
<li>Losses that you incur as a result of each risk.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The assessment of future damage is based on the following methods:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Analysis of all company activities;</li>
<li>Comparison of own forecasts and data obtained from the involved specialists;</li>
<li>The use of the experience of other enterprises that work in a similar industry.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn994">Types of business insurance.</h2>
<p>Even the most courageous entrepreneurs, who are not the first day in business, do not forget to "make themselves straws." Business insurance is an obligatory process that can not be neglected and postponed for later.</p>
<p>There are several types of risk insurance:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Property insurance.</strong> In this case, the products, equipment, and premises are subject to insurance;</li>
<li><strong>From the production break.</strong> For example, you have a fire in the company. You will not be able to quickly restore the workflow. It is necessary to spend time on repair work, purchase of new equipment. Do not forget about the wages of employees, which no one has canceled and all mandatory tax deductions. Insurance will be able to compensate for all the expenses that you incur in such a situation;</li>
<li><strong>Insurance of business liability to third parties</strong>. Under this agreement, all liabilities to partners will be insured. For example, also in the event of a fire, you will not be able to fulfill the obligations in full. The insurance company compensates all penalties, which will be exposed as a result of the occurrence of the insured event.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn995">Property insurance</h2>
<p>Let's say that you opened a business, rented an office or bought your own premises. In addition to the premises, you had to buy the necessary equipment and furniture. If it is a question of big business and production of goods, then the expensive equipment is needed. Here all the acquired property can suffer at any moment.</p>
<p>Under the contract, you can ensure:</p>
<ul>
<li>The building itself and the buildings and buildings attached to it;</li>
<li>Material values;</li>
<li>Money in the vault or safe;</li>
<li>Techniques: computers, telephones, fax machines, printers, scanners, etc .;</li>
<li>Interior items.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn996">Insurance against production interruption.</h2>
<p>Business can not work around the clock. There can be scheduled days for rest - these are weekends and holidays. But what to do with unplanned work days, which can appear due to force majeure circumstances?</p>
<p>As a result of downtime, you:</p>
<ul>
<li>Losses in the form of lost profits;</li>
<li>You will have to spend money on damages, and this is unplanned expenses;</li>
<li>Have to pay salaries to their employees, taxes, and rents.</li>
</ul>
<p>Compensate for all costs will help the insurance company.</p>
<p>Also, it is worth remembering about an additional useful insurance package:</p>
<ul>
<li>Voluntary insurance of employees ;</li>
<li>Civil liability to third parties;</li>
<li>Vehicle insurance company;</li>
<li>Insurance of goods during transportation.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn997">Liability Insurance.</h2>
<p>This is an excellent protection, if, due to unforeseen circumstances, you have caused harm to the customer and he has a complaint.</p>
<p>Let's say you decided to open a beauty salon. Your employee, when applying a mask to the client, incorrectly mixed the cosmetic substances and the client appeared redness and burns on the face. Agree, a very unpleasant situation.</p>
<p>If the injured customer makes a claim to the salon, you will have to pay compensation. But you will not be paid, but the insurance company, within the insured amount.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn998">Small Business Insurance.</h2>
<p>For a small business, any unforeseen situation can turn into a great tragedy. In most cases, there are no reserve funds for small businesses, and due to working capital, the damage cannot be compensated. In such a situation, insurance protection will help to minimize possible losses.</p>
<p>At the moment, small business insurance includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Business Liability Insurance;</li>
<li>Property insurance;</li>
<li>Possible losses in production.</li>
</ul>
<p>It is also worth knowing that if a novice businessman wants to take a loan from a bank to open a business, the bank will take care of the security of assets that will serve as collateral. In this case, the registration of a business insurance agreement will become a prerequisite.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvpqn999">Medium Business Insurance.</h2>
<p>Today, economic conditions cannot be called stable. This applies to the whole world. Every day you can hear about financial crises, which can affect the activities of large companies. But how to survive afloat representatives of medium-sized businesses? This business is in a special risk zone.</p>
<p>Experienced insurance consultants advise to acquire protection against force majeure, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fires;</li>
<li>Accidents, including utilities;</li>
<li>Change or illness of employees;</li>
<li>Official crimes;</li>
<li>Equipment failure.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cost of business insurance services.</strong></p>
<p>Insurance companies offer several business insurance programs. You can make a calculation even on the official website of the insurance company <a href="https://www.roseboroughinsurance.com/business-insurance-tulsa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.roseboroughinsurance.com/business-insurance-tulsa/</a>, or by calling the operator on a toll-free customer support phone.</p>
<p>The listed companies have a comprehensive business insurance program that guarantees full protection in the event of an insured event.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Types of Credit / Debit Cards - How to Get Prepaid VISA &amp; MasterCard Cards</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/types-of-credit-debit-cards-how-to-get-prepaid-visa-and-mastercard-cards.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/types-of-credit-debit-cards-how-to-get-prepaid-visa-and-mastercard-cards.html</id>

        <updated>2019-08-11T22:38:15+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/163/Screenshot_4.png" alt="" />
                     In this article, I am reviewing the TBF Finance https://tbffinance.com/visa-cards.php. TBF Finance Payment cards proved to be the safest way to keep your funds and use them all across&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/163/Screenshot_4.png" alt="" />
                <p> </p>
<p>In this article, I am reviewing the TBF Finance https://tbffinance.com/visa-cards.php. TBF Finance Payment cards proved to be the safest way to keep your funds and use them all across the real and electronic world. TBF Finance provides easy, safe and convenient opportunity to make purchases both off and online, travel worldwide, buy tickets, book hotel or rent a car on the internet.</p>
<p><strong>Visa</strong><br> <strong>Visa</strong> Inc. American multinational corporation for financial services. The head office is in San Francisco, California, USA. Visa is a global payment company that provides the ability to make money transfers around the world, most often with Visa's proprietary debit and credit cards. Visa Inc. was founded in 1976.</p>
<p><strong>Visa Inc.</strong> provides financial centers with Visa corporate identity products, which they use to offer debit, credit, prepaid and cash access programs to their customers. Visa does not ensure the issuance of cards, the provision of loans or the establishment of tariffs and commissions for customers. One of Visa's branded payment products is well-known cards.</p>
<p>The volume of processed operations and the number of customers is impressive with an incredibly increased volume. In 2010, Visa Inc. a global network (known as VisaNet) processed 67 billion transfers for a total of $ 5.2 trillion.</p>
<p>Visa operates in Central and South America, the Caribbean, North America, the Asia-Pacific region, Central and Eastern Europe, the Middle East and Africa, in more than 200 countries, people can use virtual currency instead of cash and checks. Since 1986 Visa Inc. was the worldwide sponsor of the Olympic Games and the only card that is accepted in all Olympic venues.</p>
<p>Read: Amazing Andalusia Tour Guide &amp;#038; Its Good Services for Booking Taxi Marbella in Andalucia Tours</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dhvprigi0">Visa offers 3 types of cards: credit, debit and prepaid.</h2>
<p><strong>Credit cards</strong><br> With Visa credit cards you can quickly, conveniently and safely make purchases, they give you the opportunity to pay bills, travel around the world and withdraw cash anywhere in the world. Cards are accepted in more than 200 countries.</p>
<p>In addition, the Visa card is widely used on the Internet. It meets all the necessary security requirements and enables its users to use a wide range of additional services.</p>
<p><strong>Visa</strong> card is accepted in millions of outlets, so for credit cards, you will find a wide application, including restaurants and entertainment, paying bills, online books, music, movies, etc.</p>
<p><strong>Debit cards</strong><br> A <strong>Visa debit card</strong> helps its owner to make purchases, pay bills and buy on the Internet simply, quickly and reliably, as with credit cards. A Visa debit card is ideal for those who first encounter a payment card and who do not have a banking history. You can apply</p>
<p>A debit card, which is attached to a debit account, allows the holder to track the completed transfers, usually indicated in the bank's monthly report, as well as allow for better control of expenses.</p>
<p><strong>Prepaid Cards</strong><br> Visa issuer banks have the opportunity to offer prepaid Visa cards with prepaid limits to their customers. This type does not imply the presence of a constantly updated bank account and is usually intended for small daily purchases. Prepaid cards can be virtual, with a magnetic strip and with a built-in chip. As for the Virtual Visa card: it is a virtual card, designed exclusively for use on the Internet.</p>
<p>The first virtual card was released in 1999, in Kuwait. The virtual Visa card has its own number and the effective date. It can not be used in a regular store. on it, there are no features of the usual card, magnetic stripe, the trademark of the payment system and the place for the signature. Thus, a Virtual Visa card is an excellent addition to an existing debit or credit card Visa.</p>
<p><strong>Mastercard</strong><br> <strong>MasterCard</strong> is an international financial services corporation. The central office is in New York, USA. <strong>MasterCard</strong> Inc. was founded in 1966, now the service of electronic money transfers operates all over the world. <strong>MasterCard</strong>, inherently known as Master Charge.</p>
<p>The company was created from several banks in California. <strong>MasterCard</strong>'s main business is to process payments between merchant banks and cards of issuing banks or credit communities of buyers that use proprietary "MasterCard" debit and credit cards to make purchases.</p>
<p><strong>MasterCard</strong> Worldwide has been a public company since 2006. Mastercard is the sponsor of most world sporting events, such as the UEFA Champions League, the Canadian Hockey League Memorial Cup and many others.</p>
<p>From the first days of the existence of credit cards to wireless payment functions these days, MasterCard Worldwide has stimulated the industry by directing this evolution. Being in the center of commerce, MasterCard makes it easier, smoother, faster and more secure, introducing understanding and innovation in the payment process.</p>
<p>In 2001,<strong> MasterCard</strong> introduced new changes in the structure, which showed a new hope for the company. In 2002 MasterCard Worldwide merged with Europay International, which allowed creating a single global corporate structure. After the merger, the company became a private joint-stock corporation.</p>
<p><strong>MasterCard</strong> also offers its customers debit, credit, and prepaid cards. They are divided into types, for example, standard, gold, platinum, worldwide credit MasterCards, gift cards or tourist cards.</p>
<p>MasterCard Worldwide continues to provide a unique mix of competence and the use of global resources used by the company in order to provide a quality product to users who choose MasterCard. MasterCard always brings innovation and a growing number of products/services.</p>
<p>Next: <a href="http://Why You Should Join TEFL Programs in Spain" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Why You Should Join TEFL Programs in Spain</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Get The Most Suitable Event Wifi Solutions From Trade Show Internet</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/get-the-most-suitable-event-wifi-solutions-from-trade-show-internet.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/get-the-most-suitable-event-wifi-solutions-from-trade-show-internet.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/162/NEW_TSI_LOGO.png" alt="" />
                    If you are hosting an exhibit, a fashion show or any automotive event, reliable and fast internet connectivity is required. For all events, this is a major requirement in order&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/162/NEW_TSI_LOGO.png" alt="" />
                <p>If you are hosting an exhibit, a fashion show or any automotive event, reliable and fast internet connectivity is required. For all events, this is a major requirement in order to enhance the attendee experience. If you are looking <a href="https://tradeshowinternet.com/services/event-WiFi" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for the most suitable event wifi solutions</a>, then Trade Show Internet is your best option. They provide internet solutions for both indoor and outdoor events. It does not matter the venue; they have customized solutions for their clients to ensure that they get flawless internet.</p>
<p>During New York art fair and the release of Warner Bros movie wonder woman, Trade Show Internet provided internet solutions. They also provided IT solutions during Footwear show this year as well as Uber summit event. These are some of their clients who rely on Trade Show Internet for event IT during their major events.</p>
<p>The most important thing to bear in mind when looking for internet service provider when hosting the event is the options they have. Check for service level guarantee as well as network design, bandwidth, and the on-site event IT management during the event. If you do so, then you will not be disappointed. Trade Show Internet ensures that you get the best wifi solutions suitable for the event.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>3 key Tips to Make Your Website User-friendly</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-key-tips-to-make-your-website-user-friendly.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-key-tips-to-make-your-website-user-friendly.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:56+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Firstly, meet your target audienceTo make something works well, you should know who you design it for. So, the first step in creating a user-friendly website is analyzing your target group. Ask yourself&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Firstly, meet your target audience</h2>
<p>To make something works well, you should know who you design it for. So, the first step in creating a user-friendly website is <strong>analyzing your target group</strong>. Ask yourself some questions referring to your readers, for example:</p>
<ul>
<li>Why do they visit your page and what do they expect to find there?</li>
<li>In which circumstances do they visit your page?</li>
<li>What is the problem that your website can solve?</li>
<li>Who are your users? What’s the way they use an Internet?</li>
<li>Are they people with any disabilities?</li>
</ul>
<p>A user-friendly design usually uses so-called Personas. They are 2-3 representatives of your target group and they can help you understand your users better. <strong>Describe your Personas as detailed as possible and then plan the page for the sake of their needs, lifestyles, and qualities</strong>. It will increase your chance of creating a highly user-friendly website.</p>
<h2>Secondly, take care of UX best practices</h2>
<p>The essence of so-called <em>User Experience</em> is to make the product as easy for users as possible. In case of web design, <em>Usability</em> means <strong>making your readers experience intuitive</strong>. It should be so seamless and problem-free for users that almost invisible. <strong>There are some best practices that will help you make your page intuitive</strong>. The list of basic tips includes, for example, what follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>Name the elements of your page’s menus accurately to their content.</li>
<li>Add to your page a navigation bar. It will help your users stay oriented about their location on a page. It will also enable them to come back to any previous step of their web journey.</li>
<li>Make sure your page is responsive and looks good at any devices: smartphones, tablets, desktops.</li>
<li>Take care of your page load time. Check if there is no surplus of the website’s code and then make sure your page loads as fast as possible.</li>
<li>Do UX audits for your page regularly. Check the possible users’ journey and make sure there are no so-calls dead ends, for example.</li>
<li>Make sure there is a home button on your page. It is good to place it as a link under your logo. It helps users come back to the home page in case they get lost.</li>
<li>Keep a weather eye on how your website looks like. Make sure about the font readability, the usage of colors, the quality of graphics.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Thirdly, follow the trends</h2>
<p>If you want to create a <a href="https://cut2code.com/3-key-tips-on-how-to-make-your-website-user-friendly/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">user-friendly website</a>, be up to date with UX trends. If more and more pages use, for example, face recognition or gesture-based interactions, after some time these trends can become standards. Of course, sometimes it is not rational to keep up with the Joneses blindly. But, <strong>some trends can be related to your industry and not respecting them may be a sign of the backwardness of your brand</strong>. So, keep your finger on the heartbeat.</p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://cut2code.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">How to cut PSD to HTML</a></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Amazing Andalusia Tour Guide &amp; Its Good Services for Booking Taxi Marbella in Andalucia Tours</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/amazing-andalusia-tour-guide-and-its-good-services-for-booking-taxi-marbella-in-andalucia-tours.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/amazing-andalusia-tour-guide-and-its-good-services-for-booking-taxi-marbella-in-andalucia-tours.html</id>

        <updated>2019-07-27T23:19:54+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="" />
                    Those who have never been to Andalusia, and only heard from friends about the beauty of this place in the south of Spain. The edge of sun and joy, magnificent&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="" />
                <p>Those who have never been to Andalusia, and only heard from friends about the beauty of this place in the south of Spain. The edge of sun and joy, magnificent nature and unusual man-made beauties will undoubtedly fascinate you and will not let go without a desire to visit it again.</p>
<h2>AMAZING ANDALUSIA - A PLACE WHERE YOU WANT TO COME BACK</h2>
<p>From the first moments of the stay, the travelers are surprised by the positiveness and friendliness of the local population. Growing up under the rays of the southern sun Andalusians, absorbed his energy and cheerfulness, and therefore generously share it with their numerous guests. And the guests come to Andalusia a lot because there are really many opportunities for a variety of recreation.</p>
<p>Nobody is indifferent to the magnificent cities of the province: Seville, Granada, Malaga ( Marbella is its city visit once in your life) and Ronda and others, managing to harmoniously combine the precious heritage of the past and the rhythms of modern life. It is these cities that make up the so-called Heart of Andalusia and best characterize its unusually passionate and quivering temperament.</p>
<p>Surprisingly beautiful against the backdrop of the hills and valleys are the white villages of Andalusia, attracting the attention of tourists to<a href="https://bookingtaximarbella.com/tours-booking-taxi-marbella/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> tour in Taxi of Andalucia</a> and admiring their unusual.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1712" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/160/Screenshot_3.png" alt="Andalucía Tours in taxi" width="1834" height="812" /></p>
<p>Traveling along this edge, be sure to check at least one of them - each has its own charm. If you are looking for a good service for booking taxi Marbella in Andalucia tours or Malaga airport to Marbella, here is<a href="https://bookingtaximarbella.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> a good service for booking taxi Marbella in Andalucia tours</a>.</p>
<p>The coast of Andalusia is ideal for beach holidays, and therefore its famous resorts from the Atlantic and from the Mediterranean Sea are never empty during the season. Small beaches in numerous coves near the cities are always filled with vacationers, so for a rest in peace, it is worthwhile to get out or rent yachts, and pleasure boats.<br />
The city beaches are clean and equipped with everything necessary, and also have reputable fun on the water. Do not be bored and lovers of outdoor activities, come with or without children: water parks and entertainment centers, zoos and aquariums, a safari park and numerous protected areas guarantee a full and out of boring holiday at any time of the year. From the first spring months to the end of the harvest season, numerous festivals take place in the provinces.</p>
<p>Andalusia is famous for its splendid weather - sunny days on its territory are rarely replaced by foul weather, and even during the winter months, it offers tourists many interesting activities. Before the New Year holidays in the cities of the province, there are numerous sales, so that rest at this time can be successfully combined with a successful shopping.</p>
<p>Unforgettable experiences await the visitors to the unique mountain resort of Sierra Nevada - from December to April its slopes accept everyone who wants to go, and from the highest peaks, one can see the sunny beaches of the Costa del Sol. The resort pays much attention to the beginners: in addition to numerous special trails and instructors, there are also good services for booking the taxi from Malaga airport to Costa del Sol.</p>
<p>The tourist industry in Andalusia is thriving, and numerous hotels on the coastal resorts are always ready to welcome guests. Depending on the composition of the group, age, and interests, you can choose different places: near the beaches or from the historical part, on the outskirts or in the city center.</p>
<p>There is also an exotic tour booking taxi Marbella, allowing to combine accommodation with travel - train-hotel Al Andalus, which is often called a palace on wheels. With comfort and convenience, the tour participants visit all the important cities of the provinces and inspect most of the sights, enjoying in between gorgeous restaurant dishes and a pleasant stay in the tea rooms.</p>
<p>Rest in Andalusia is sure to please all members of the family because interesting activities can be found here for everyone. The charm of the ancient East and the energy of the modern West wonderfully intertwined in this wonderful corner of the world, and the chic nature and the dazzling sun only underline his magical aura.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
