<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2020-07-01T08:48:29+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>6 proven ways to make money in TikTok</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/6-proven-ways-to-make-money-in-tiktok.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/6-proven-ways-to-make-money-in-tiktok.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-01T08:37:52+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/211/tiktok-5323006_640.jpg" alt="6 proven ways to make money in TikTok" />
                    Publishing videos in TikTok is pretty easy thanks to the built-in editor. To add special effects, you can use effects inside the editor, as well as special masks and filters.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/211/tiktok-5323006_640.jpg" alt="6 proven ways to make money in TikTok" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1ec32jnda0"><span >Publishing videos in TikTok is pretty easy thanks to the built-in editor. To add special effects, you can use effects inside the editor, as well as special masks and filters. In the video, you can legally add any track from the free library of the application, or upload your audio.</span></p>
<p><span >Popular TikToker are already actively monetizing their accounts. How to profit from your TikTok account in 2020? We will analyze the proven methods:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Native advertising</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >It’s acceptable to advertise other accounts, brands, products, and services. This is a well-known format that is already successfully sold on Instagram. Experienced bloggers recommend observing the main rule of native advertising: we focus on the quality of content, advertising should be no more than 30%.</span></p>
<p><span >Let's analyze one of the options for native advertising in TikTok. Suppose a music group has recorded a new track and wants to attract the attention of the audience to this event. Next, the group manager looks for bloggers with a suitable target audience and buys a placement from them (prices depending on the popularity of the tiktoker). The placement may be a video recording for the specified track.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Live broadcasts</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Some time ago, TikToker blew up the story of a professional player from China. Meng Lei streamed his game in the application, one of these broadcasts gathered 22 million viewers who sent donations to the player for 1 million yuan, which amounted to about 167 thousand dollars!</span></p>
<p><span >That is, another option for monetizing an account in TikTok is to receive donations (thanks in monetary terms, in the application it is called coins or tips, in an average of 100 coins it costs about $ 1) from the audience. Such broadcasts are available for tickers with many followers from 1000, TikTok will take 20% of donations. Amounts can be withdrawn to a bank card or online wallet, withdrawal is available from $ 10.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Influence marketing</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The large reach in TikTok surely attracts large and medium-sized advertisers, despite the inability to put a direct link to your project. In-app advertising inspires user confidence and strengthens the brand position. This type of monetization is available to bloggers from 10-20 thousand subscribers. Usually, influence-marketing in TikTok includes the following activities:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><em><span >creating viral videos</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >Challenges</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >publishing brand hashtags videos</span></em></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Affiliate Programs</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >A popular tikToker can become a member of the affiliate program and receive deductions from going to the page or selling the advertised product. The blogger is required to put the right link under the video and motivate the audience to follow it. These methods of promotion are actively used by traffic arbitrators.</span></p>
<p><span >Typically, such a scheme works as follows: an interesting video is posted in TikTok, but in an incomplete form, under the video, there is a link to another social network (YouTube or Instagram) and from there, there is a redirect to an affiliate link (either in the profile header or in the story). The application has proven itself in partnerships with offers for clothing, cosmetics, and products in general for a young audience, as well as for the games and entertainment industry.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Attracting customers to the business</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >TikTok works great as an additional advertising channel for attracting customers to online and offline businesses. The best performance so far in the niches voiced in the paragraph above. The specifics of the audience are affected, the products “for the youth audience” most likely “enter”.</span></p>
<p><span >In the application, you can get wide coverage with the help of a catchy viral video. However, there are limitations: you cannot configure an exact target by parameters, for example, by geolocation.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >TikTok manager</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The demand for promotion in TikTok has thrown the work of SMM-managers. The new social network requires new skills, mainly related to the preparation of video content. Most often, the tasks of a tiker manager include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><em><span >promotion strategy planning,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >scripting videos,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >terms of reference for photographers and videographers,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >account promotion</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >communication and engagement of the audience, activity planning,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >communication with brands and customers for advertising.</span></em></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><span >Conclusion:</span></strong><span > TikTok enters everyday life with huge turns and is gaining popularity. If you spend time recording videos, it’s just silly not to take advantage of monetization opportunities. It is important to remember some of the limitations that the new social network imposes:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >you need to prepare for the difficulties and not abandon the work with accounts in other popular social networks. Reason: TikTok does not yet allow direct links to anything other than its social networks;</span></li>
<li><span >age restrictions: earning in Tik-Tok is officially possible only from the age of 18 or with the consent of the parents.</span></li>
</ul>
<p> Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-make-money-online-using-publisuitescom.html">How to make moeny online using Publisuite</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Need a free VPN - TOP 3 best VPN services 2020</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/need-a-free-vpn-top-3-best-vpn-services-2020.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/need-a-free-vpn-top-3-best-vpn-services-2020.html</id>

        <updated>2020-06-20T19:19:36+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/210/Screenshot_4.png" alt="Need a free VPN - TOP 3 best VPN services 2020" />
                    Today it is impossible to live a day without going online But there are various threats in the form of tracking user activity on the Internet and this is depressing.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/210/Screenshot_4.png" alt="Need a free VPN - TOP 3 best VPN services 2020" />
                <p><strong><em><span >Today it is impossible to live a day without going online</span></em></strong></p>
<p><span >But there are various threats in the form of tracking user activity on the Internet and this is depressing. However, there are ways to protect yourself. </span><strong><span >VPN (Virtual Private Network) service</span></strong><span > is a great way to provide a secure online network connection. The VPN also allows you to protect your browsing history and access to content that is blocked or limited at the regional level.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1eb9043a90"><strong><em><span >In this article, we will consider the TOP-3 of the best VPN services in 2020! first, you need to understand what does a VPN does?. So let's go!</span></em></strong></h3>
<p><span >Each of your devices (computer, smartphone, tablet, etc.) has its unique IP address, which tells the services who you are, what you are doing and where you are. </span><strong><span >A VPN is located between your device and the Internet service provider (ISP).</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><span >When a user logs on to the network, the</span></strong><span > VPN "spoofs" the device’s IP address. Everything that you do on the network, first goes through a VPN, then to the router - as a result, your router (and everything that is outside of your device) thinks that you have a </span><strong><span >different identity.</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><span >A VPN is very useful</span></strong><span > when you plan to connect to the Internet through an insecure connection (a network that does not ask for your password), for example, in a cafe, because it stores all kinds of information about you </span><strong><span >(for example, the history of visited pages and any data you transmit) .</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><span >A VPN even has other features,</span></strong><span > such as access to content, which may be limited geographically, as it allows you to view the contents of web pages as if you are in another place (city, country, continent).</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eb9043a91"><span >How to choose the right VPN</span></h2>
<p><span >If you have chosen a free VPN, it’s simple enough to start working with it: just select a VPN service, register on the website of the developer company and download the client.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Here are a few features to consider when choosing a VPN.</span></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Many servers:</span></strong><span > the more servers the VPN service has, the higher the connection speed and, as a rule, you will have more options for connecting to the selected country. This means that you most likely will not have to deal with buffering problems.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Multi-device connectivity:</span></strong><span >  if you need to connect more than one device to VPN simultaneously, you need more power. </span><strong><span >The best VPNs</span></strong><span > allow you to connect up to 5 devices at the same time, if not more.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Ease of use:</span></strong><span >  for beginners in a VPN, it’s important to have a clean and well-defined interface, as well as easy access to customer support. For </span><strong><span >experienced users, an</span></strong><span > application that is customizable and allows you to work with additional functions, such as a network switch, data compression (for mobile devices) and automatic HTTPS redirection, will be convenient.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Great security and no registration. </span></strong><span > Good VPN services will not track, register or sell your personal information - for example, which websites you visited. They also guarantee that they protect you with strong encryption (256-bit AES) and regular security checks - the </span><strong><span >most important criterion when choosing a VPN in 2020!</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1eb9043a92"><strong><span >To make life easier for my readers, I picked up TOP-3 of the best free VPN services in 2020 . You can not worry, they are completely safe!</span></strong></h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eb907tlp8"><em>ExpressVPN</em> - the<em> best in my opinion</em></h2>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><span >ExpressVPN </span></em></strong><span >is my choice of the fastest and most powerful VPN service. It is great for getting through any blocked websites and protecting your computer.</span></p>
<p><span >In its arsenal, the service has more than 30,000 IP addresses, 160 server locations in 94 countries and more than 3,000 available servers. It is also backed by a strict privacy policy, </span><strong><span >available without registration</span></strong><span > , so you can continue </span><strong><span >to surf with peace of mind.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >Even more impressive is the fact that the service is available on a wide variety of platforms: </span><strong><span >Mac, Windows, Linux, Android and iOS.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >Want your smart TVs, routers and game consoles to be </span><strong><span >protected by VPN</span></strong><span >? In </span><strong><em><span >ExpressVPN</span></em></strong><span > have their </span><strong><span >firmware for them</span></strong><span > , as well as extensions for browsers. </span><strong><span >The Android app</span></strong><span > works even on a </span><strong><span >Chromebook</span></strong><span > .</span></p>
<p><strong><span >As for the enhanced version,</span></strong><span > ExpressVPN also offers split tunneling, a network lock switch, server speed tests, zero-knowledge DNS, and unlimited bandwidth.</span></p>
<p><span >ExpressVPN has tons of tutorials and manuals that you can learn, as well as 24-hour online chat support, so you can get started right away.</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eb907k1u7">Tunnelbear - Best Budget VPN</h2>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong><span >A</span></strong><span >n extremely user-friendly interface, this is a great option for those who are not familiar with VPNs. Its free access is limited to 500 MB per month, and if you need more, the cheapest subscription option starts at $ 4.95 per month, giving you unlimited secure access to up to 5 devices and priority customer service.</span></p>
<p><span >Even though the nice graphic design makes the service fun and affordable, </span><strong><span >Tunnelbear shines with</span></strong><span > its incredibly amazing privacy policy. He will never register or sell your activity history on the Internet, and will also conduct independent annual service audits </span><strong><span >- something you will not see in most other VPNs.</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Tunnelbear is</span></strong><span > a simpler and less powerful VPN service, but it is a great option for beginners and those who don’t care about the many settings and advanced features. It has only about 22 server seats and 1800 servers, so it is comfortable for working in a cafe, but probably not ideal for active users.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Tunnelbear is</span></strong><span > also available on Mac, Windows, iOS, and Android, and there are browser extensions for Chrome, Firefox, and Opera.</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eb9075su6"><strong>IPVanish - the best VPN for connecting multiple devices</strong></h2>
</li>
</ul>
<p><span >If you need to connect multiple devices to a VPN at the same time, </span><strong><span >IPVanish</span></strong><span > ($ 10 / month) is the perfect choice for your purpose. With it, you can connect up to </span><strong><span >10 devices</span></strong><span > at the same time without problems.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >IPVanish</span></strong><span > has excellent statistics, offering over 1300 anonymous servers in more than 75 locations and 40,000 shared IP addresses. It also has a clear zero-log privacy policy and keeps your data safe with </span><strong><span >256-bit AES encryption.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >This VPN service has convenient applications for all platforms and devices: </span><strong><span >Windows, macOS, Android, iOS, Linux, Chrome OS, Fire TV and WiFi routers.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >All applications are feature rich and feature options such as </span><strong><span >automatic IP address switching</span></strong><span > . One of the main </span><strong><span >disadvantages of</span></strong><span > IPVanish is that its interface is not as accessible and intuitive as others - therefore, </span><strong><span >it may not be the best choice for novice users.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >Nevertheless, thanks to round-the-clock customer support, users can quickly get answers to questions when they need it most.</span></p>
<p>Read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-unblock-blocked-sites-in-android-with-3-best-apps.html">How to unblock blocked sites in Android </a></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1eb9043a93"><span >Final Words:</span></h3>
<p><span >We reviewed the </span><strong><span >TOP-3 of the best free VPN services in 2020,</span></strong><span > each of which has its advantages and disadvantages, which can be solved, for the most part, by purchasing advanced access or a premium account.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >You can download and use any of the above VPN services for free.</span></strong></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>11 best open-source software for your Pc in 2020</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/11-best-open-source-software-for-your-pc-in-2020.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/11-best-open-source-software-for-your-pc-in-2020.html</id>

        <updated>2020-06-12T09:02:29+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/209/11-best-open-source-software-for-your-Pc-in-2020.png" alt="11 best open-source software for your Pc in 2020" />
                    In this post, we will know some best open-source software for our computer. Why use open source software? Firstly, they are free. Secondly, they are safe, as their development is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/209/11-best-open-source-software-for-your-Pc-in-2020.png" alt="11 best open-source software for your Pc in 2020" />
                <p><span >In this post, we will know some best open-source software for our computer. Why use open source software? Firstly, they are free. Secondly, they are safe, as their development is supported and verified by a large community around the world. In my opinion, here are 11 of the best programs, </span></p>
<p><span >Please note that a lot of open sources programs have been developed for various tasks. It is impossible to cover everything. However, this is what I consider the best for the end-user. </span><strong><span >However, be sure to write to me in the comments which programs you prefer.</span></strong></p>
<p><strong>1. Brave Browser</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux, iOS, Android</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Brave Browser</span></strong><span > is an open-source browser that puts user privacy at the forefront and blocks ads and trackers by default.</span></p>
<p><span >In terms of security, Brave browser supports end-to-end data encryption, built-in VPN, and decentralized applications, allows you to work with magnet links.</span></p>
<p><span >Also, it pays users for viewing advertisements with native Basic Attention Tokens. To do this, a crypto wallet that supports BAT is integrated into the browser.</span></p>
<p><span >The browser is very fast and easy to use, as it is based on the open-source Chromium browser. It is still lagging behind the big players when it comes to supporting extensions, but given its rapid development, we can expect that things will change very soon.</span></p>
<p><strong>2. LibreOffice</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><span >This office suite has a traditional and familiar interface, as well as the fact that it includes the working equivalents of Microsoft Word, Excel, Publisher, Powerpoint, and Access. This is perhaps the most useful free open-source package you will find.</span></p>
<p><span >LibreOffice has excellent compatibility with many formats - from Microsoft proprietary formats to less well-known ones - and is constantly evolving. </span><span >The next step we will wait for is some kind of cloud storage!</span></p>
<p><strong>3. Krita</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><span >Krita is a great digital graphics editing tool, which is great for those who are just trying their hand at design, and for professionals. </span><span >Krita has a layering system, and the program itself also loads your system significantly.</span></p>
<p><strong>4. Notepad ++</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows</span></p>
<p><span >Experienced users do not need to talk about Notepad ++. This is a great tool for programmers and experienced users with support for programming languages ​​and syntax highlighting.</span></p>
<p><span >Notepad ++ also offers an excellent tab system that allows you to work with multiple files simultaneously. The program remembers open tabs, so you can continue to work from the place where you left off, even after restarting the computer.</span></p>
<p><strong>5. TestDisk &amp; PhotoRec</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><span >TestDisk was released over twenty years ago but is still one of the best tools for recovering entire sections of lost or deleted data in various formats. PhotoRec does the same job but specializes in recovering photos from digital media.</span></p>
<p><strong>6. stud.io</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac</span></p>
<p><span >stud.io lets you intuitively create digital LEGO models.</span></p>
<p><strong>7. GIMP</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><span >GIMP has firmly established itself as the most viable free alternative to Adobe Photoshop.</span></p>
<p><strong>8. Dia</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms: </span></strong><span > Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><span >Dia is one of the best free alternatives to Microsoft Visio. Charting software comes with a variety of native forms, allowing you to create all kinds of charts, from flowcharts to network architectures.</span></p>
<p><strong>9. Search Everything</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows</span></p>
<p><span >This is an incredibly effective search tool that can find absolutely anything on your computer in seconds.</span></p>
<p><strong>10. BleachBit</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux</span></p>
<p><strong><span >BleachBit</span></strong><span > is a free and easy-to-use program that is designed to thoroughly clean the operating system of various digital junk.</span></p>
<p><strong>11. Retroarch</strong></p>
<p><strong><span >Platforms:</span></strong><span >  Windows, Mac, Linux, Android</span></p>
<p><span >Retroarch is an open-source video game emulator. It contains many emulators for all the most popular consoles in the form of "cores", which are adapted for downloading, updating, and working within the software.</span></p>
<p>What is next: <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null">Facebook has released CatchUp a new application for audio calls</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Facebook has released CatchUp a new application for Audio calls and How to use CatchUp Application</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/facebook-has-released-catchup-a-new-application-for-audio-calls-and-how-to-use-catchup-application.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/facebook-has-released-catchup-a-new-application-for-audio-calls-and-how-to-use-catchup-application.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-31T21:20:51+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/208/CatchUp-Application.png" alt="Facebook has released CatchUp a new application for Audio calls and How to use CatchUp Application" />
                    FaceBook's new audio calling App CatchUp offers simple calls, like in the days of regular phones. At the same time, users themselves indicate their willingness to talk Facebook’s NPE Team&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/208/CatchUp-Application.png" alt="Facebook has released CatchUp a new application for Audio calls and How to use CatchUp Application" />
                FaceBook's new audio calling App CatchUp offers simple calls, like in the days of regular phones. At the same time, users themselves indicate their willingness to talk<br><br>Facebook’s NPE Team Experimenters New Voice Calling App CatchUp Its feature is that it shows users when subscribers are ready to communicate.<br><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/facebook-wants-you-to-share-more-music-on-your-network-with-music-stories.html">Facebook</a> knows the importance of communication, especially now that the world is facing a difficult situation. People are forced to stay at home, therefore, by any means maintain contact with each other. In this regard, new calling application CatchUp will be an excellent assistant, since the program offers simple calls - such as during the time of conventional push-button phones. According to studies, one of the main reasons people don’t call friends, relatives, and friends more often is that they don’t know when they are ready to talk to them. Often people worry that they can call at an uncomfortable time. but CatchUp solves this problem.
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e9lo9c7v0">Important features of CatchUp Application.</h2>
In the CatchUp application, users can indicate that they are ready for a conversation by setting the appropriate status. It will be visible to all other participants. In addition to individual calls, CatchUp also has group calls, which are easy to join. The program is not related to the Facebook application, so users do not need to have a social network account. Linking is carried out by phone number, as in any other messenger, so you can even chat with those who do not have a Facebook account.<br>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e9lo9p321">How to use CatchUp Application.</h2>
<p>CatchUp is currently being tested in the US on iOS and Android. Since this is an experimental product, I hope Facebook will release and updates all over the world as soon as possible.</p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/facebook-will-create-operating-system-as-like-android.html">Facebook will create Operating System as like Android </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to set up Google Assistant on Android with Action Block</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-set-up-google-assistant-on-android-with-action-block.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-set-up-google-assistant-on-android-with-action-block.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-23T19:04:15+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/207/voice-search-1792301_640.png" alt="How to set up Google Assistant on Android with Action Block" />
                    I love Google Assistant and use it regularly. Unlike Siri on iOS, the voice assistant of the Google Assistant is more deeply integrated with Android and allows you to interact&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/207/voice-search-1792301_640.png" alt="How to set up Google Assistant on Android with Action Block" />
                <p><span >I love Google Assistant and use it regularly. Unlike Siri on iOS, the voice assistant of the Google Assistant is more deeply integrated with Android and allows you to interact with the operating system with great convenience. You can ask him to translate the text, find the right product on the Internet from a photograph, read out the contents of the website, return the application that was mistakenly bought on Google Play, not to mention controlling music playback, setting alarms, and more. However, because it was possible to manage the Google Assistant only by voice or through correspondence, many avoided using it, hesitating to contact their phone. It’s good that Google understood this.</span></p>
<p><span >Google has launched the Action Blocks app for Android. It allows you to create a kind of shortcut for the Google Assistant quick commands that you can place on your desktop and activate the necessary actions without speaking to the assistant by voice. That is Action Blocks is an analog of Siri Shortcuts on iOS, and its key difference from the proprietary Apple application is a less extensive set of functions, although Google Assistant itself will be more capable than Siri. However, the purpose of Action Blocks is a bit different.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e90sme1a0"><span >How Google Assistant with Action block Quick Commands Work</span></h2>
<p><span >The goal of Action Blocks is not to expand the capabilities of the device, like Siri Shortcuts, which adds functionality to the device but to simplify the interaction with it. Suppose, earlier, to set the alarm, you should first call the assistant, then say the appropriate command, set the time, check whether he understood you correctly, and only then confirm the action. With Action Blocks, you can make Google Assistant remember the action you need, save it, and you just click on the shortcut on the desktop to activate it.</span></p>
<p>Read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-useful-google-chrome-browser-features-you-need-to-know.html">5 useful Google Chrome browser feature </a></p>
<p><span >While the Action Blocks application is available only in English, which, however, will not prevent you from downloading it. At the time of publication, the development is already available in the Russian segment of the Google Play catalog and is distributed free of charge. Well, to make it easier for you to understand the features of the program and configure everything the way you want, although its interface is as simple and logical as possible, I offer you this short instruction.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e90sme1b1"><span >How to create a quick command for Google Assistant using Action Block Application</span></h2>
<ul>
<li><span >Download Action Block on your smartphone and activate it;</span></li>
<li><span >Click Create Action Block to create a shortcut with the command;</span></li>
<li><span >Select a command from the proposed ones or click Create custom action to create your own;</span></li>
<li><span >Click on the microphone icon and say a command with your voice or write it on the keyboard;</span></li>
<li><span >Click Test action to make sure that Google Assistant correctly recognized the command;</span></li>
<li><span >Select an icon for a shortcut with a quick command and name it;</span></li>
<li><span >Save the quick command and place it on your desktop.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >In my opinion, Action Blocks could be a decisive factor in favor of promoting Google Assistant. Not only that, thanks to the shortcuts with quick commands, the assistant will be able to use those who were embarrassed to use their smartphone's voice, but they will also help facilitate the use of older people. Practice shows that most users of advanced age interact with their smartphones only within a certain functional circle. However, with shortcuts, they can do much more without having to remember ways to activate certain features.</span></p>
<p> Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/google-and-facebook-kings-of-internet.html">Google and Facebook King of Internet </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Factors to consider before choosing a web hosting service provider</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/factors-to-consider-before-choosing-a-web-hosting-service-provider.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/factors-to-consider-before-choosing-a-web-hosting-service-provider.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-16T22:07:18+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/206/cloud-3406627_640.jpg" alt="Factors to consider before choosing a web hosting service provider" />
                    We go to dozens of sites every day, this is called "web surfing." In this article, let's understand how sites work, and what does web hosting have to do with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/206/cloud-3406627_640.jpg" alt="Factors to consider before choosing a web hosting service provider" />
                <p><span >We go to dozens of sites every day, this is called "web surfing." In this article, let's understand how sites work, and what does web hosting have to do with it.</span></p>
<p><span >When you need to go to any site, we open a browser and write the name of the site, or rather a <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/earning-money-from-domain-parking-basic-ideas.html">domain name</a>. It consists of the name and designation of the domain zone, for example, the domain "thetrickspeak.com" refers to the zone "global". Next, the browser needs to convert the alphabetic name to the digital address of the site - IP (Internet Protocol). Text names were invented for the convenience of using the Internet, but in reality, only digital IP addresses are “under the hood”.</span></p>
<p><span >For mapping domains with IPs, a global database of Domain Name System (DNS) names is used.</span></p>
<p><span >When the IP is found, the browser accesses this address and starts <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-free-ways-to-download-youtube-videos.html">downloading</a> the site files. These files must be stored somewhere, this place is called web hosting. That is, hosting is a place on the Internet, the server where the site “lives”. Web hosting is provided by hosting providers. The stability of work and the speed of loading the site directly depend on the quality of the hosting. Hosting service is paid, and prices vary depending on requirements, from $ 1 per month. There are thousands of providers now, so it’s better to understand factors before buying any hosting for your website.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e8f6nnv40"><span >Hosting Features</span></h2>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/web-hosting-solution-for-small-business.html">Hosting</a> not only contains site files, but it is also a complex system that includes several basic modules:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Name Server (DNS).</span></li>
<li><span >File storage.</span></li>
<li><span >Programming language handlers.</span></li>
<li><span >Database servers.</span></li>
<li><span >Backup system.</span></li>
<li><span >HTTP server.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The name server stores a database of domains and IP addresses. These databases are synchronized with each other and, theoretically, the same database on all hosting sites. Your ISP has the same database.</span></p>
<p><span >The file server provides disk space. There are several basic file types used for the site:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >HTML is the source code of the page that is loaded into the browser.</span></li>
<li><span >PHP - code in the programming language PHP.</span></li>
<li><span >CSS - styles for visualizing content.</span></li>
<li><span >JS - code in the Javascript programming language.</span></li>
<li><span >JPG, PNG, GIF, WEBP - pictures, photos.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >You can, of course, store any files, but the described types are used on most pages on the Internet.</span></p>
<p><span >On the Internet, some sites were static. This means that the hosting kept ready-made files that the browser simply downloaded and rendered the page. Now the sites are dynamic, i.e. the finished HTML file does not lie on the server, but it needs to be generated. This happened because there were content management systems (CMS), for example, WordPress.</span></p>
<p><span >CMS uses programming languages ​​and databases. Different information is stored across dozens of tables in the database. With the help of a code, information is collected according to a given algorithm and a page is formed.</span></p>
<p><span >Thus, you can generate millions of pages, and you do not need to store HTML files for each. But most importantly, it is easy to change something immediately on all pages of the site. Web hosting can interpret code in programming languages. The most popular are PHP, Perl, Python, ASP.NET, node.js. When choosing a hosting, pay attention above things</span></p>
<p><span >The HTTP server accepts the connection from the browser and gives the files. If the page is static, then the HTTP server simply downloads the HTML file, and if it is dynamic, it will first transfer control to the interpreter and then take the HTML code from it. Hosting ability to process a large number of connections, i.e. visitors, depends on the HTTP server.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e8f6nnv51"><span >Types of Hosting</span></h2>
<p><span >The described model is called "Shared hosting", also called virtual or private. With shared hosting, a site is allocated disk space and a processor time limit for processing commands. As a rule, this limit is small, since hundreds of sites use one server, hence the name - “common”. This is the most inexpensive and common type of hosting.</span></p>
<p><span >Shared hosting has disadvantages:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Limited computing resources.</span></li>
<li><span >You can not change the software environment.</span></li>
<li><span >Server settings are very limited.</span></li>
<li><span >The security of all sites is interconnected.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >But there are advantages:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Low cost.</span></li>
<li><span >Everything works out of the box.</span></li>
<li><span >Server administration is entirely in the hands of technical support.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Serious web owner does not use shared hosting, although large content resources may remain here. In fact, shared hosting can withstand impressive traffic if you turn a dynamic site into a static one.</span></p>
<p><span >Caching plugins are used for this. It works simply: the first time you access the page, it, as expected, is generated by the engine from scratch. Then, the finished page is saved to an HTML file on disk, and the next time the hosting gives a static file.</span></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/web-hosting-solution-for-small-business.html">Shared hosting</a> does not guarantee a processor resource, and it is not measured at all. Some hosters have come up with an internal processor unit, such as 50 CPUs. The number does not allow you to somehow evaluate the load capacity of the server, but in this way, you can compare tariffs among themselves. This gives an understanding that a more expensive tariff is not only distinguished by available disk space, but also by an increased limit on the processor.</span></p>
<p><span >For guaranteed power they use virtual private servers - VPS / VDS. In this case, you get not just disk space for the site, but your own server. This means that you have your own operating system. On the OS, you can put any modules, programming languages, HTTP-servers, and databases. </span></p>
<p><span >There can be some analogy between VPS and Shared: instead of a piece of disk space, you get a piece of the server. One real server is divided into dozens of virtual servers. Guaranteed resources are determined by the VPS parameters:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >The processor clock speed in MHz, for example, 2900 MHz.</span></li>
<li><span >The number of processor cores: from 1 to 32 and above.</span></li>
<li><span >The amount of RAM.</span></li>
<li><span >Disk space</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >VPS hosting launches online stores and services. If you need a complete server, then this is called a dedicated server rental. A physical server passes to your control, on which you can install your OS.</span></p>
<p><span >Unlike Shared, a dedicated server needs to be independently administered, to monitor health and safety. If at night the server freezes and the site stops working, then only you are responsible for this. In the case of Shared hosting, technical support will see that the server crashed and restore its operation.</span></p>
<p><span >Hosting is used not only for websites, but it is also a remote server to run applications. Sites run on Linux, programs run on Microsoft Windows. Conveniently, the servers work 24 hours a day, do not make noise, and do not take up space in the room. On a remote server, you can run a program that should work without interruption, and not require large processing power. For example, Windows hosting is used for the work of exchange robots.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e8f6nnv52"><span >Conclusions</span></h2>
<p><span >You need to carefully approach the choice of hosting provider services to host the site. After reviewing the available information, you can choose what the user needs in a particular situation: shared hosting or a VPS / VDS server. Both types of hosting have their pros and cons, choose what suits you best.</span></p>
<p> Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/review-on-the-best-web-hosting-to-best-suit-your-budget.html">Review on the best web hosting to best suit to your budget </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to transfer files from phone to computer without a USB cable</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-transfer-files-from-phone-to-computer-without-a-usb-cable.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-transfer-files-from-phone-to-computer-without-a-usb-cable.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-11T00:49:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/205/cloud-4828080_640.jpg" alt="How to transfer files from phone to computer without a USB cable" />
                    Often there are situations when you need to transfer information from a phone to a computer - be it text, video, or file. You can use the USB-wire, which will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/205/cloud-4828080_640.jpg" alt="How to transfer files from phone to computer without a USB cable" />
                <p><span >Often there are situations when you need to transfer information from a phone to a computer - be it text, video, or file. You can use the USB-wire, which will quickly transmit information. But what to do when there is no wire? I talk about 5 alternative methods of transfer files from phone to computer without a USB cable.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e801u9md0"><span >Email</span></h2>
<p><span >This is a very easy way to transfer files. It is enough to have even one email address to transfer files. But, there are some restrictions - 10 GB. Files larger than 25 MB will be uploaded to the cloud.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e801u9me1"><span >Instant messengers</span></h2>
<p><span >As a rule, instant messengers have a web version or a desktop client. In the case of WhatsApp, you can use</span><strong><span > the web version</span></strong><span >. I recommend downloading for Telegram </span><strong><span >desktop version</span></strong><span >. But still, there are size restrictions. For WhatsApp, this is 16 MB for photos and 100 MB for files. Telegram has more loyal limits - 1.5 GB for all file types.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e801u9mf2"><span >Cloud</span></h2>
<p><span >There are a large number of cloud services. Almost all of them have a mobile application, so it’s convenient to upload files there and download them from your smartphone. Limits for the most popular cloud services:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Google Cloud - from 50 Mb to 5 Tb</span></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e801u9mf3"><span >FTP Transfer</span></h2>
<p><span >This method is very interesting. Unlike the method above, it does not have any limits, but you need to at least have a minimum understanding of phones and computers. The plus is also that you do not need to use traffic since you do not need to publish and then download the file.</span></p>
<p><span >First, you need to download </span><strong><span >ES File Explorer</span></strong><span > and connect to the same Wi-Fi network. After that, in the explorer in the side menu, select the network -&gt; View on PC. There will be a line similar to ftp://192.168.1.6:3721/. Enter it on the computer in the search menu. And here they are, all the files in front of you:</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e801u9mf4"><strong><span >Shareit</span></strong></h2>
<p><span >A very simple method. You need to install the ShareIt program on the phone and computer. After that, send the file on the phone and accept it on the computer. Using the internet is optional.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-reset-the-bios-why-it-is-needed.html">How to reset the BIOS - Why it is needed</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to reset the BIOS - why it is needed</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-reset-the-bios-why-it-is-needed.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-reset-the-bios-why-it-is-needed.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-05T22:08:32+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/204/bios-154046_640.png" alt="How to reset the BIOS - why it is needed" />
                    Basic settings regarding the operation of equipment and accessories are stored in the BIOS. You can get to this menu when you boot your computer or laptop. Usually, you need&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/204/bios-154046_640.png" alt="How to reset the BIOS - why it is needed" />
                <p><span >Basic settings regarding the operation of equipment and accessories are stored in the BIOS. You can get to this menu when you boot your <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/computer-tips-and-tricks/">computer or laptop</a>. Usually, you need to hold the Del key while turning on the PC. Notebooks, as well as other brand assemblies, may have a different key. For example, there are options with F1, F2, F10. In any case, the key can be indicated on the loading screen, as well as in the instructions. In addition, it is worth looking for information on the official website of the manufacturer.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e7is5at20"><span >Why reset</span></h2>
<p><span >Resetting is required if you did something wrong and the computer does not start or is unstable. Often this happens when components are improperly dispersed. For example, you can try resetting the BIOS if the computer does not boot after changing any settings. And even when the system starts normally, errors and crashes to the blue screen can occur under load.</span></p>
<p><span >Moreover, by resetting the BIOS, you can remove the previously set password if you forget it. This refers to the password set specifically in the BIOS, and not in Windows.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e7is5at31"><span >What happens if you reset the BIOS</span></h2>
<p><span >Simply put, when you reset the BIOS, nothing bad will happen. However, you need to understand that the settings will return to the factory state, which may affect the operation of the entire system. For example, you will lose the overclocking of components. This includes at least the frequency of the processor and RAM.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e7is5at42"><span >How to reset BIOS</span></h2>
<p><span >There are many ways to reset the BIOS, the easiest of which is software. This is done from the settings and therefore the computer should turn on. Also, this method will not work if there is a password and you do not remember it. Depending on the BIOS version, the name of the item in the settings may differ. Therefore, you should at least be a little familiar with how this works. You need to search for items with names: Load Optimized Defaults, Load Setup Defaults.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e7is5at43"><span >Battery</span></h2>
<p><span >In addition, you can reset the settings in a physical way. First of all, and it is much simpler, you should remove the battery power memory to store settings. This same battery allows the computer to display the correct time. </span></p>
<p><span >It is located on the motherboard both in a stationary computer and on a laptop. In the latter case, you have to disassemble the laptop, which may void your warranty. The same applies to branded desktops, if the warranty seal is on the case, then you can not open it.</span></p>
<p><span >Before removing the battery, disconnect the system unit, remove the laptop battery. Remove the battery and wait a few minutes before returning it to its place. Please note that the battery may be non-removable.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e7is5at44"><span >Jumper to reset</span></h2>
<p><span >Another way is connected with a special jumper located on the motherboard. Before performing the operation, be sure to turn off the power supply, using the switch on its case. In addition, the battery is also worth removing.</span></p>
<p><span >Typically, a jumper is located next to the battery. There is no standard name for it. Designations can be: CLRTC, Clear CMOS, Reset CMOS, as well as various combinations and abbreviations of these words. Physically, the jumper looks like two or three-pin contacts. In the first case, they just need to be closed, for example, with a screwdriver. However, it is better to do this with the so-called jumper. It can be taken from another place on the motherboard, and put back after use. In the second case, the jumper is already present and connects two of the three contacts. It needs to be rearranged to the second position.</span></p>
<p><span >Keep the contacts closed for 10-15 seconds and then put everything back. If this option does not work, then with the contacts closed, hold down the power button on the case and hold it for the same 10-15 seconds. After that, you may need to leave the board in this state for 15 minutes.</span></p>
<p><span >Also on the motherboard, there may be a separate button to reset the settings. If it is present, then fiddling with jumpers is no longer necessary. It will be enough to hold it for 5-10 seconds with the power off.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/top-seven-tips-for-buying-a-gaming-computer.html">Top seven tips for vuying a gaming computer</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>10 free services for efficient work from home</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-free-services-for-efficient-work-from-home.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-free-services-for-efficient-work-from-home.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-01T04:37:58+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="8 free services for efficient work from home" />
                    Work from home by someone has long been perceived as a dream. But everyone was sent to a remote place and it turned out that fulfilling duties while sitting in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="8 free services for efficient work from home" />
                <p><span >Work from home by someone has long been perceived as a dream. But everyone was sent to a remote place and it turned out that fulfilling duties while sitting in a favorite chair is not so simple. <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/frontpage/1">The Tricks Peak</a> has put together applications that will make your Home office life easier.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76kverj0"><span >1. Trello </span></h2>
<p><strong> Purpose: task manager </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://trello.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/trello/id461504587" rel="nofollow">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.trello" rel="nofollow">Android </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Trello-Purpose-task-manager.jpg" alt="" width="1438" height="530"></p>
<p><span >Trello is an application for project management. It allows you to organize teamwork - it is easier for employees to report to the head of your work, and the main thing is easier to monitor what tasks workers performed. </span></p>
<p><span >The head creates the columns, employee cards. Depending on the state of the task, the card moves from one column to another. </span></p>
<p><span >Conventionally, Trello has three columns: ideas, in progress, and delivered. The employee proposed a new logo for the client company, which means he creates the corresponding card in the “ideas” column. The manager accepts it and transfers the card to the “in progress” column. At the end of the day, the employee passes the logo. The manager has no complaints, so the card is transferred to the column “delivered”. </span></p>
<p><span >It would seem that everything is simple in Trello. But the company has more than one employee, and everyone can’t keep track of it. And in Trello, the leader can see the team’s work and which projects are ready and which ones to expect in the near future. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l00ne1"><span >2. Asana </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: task manager </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://asana.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/asana-organize-tasks-work/id489969512" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.asana.app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android  </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Asana-Purpose-task-manager.jpg" alt="" width="1675" height="520"></p>
<p><span >Alternative to Trello. Asana is a more complex but more versatile task manager. First of all, here you can choose the type of project - board, list, timeline, calendar. </span></p>
<p><span >Further, the essence is the same - you add sections (the same columns) and tasks (the same cards). For example, these are the same “ideas”, “in progress” and “delivered”. The proposed task is added to the "ideas". If the manager accepts it, the task moves to the "in progress" section. At the end of the day, the employee performs the task. The manager has no complaints, and the card is transferred to the "delivered" section.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0aif2"><span >3. Ticktick</span></h2>
<p><strong>Pupose: time control </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://ticktick.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/tick-tick/id626144601" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ticktick.task" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android  </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="" width="1710" height="635"></p>
<p><span >This service allows you to monitor completed tasks and monitor the implementation of the daily plan. </span></p>
<p><span >The principle of operation is as follows. You create tasks, they, in turn, are divided into lists. If in one list all the tasks are completed, then you achieve the goal. It turns out a kind of game. </span></p>
<p><span >Conditionally, you have created three lists: the main project, secondary tasks, the second job. In the main project, you have three tasks. Once you complete them, the goal is considered complete.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0ije3"><span >4. Zoom </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose:</strong><span ><strong> video conferencing </strong> </span></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://zoom.us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/id546505307" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=us.zoom.videomeetings" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Zoom.jpg" alt="" width="1661" height="510"></p>
<p><span >Optimal service for video chats. Skype is a thing of the past, and FaceTime is only available on Apple devices. Zoom allows you to create a conference for up to 100 participants. In it, one person is endowed with the rights of the organizer, he has the opportunity to invite and remove interlocutors. </span></p>
<p><span >However, the free version is not without limitations. In it, you can conduct a conference for up to 40 minutes. The restriction is removed in the paid version. In addition, in it, you can vest the rights of administrators of other conference participants. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0qa44"><span >5. Slack </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: communication </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://slack.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/slack/id618783545" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Slack" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >Corporate messenger. Replaces a number of services for communication and file transfer - Skype, mail, other instant messengers, cloud storage. </span></p>
<p><span >Slack feature - synchronization with other services like Google Drive, Google Docs, Twitter, Trello, Hangouts, Dropbox, GitHub, and others. The messenger is free, but there are also paid tariffs, they increase the number of saved messages and the amount of cloud storage. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l16rl5"><span >6. Toggl</span></h2>
<p><strong>Appointment: time control </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://toggl.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/toggl-time-tracker-for-work/id1291898086" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.toggl.giskard" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span >Android</span></a></p>
<p><span >Application for time management. You will see how many hours you spend on various tasks. Toggl can look different: as a web version, a utility for a computer, or a mobile application for iOS and Android. </span></p>
<p><span >Working with the application is simple: specify the title of the task, write the name of the project to which this task belongs, and start the timer. Once done, stop the timer. And if you are distracted, also click “stop” so that the tracker fixes it. Thus, you will get a list of tasks that you perform in a day. The main thing is not to forget to turn the tracker on or off. To do this, turn on reminders: then the application will remind you of itself, asking if you forgot to turn the tracker on or off. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l1iie6"><span >7. Teamweek </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: control of the time of all team </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/teamweek/id1242738862" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.teamweek.android.app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android</a></span><span > </span></p>
<p><span >Teamweek allows the team to maintain a common calendar to visually plan the time of each employee and see who is busy and who is free at a particular moment.</span></p>
<p><span >Tasks can be created and scheduled on the timeline. The team can be divided into groups, for each set its own time frame. Users can view tasks, filter them by project, view the team calendar in the week or month format, and see their tasks on it.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l27437"><span >8. Onedrive </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: Cloud Storage  </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://onedrive.live.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/microsoft-onedrive/id477537958" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.microsoft.skydrive" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >OneDrive cloud storage is preinstalled on Windows 10, however, it can also be used on a Mac. We are used to the fact that iCloud and Google Drive are clouds for personal files. OneDrive will work as a worker. </span></p>
<p><span >5 GB is free. By features, the application is not inferior to competitors. Synchronization between computers, support for mobile platforms, file sharing, online backup of files, storage of various file versions, advanced access rights, customizable access levels, administration console, network control - all these functions OneDrive supports. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l2pvu8"><span >9. Blimb</span></h2>
<p><strong>Pupose: warm-up of eyes </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="http://blimb.su/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Site</a></span></p>
<p><span >Warming up the eyes is just as important as warming up the back, neck, and limbs. 2-3 minutes of exercises on this site can restore the tone of the eye muscles.</span></p>
<p><span >The principle is this: a ball moves around the screen, your task is to follow it. At the end of the session, the eyes should feel better. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l3d669"><span >10. Anydesk </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose:</strong><span ><strong> remote computer control</strong> </span></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://anydesk.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/anydesk/id1176131273" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.anydesk.anydeskandroid" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >Such programs provide remote access to third-party computers running the host application. AnyDesk is the fastest remote desktop management software on the market, according to its developers. </span></p>
<p><span >And if you look at its features, then their confidence is justified. AnyDesk shows high-performance thanks to the proprietary DeskRT video codec. Thanks to it, only changed sections are transmitted to the screen, which greatly saves traffic and reduces delays.</span></p>
<p>This is also intresting:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html">Evernote and its benefits you need to know</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.html">How to use Skype video conferencing without login</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.html">10 tools to help concentrate while working from home</a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Evernote and its benefits you need to know</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-28T02:36:48+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/202/14274370015_65440f5852_w.jpg" alt="Evernote and its benefits you need to know" />
                    Evernote is a sync manager for your notes. You can create and edit notes through any computer that has a web browser installed, and through some types of mobile phones.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/202/14274370015_65440f5852_w.jpg" alt="Evernote and its benefits you need to know" />
                <p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/review-evernote-vs-onenote-which-is-better-notes.html">Evernote</a> is a sync manager for your notes. You can create and edit notes through any computer that has a web browser installed, and through some types of mobile phones. You can save pictures, web pages, voice recordings, text, in general, whatever you want.</span></p>
<p><span >What is convenient is that when you draw a note written manually (unless of course, it is readable at all), Evernote will automatically recognize the text and save it in a separate file. Suppose you made some notes on paper during a meeting that you might find useful later. Paper can easily get lost, but Evernote will save all your notes. Take a picture of your notes, and then just upload them to Evernote. After that, they will not go anywhere from you.</span></p>
<p><span >Evernote can also help you control waste, save money and time.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >1. Use</span></strong><span > it to control your spending while traveling. When traveling, we often spend a lot of money, and then we can’t remember what this or that amount took. Evernote saves you from lengthy calculations.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >2. Record the</span></strong><span > prices of the same products in different stores, so that you can compare them later and make a purchase where it’s cheaper.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >3. Keep</span></strong><span > track of potential investment opportunities. Often reading ads or an article in a newspaper about the opportunity to invest money profitably, you do not have enough time to immediately understand everything in detail. Use Evernote to schedule this for later.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >4. Use</span></strong><span > Evernote in the library to jot down important information. Why carry a laptop with you when you can make the necessary notes with Evernote!</span></p>
<p><strong><span >5. Write down</span></strong><span > ideas for birthday gifts for relatives and friends. We often don’t know what to give them for their birthday, and, oddly enough, good ideas come up all of a sudden. Evernote helps you not to forget them.</span></p>
<p><span >In short, Evernote can make life easier for anyone with the most ordinary lifestyles.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/music-production-basics-4-steps-to-record-your-song.html">Music production Basic</a></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
