<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2020-05-01T04:40:20+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>10 free services for efficient work from home</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-free-services-for-efficient-work-from-home.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-free-services-for-efficient-work-from-home.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-01T04:37:58+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="8 free services for efficient work from home" />
                    Work from home by someone has long been perceived as a dream. But everyone was sent to a remote place and it turned out that fulfilling duties while sitting in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="8 free services for efficient work from home" />
                <p><span >Work from home by someone has long been perceived as a dream. But everyone was sent to a remote place and it turned out that fulfilling duties while sitting in a favorite chair is not so simple. <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/frontpage/1">The Tricks Peak</a> has put together applications that will make your Home office life easier.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76kverj0"><span >1. Trello </span></h2>
<p><strong> Purpose: task manager </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://trello.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/trello/id461504587" rel="nofollow">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.trello" rel="nofollow">Android </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Trello-Purpose-task-manager.jpg" alt="" width="1438" height="530"></p>
<p><span >Trello is an application for project management. It allows you to organize teamwork - it is easier for employees to report to the head of your work, and the main thing is easier to monitor what tasks workers performed. </span></p>
<p><span >The head creates the columns, employee cards. Depending on the state of the task, the card moves from one column to another. </span></p>
<p><span >Conventionally, Trello has three columns: ideas, in progress, and delivered. The employee proposed a new logo for the client company, which means he creates the corresponding card in the “ideas” column. The manager accepts it and transfers the card to the “in progress” column. At the end of the day, the employee passes the logo. The manager has no complaints, so the card is transferred to the column “delivered”. </span></p>
<p><span >It would seem that everything is simple in Trello. But the company has more than one employee, and everyone can’t keep track of it. And in Trello, the leader can see the team’s work and which projects are ready and which ones to expect in the near future. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l00ne1"><span >2. Asana </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: task manager </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://asana.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/asana-organize-tasks-work/id489969512" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.asana.app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android  </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Asana-Purpose-task-manager.jpg" alt="" width="1675" height="520"></p>
<p><span >Alternative to Trello. Asana is a more complex but more versatile task manager. First of all, here you can choose the type of project - board, list, timeline, calendar. </span></p>
<p><span >Further, the essence is the same - you add sections (the same columns) and tasks (the same cards). For example, these are the same “ideas”, “in progress” and “delivered”. The proposed task is added to the "ideas". If the manager accepts it, the task moves to the "in progress" section. At the end of the day, the employee performs the task. The manager has no complaints, and the card is transferred to the "delivered" section.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0aif2"><span >3. Ticktick</span></h2>
<p><strong>Pupose: time control </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://ticktick.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/tick-tick/id626144601" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ticktick.task" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android  </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Ticktick-Pupose-time-control.jpg" alt="" width="1710" height="635"></p>
<p><span >This service allows you to monitor completed tasks and monitor the implementation of the daily plan. </span></p>
<p><span >The principle of operation is as follows. You create tasks, they, in turn, are divided into lists. If in one list all the tasks are completed, then you achieve the goal. It turns out a kind of game. </span></p>
<p><span >Conditionally, you have created three lists: the main project, secondary tasks, the second job. In the main project, you have three tasks. Once you complete them, the goal is considered complete.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0ije3"><span >4. Zoom </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose:</strong><span ><strong> video conferencing </strong> </span></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://zoom.us/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/id546505307" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=us.zoom.videomeetings" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/203/Zoom.jpg" alt="" width="1661" height="510"></p>
<p><span >Optimal service for video chats. Skype is a thing of the past, and FaceTime is only available on Apple devices. Zoom allows you to create a conference for up to 100 participants. In it, one person is endowed with the rights of the organizer, he has the opportunity to invite and remove interlocutors. </span></p>
<p><span >However, the free version is not without limitations. In it, you can conduct a conference for up to 40 minutes. The restriction is removed in the paid version. In addition, in it, you can vest the rights of administrators of other conference participants. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l0qa44"><span >5. Slack </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: communication </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://slack.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/slack/id618783545" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Slack" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >Corporate messenger. Replaces a number of services for communication and file transfer - Skype, mail, other instant messengers, cloud storage. </span></p>
<p><span >Slack feature - synchronization with other services like Google Drive, Google Docs, Twitter, Trello, Hangouts, Dropbox, GitHub, and others. The messenger is free, but there are also paid tariffs, they increase the number of saved messages and the amount of cloud storage. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l16rl5"><span >6. Toggl</span></h2>
<p><strong>Appointment: time control </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://toggl.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/toggl-time-tracker-for-work/id1291898086" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.toggl.giskard" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span >Android</span></a></p>
<p><span >Application for time management. You will see how many hours you spend on various tasks. Toggl can look different: as a web version, a utility for a computer, or a mobile application for iOS and Android. </span></p>
<p><span >Working with the application is simple: specify the title of the task, write the name of the project to which this task belongs, and start the timer. Once done, stop the timer. And if you are distracted, also click “stop” so that the tracker fixes it. Thus, you will get a list of tasks that you perform in a day. The main thing is not to forget to turn the tracker on or off. To do this, turn on reminders: then the application will remind you of itself, asking if you forgot to turn the tracker on or off. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l1iie6"><span >7. Teamweek </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: control of the time of all team </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/teamweek/id1242738862" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.teamweek.android.app" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android</a></span><span > </span></p>
<p><span >Teamweek allows the team to maintain a common calendar to visually plan the time of each employee and see who is busy and who is free at a particular moment.</span></p>
<p><span >Tasks can be created and scheduled on the timeline. The team can be divided into groups, for each set its own time frame. Users can view tasks, filter them by project, view the team calendar in the week or month format, and see their tasks on it.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l27437"><span >8. Onedrive </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose: Cloud Storage  </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://onedrive.live.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/microsoft-onedrive/id477537958" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.microsoft.skydrive" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >OneDrive cloud storage is preinstalled on Windows 10, however, it can also be used on a Mac. We are used to the fact that iCloud and Google Drive are clouds for personal files. OneDrive will work as a worker. </span></p>
<p><span >5 GB is free. By features, the application is not inferior to competitors. Synchronization between computers, support for mobile platforms, file sharing, online backup of files, storage of various file versions, advanced access rights, customizable access levels, administration console, network control - all these functions OneDrive supports. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l2pvu8"><span >9. Blimb</span></h2>
<p><strong>Pupose: warm-up of eyes </strong></p>
<p><span ><a href="http://blimb.su/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Site</a></span></p>
<p><span >Warming up the eyes is just as important as warming up the back, neck, and limbs. 2-3 minutes of exercises on this site can restore the tone of the eye muscles.</span></p>
<p><span >The principle is this: a ball moves around the screen, your task is to follow it. At the end of the session, the eyes should feel better. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e76l3d669"><span >10. Anydesk </span></h2>
<p><strong>Purpose:</strong><span ><strong> remote computer control</strong> </span></p>
<p><span ><a href="https://anydesk.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Website</a></span><span >, </span><span ><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/anydesk/id1176131273" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iOS</a></span><span >, </span><a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.anydesk.anydeskandroid" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Android </a></p>
<p><span >Such programs provide remote access to third-party computers running the host application. AnyDesk is the fastest remote desktop management software on the market, according to its developers. </span></p>
<p><span >And if you look at its features, then their confidence is justified. AnyDesk shows high-performance thanks to the proprietary DeskRT video codec. Thanks to it, only changed sections are transmitted to the screen, which greatly saves traffic and reduces delays.</span></p>
<p>This is also intresting:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html">Evernote and its benefits you need to know</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.html">How to use Skype video conferencing without login</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.html">10 tools to help concentrate while working from home</a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Evernote and its benefits you need to know</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/evernote-and-its-benefits-you-need-to-know.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-28T02:36:48+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/202/14274370015_65440f5852_w.jpg" alt="Evernote and its benefits you need to know" />
                    Evernote is a sync manager for your notes. You can create and edit notes through any computer that has a web browser installed, and through some types of mobile phones.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/202/14274370015_65440f5852_w.jpg" alt="Evernote and its benefits you need to know" />
                <p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/review-evernote-vs-onenote-which-is-better-notes.html">Evernote</a> is a sync manager for your notes. You can create and edit notes through any computer that has a web browser installed, and through some types of mobile phones. You can save pictures, web pages, voice recordings, text, in general, whatever you want.</span></p>
<p><span >What is convenient is that when you draw a note written manually (unless of course, it is readable at all), Evernote will automatically recognize the text and save it in a separate file. Suppose you made some notes on paper during a meeting that you might find useful later. Paper can easily get lost, but Evernote will save all your notes. Take a picture of your notes, and then just upload them to Evernote. After that, they will not go anywhere from you.</span></p>
<p><span >Evernote can also help you control waste, save money and time.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >1. Use</span></strong><span > it to control your spending while traveling. When traveling, we often spend a lot of money, and then we can’t remember what this or that amount took. Evernote saves you from lengthy calculations.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >2. Record the</span></strong><span > prices of the same products in different stores, so that you can compare them later and make a purchase where it’s cheaper.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >3. Keep</span></strong><span > track of potential investment opportunities. Often reading ads or an article in a newspaper about the opportunity to invest money profitably, you do not have enough time to immediately understand everything in detail. Use Evernote to schedule this for later.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >4. Use</span></strong><span > Evernote in the library to jot down important information. Why carry a laptop with you when you can make the necessary notes with Evernote!</span></p>
<p><strong><span >5. Write down</span></strong><span > ideas for birthday gifts for relatives and friends. We often don’t know what to give them for their birthday, and, oddly enough, good ideas come up all of a sudden. Evernote helps you not to forget them.</span></p>
<p><span >In short, Evernote can make life easier for anyone with the most ordinary lifestyles.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/music-production-basics-4-steps-to-record-your-song.html">Music production Basic</a></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Music Production Basics: 4 Steps to Record Your Song</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/music-production-basics-4-steps-to-record-your-song.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/music-production-basics-4-steps-to-record-your-song.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-10T23:45:48+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/201/Reason-Studio-compressed.jpg" alt="Reason Studios is a music production software" />
                    The world of music has changed. Decades ago, if you were a musician and wanted to record an album ... That you and the band played every night in the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/201/Reason-Studio-compressed.jpg" alt="Reason Studios is a music production software" />
                <p><span >The world of music has changed.</span></p>
<p><span >Decades ago, if you were a musician and wanted to record an album ...</span></p>
<p><span >That you and the band played every night in the bars like damned ...</span></p>
<p><span >But everything has changed.</span></p>
<p><span >Today, in the production of music, there is a trend towards a transition to </span><em><span >home</span></em><span > studios.</span></p>
<p><span >Great music is constantly recorded in bedrooms, garages, and basements by ordinary people like us ...</span></p>
<p><span >Usually only with a computer, USB microphone and headphones.</span></p>
<p><span >Record a song, put it on the Internet, watch how it becomes popular ... the next day you are a star.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3h0"><span >It is easy and simple due to Reason Studios. Here is the short intro about Reason Studio:</span></h3>
<p><span ><a href="https://patrickdearteaga.com/propellerhead-reason/" title="Reason Studios is a music production software" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Reason Studios</a>, turning the world’s music dreamers into music makers and inspiring them to keep dreaming.</span></p>
<p><span >As developers of the Reason platform of instruments, plugins, music production software and mobile app, Reason Studios inspired millions of users all over the world to create.</span></p>
<p><span >Whether you’re making your first beat, producing the next hit song, crafting your own sound, playing around with an idea, or just figuring stuff out—Reason Studios empower you to do it.</span></p>
<p><span >But before any of this happens, you first need to learn how the process of recording music happens.</span></p>
<p><span >Therefore, in this post, I will divide it into 4 steps ... from start to finish.</span></p>
<p><span >Let's start ...</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i1"><span >Step 1: Recording Process</span></h2>
<p><span >In the early era of sound recording ...</span></p>
<p><span >The recording process was much simpler than it is now.</span></p>
<p><span >Entire performances were recorded on one try, sometimes with one or two microphones.</span></p>
<p><span >However, today a more complex process is used, known as </span><strong><span >multi-channel recording</span></strong><span > ...</span></p>
<p><span >When each instrument is recorded separately and then inserted into the “mix”.</span></p>
<p><span >This method has 2 BIG advantages :</span></p>
<ol>
<li><strong><span >It allows engineers to shape and modify the sound of each instrument independently of the others.</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >It allows you to record all instruments in turn.</span></strong></li>
</ol>
<p><span >When this method appeared, one person became able to do something that previously required a team of sound engineers and musicians.</span></p>
<p><span >And although in reality, each engineer has his own process steps ...</span></p>
<p><span >When you are done with this, you are ready for the </span><strong><span >next phase</span></strong><span > ...</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i2"><span >Step 2: mount process</span></h2>
<p><span >Now that you have recorded the tracks, it is time to clean them up.</span></p>
<p><span >Because no matter how accurate you are when recording ...</span></p>
<p><span >There will always be SOME errors that can and should be fixed ...</span></p>
<p><span >Using the great editing tools now available in the Reason music production software.</span></p>
<p><span >Typically, mounting includes 5 tasks :</span></p>
<ol>
<li><strong><span >Ordering</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >Comparison</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >Noise suppression</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >Time adjustment</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >Sound adjustment</span></strong></li>
</ol>
<p><span >During </span><strong><span >ordering,</span></strong><span > you can once again listen to everything that you have done to evaluate what is good and what is bad.</span></p>
<p><span >For example, you can :</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >delete whole useless tracks</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >cut sections of tracks that interfere with the mix</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >move sections to other parts of a song</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >delete entire sections of a song together</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >During the </span><strong><span >comparison,</span></strong><span > you compare the identical examination of each track and select the best.</span></p>
<p><span >With </span><strong><span >noise reduction,</span></strong><span > you cut out all the sounds before, after, and between the sections where the instrument is playing.</span></p>
<p><span >This means getting rid of :</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >background voices</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >amplifier hiss</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >foot sounds</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >creaks of a chair</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >sounds of breathing</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >or just stagnant air</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >To further reduce noise, you can add a high-pass filter to the lower frequency range of </span><em><span >non-bass</span></em><span > instruments to get rid of rattling sounds.</span></p>
<p><span >When </span><strong><span >adjusting for sound,</span></strong><span > you can substitute any fake note back </span><em><span >into action</span></em><span > using </span><strong><span >auto-tuning</span></strong><span > or a similar instrument.</span></p>
<p><span >This is usually used for vocals but is also suitable for most melodic instruments.</span></p>
<p><span >This completes </span><strong><span >the mounting process</span></strong><span >.</span></p>
<p><span >Let's move on to the next step ...</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i3"><span >Step 3: The Mixing Process</span></h2>
<p><span >When the tracks are put in order as you need ...</span></p>
<p><span >The next goal is to make one connected record out of them ... by “ </span><strong><span >mixing</span></strong><span > ”.</span></p>
<p><span >Mixing in itself is a kind of art, and can occur in various ways ...</span></p>
<p><span >There are certain tasks that absolutely everyone does ...</span></p>
<p><span >Such as :</span></p>
<ol>
<li><strong><span >Balance the volume</span></strong><span > so that no instrument sounds too loud or quiet in relation to others.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Panning</span></strong><span >, which sets each instrument to its place in the </span><em><span >stereo image</span></em><span >, just like the musicians have their own place </span><em><span >on the stage</span></em><span >.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Frequency correction</span></strong><span >, creating its place in the frequency spectrum of each instrument, so that sounds do not compete with each other for the frequency range.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Compression</span></strong><span > equalizing the dynamic range of the instrument so that each note is clearly audible and the mix as a whole sounds louder.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >A reverb</span></strong><span > that creates a three-dimensional space for the mix, giving a sense of depth and making instruments sound like in </span><em><span >one room</span></em><span >.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Automation</span></strong><span > allows you to change settings in different parts of the song, adding a sense of </span><em><span >movement to the</span></em><span > mix.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span >When will your mix be ready after using these instruments and when it will sound </span><em><span >great</span></em><span > ...</span></p>
<p><span >It’s time to move on to the next step ...</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i4"><span >Step 4: mastering process</span></h2>
<p><span >Before your song is ready for mastering ...</span></p>
<p><span >All tracks must be </span><em><span >rewritten</span></em><span > in one stereo file ...</span></p>
<p><span >Or, as they say, " </span><strong><span >merge into one</span></strong><span > ."</span></p>
<p><span >When this is done, you need to apply different </span><strong><span >mastering techniques</span></strong><span > to the song ...</span></p>
<p><span >To make it sound even </span><em><span >better</span></em><span >.</span></p>
<p><span >The following techniques are commonly used :</span></p>
<ol>
<li><strong><span >Maximize the volume</span></strong><span > by further compressing and limiting the signal to maintain the average signal level at the highest level, but without sacrificing dynamics </span><em><span >too much</span></em><span >.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Frequency balancing</span></strong><span > by further correction, as well as </span><em><span >multi-band compression</span></em><span >, which allows compressing frequency ranges separately from the entire spectrum.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Stereo extension</span></strong><span > using a special plugin designed to create an additional feeling of “width” at high frequencies of the mix.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span >When everything sounds great, the track is converted to the appropriate </span><strong><span >sampling frequency and bit depth</span></strong><span >. For example, audio on a CD has a frequency of </span><strong><span >44.1 kHz</span></strong><span > and a depth of </span><strong><span >16 bits</span></strong><span >.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i5"><span >Do it yourself or delegate?</span></h3>
<p><span >Simply put, mastering is a </span><em><span >difficult</span></em><span > process. And if you do not understand what you are doing, then you can only </span><em><span >make</span></em><span > things </span><em><span >worse</span></em><span >.</span></p>
<p><span >Therefore, for intelligence engineers, the usual thing is to transfer this work into the hands of “ mastering engineers, ” rather than do it yourself.</span></p>
<p><span >But…</span></p>
<p><span >If you want to try, here are the apps that I recommend:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Reason Studios - a music production software.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >On the </span><em><span >good</span></em><span > engineers mastering it is necessary to spend more money, which not everyone has or not everyone wants to spend.</span></p>
<p><span >Fortunately, today there are many freelance engineers who are willing to do this job for little money.</span></p>
<p><span >As I said earlier in this article, look for sites similar to </span><strong><span >Fiverr</span></strong><span >.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >See sample offers for everything related to sound ... including </span><strong><u><span >editing</span></u></strong><span >, </span><strong><u><span >mixing,</span></u></strong><span >  and </span><strong><span ><span style="text-decoration: underline;">mastering</span> </span></strong><span >at Reason Studio.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Now…</span></p>
<p><span >Given the above, the next question ...</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e5im4i3i6"><span >Is mastering always necessary?</span></h3>
<p><span >Decades ago, when all studio recordings were for sale, </span><em><span >everything</span></em><span > worked out.</span></p>
<p><span >However, these days ... when many amateur recordings are made " </span><em><span >simply because</span></em><span > " ...</span></p>
<p><span >Home studios themselves do mastering or don't do it at all. And that is the norm.</span></p>
<p><span >If all you do is record music for family and friends, then who cares?</span></p>
<p><span >But…</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >If you want to professionally record music or ...</span></strong></li>
<li><strong><span >You just want her to sound the best ...</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Reason Studios - a music production software is MANDATORY.</span></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to use Skype video conferencing without registration and login</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-08T15:20:39+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/200/How-to-use-Skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.jpg" alt="How to use Skype video conferencing without registration and login" />
                    You don’t have to download and install the Skype Smartphone Application or Skype for windows. You don’t even need to sign in. Since we are all sitting at home now,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/200/How-to-use-Skype-video-conferencing-without-registration-and-login.jpg" alt="How to use Skype video conferencing without registration and login" />
                <p>You don’t have to download and install the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-things-about-skype-for-business.html">Skype Smartphone Application</a> or Skype for windows. You don’t even need to sign in.<br>Since we are all sitting at home now, video calling is needed more than ever. This is sometimes the only way to get in touch with family, friends, and sometimes the employer. The most popular video conferencing tool is Zoom. It allows you to make free 40-minute conference calls in which up to 100 people can participate. This allows for real online parties. But what if you need to talk continuously for several hours, when you, for example, work on a complex project or are just used to talking with a loved one for a long time?<br>So here old Skype comes to the rescue, which with the latest update has got a new Meet Now feature. It works: you click on the “Meeting” button in the installed Skype client or simply in the web interface in the browser. Copy the created link and send it to friends or colleagues. That's it, <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-viber-for-windows-featured-some-interesting-updates-including-video-chats.html">video conferencing</a> is created.<br>Anyone who has a link can join. No need to register or install Skype - everything works right in the browser.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/200/Screenshot_6.png" alt="Image Credit: https://www.skype.com/en/free-conference-call/" width="1706" height="496">
<figcaption >Image Credit: https://www.skype.com/en/free-conference-call/</figcaption>
</figure>
<p>If you yourself do not use Skype, do not want to download it or enter the web client, you can still create a conference using a special page.<br>The number of voice communication participants should not exceed 50, but up to 600 people can be present in a text <br><br>There are no restrictions on the duration of the communication session - you can create a meeting in advance, and later join it. Call records are stored for 30 days, which is convenient for webinars and interviews.<br>In Skype, you can’t add cool backgrounds, like in Zoom, but you can blur the background behind you so that no one can see what mess you have. By default, this feature is already active.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>7 Cancer Prevention Tips to Reduce Risk</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/7-cancer-prevention-tips-to-reduce-risk.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/7-cancer-prevention-tips-to-reduce-risk.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-31T19:20:10+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/199/smoke-1002461_640.jpg" alt="7 Cancer Prevention Tips to Reduce Risk" />
                    It is generally accepted that the risk of developing cancer depends on lifestyle. However, what is known today about its prevention (preventing cancer) is still at the stage of development&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/199/smoke-1002461_640.jpg" alt="7 Cancer Prevention Tips to Reduce Risk" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1e4oas36s0">It is generally accepted that the risk of developing cancer depends on lifestyle. However, what is known today about its prevention (preventing cancer) is still at the stage of development and refinement.</p>
<p><span >Therefore, those who are interested in cancer prevention should follow these tips.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oat20n1"><span >1. Stop smoking</span></h2>
<p><span >Using any type of tobacco is a risk of disease. Smoking is associated with various types of cancer: cancer of the lungs, mouth, throat, larynx, pancreas, bladder, cervix and kidney. Chewing tobacco more provokes cancer of the oral cavity and pancreas. Even if you do not smoke, exposure to secondhand smoke can increase your risk of developing lung cancer.</span></p>
<p><span >Quitting smoking is an important part of cancer prevention. If you need help with this, contact a specialist.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oat9cl2"><span > 2. Follow a healthy diet</span></h2>
<p><span >Although choosing healthy foods cannot guarantee cancer prevention, it can reduce your risk. The following are recommendations:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Eat lots of fruits and vegetables. Base your diet on fruits, vegetables, and other plant-based foods such as whole grains and beans.</span></li>
<li><span >Watch your weight. Choose low-calorie foods, including refined sugar and fat from animal sources.</span></li>
<li><span >Drink moderate amounts of alcohol. The risk of various types of cancer — including breast, colon, lung, kidney, and liver cancer — increases with the amount of alcohol consumed and the length of time it is consumed.</span></li>
<li><span >Limit the consumption of processed meat. A report by the International Agency for Research on Cancer, the cancer agency of the World Health Organization, concluded that eating large amounts of processed meat may slightly increase the risk of certain types of cancer.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Also, women who use the Mediterranean diet with olive oil and mixed nuts are less likely to have breast cancer. The Mediterranean diet focuses mainly on plant foods such as fruits and vegetables, whole grains, legumes and nuts. People who follow the Mediterranean diet choose healthy fats, such as olive oil, rather than animal origin; fish instead of red meat.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oatmq13"><span >3. Maintain a healthy weight and be physically active</span></h2>
<p><span >Maintaining a healthy weight can reduce the risk of various types of cancer, including cancer of the breast, prostate, lung, colon and kidney.</span></p>
<p><span >Physical activity also matters. Besides being able to control your weight, physical activity alone can reduce the risk of breast and colon cancer.</span></p>
<p><span >Adults who participate in any physical activity receive certain health benefits. Essential health benefits will be at least 2.5 hours per week of moderate physical activity or 1.5 hours per week of active exercise. You can also combine moderate and vigorous activity. As a general goal, include at least 30 minutes of physical activity in your daily routine, and even more if you can.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oau1gb4"><span >4. Protect from the sun</span></h2>
<p><span >Skin cancer is one of the most common types of cancer, and at the same time one of the most preventable. Try these tips:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Avoid the midday sun. Stay away from the sun from 10 to 16 hours, when the sun's rays are the strongest.</span></li>
<li><span >Stay in the shade. When you are outdoors, stay in the shade for as long as possible. Sunglasses and a wide-brimmed hat also help.</span></li>
<li><span >Cover open areas. Wear loose clothing that covers as much of the skin as possible. </span></li>
<li><span >Do not save on sunscreen. Use a broad spectrum sunscreen with SPF. Apply it abundantly every two hours or more often, especially if you are in the sun.</span></li>
<li><span >Avoid tanning beds and tanning beds. They are just as harmful as the active sun rays.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oauau45"><span >5. Get vaccinated</span></h2>
<p><span >Cancer prevention includes protection against some viral infections:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span >Hepatitis B. Hepatitis B may increase your risk of developing liver cancer. Hepatitis B vaccine is recommended for some high-risk adults:</span></li>
<li><span > people with transmitted infections;</span></li>
<li><span > people who take drugs (intravenously);</span></li>
<li><span > men who have intrest with men, and medical facilities and their employees who may be exposed to contaminated blood or body fluids.</span></li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><span >Human papillomavirus (HPV). HPV is a transmitted virus that can lead to cancer of the cervix and other genital organs, as well as squamous cell carcinoma of the head and neck. The HPV vaccine is recommended for girls and boys aged 11 and 12 years. </span></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oaulsh6"><span >6. Avoid risky behavior</span></h2>
<p><span >Another effective cancer prevention tactic is to avoid risky behavior that can lead to infections, which in turn can increase your risk of cancer. For instance:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Practice safe. Limit the number of your partners and use a condom during meet. The more partners you have, the more likely you are to get a transmitted infection, such as HIV or HPV. People with HIV or AIDS have a higher risk of developing cancer of the anus, liver, and lungs. HPV is most often associated with cervical cancer, but it can also increase the risk of developing cancer of the anus, penis, throat, vulva and vagina.</span></li>
<li><span >Use disposable needles for any injection. Sharing needles with people who use intravenous drugs can lead to HIV, as well as to hepatitis B and hepatitis C, which can increase the risk of developing liver cancer.</span></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4oausps7"><span >7. Have a regular medical examination</span></h2>
<p><span >Regular examinations for various types of cancer, such as cancer of the skin, colon, cervix and breast, etc., can increase the chances of early diagnosis of cancer, then treatment is likely to be successful. </span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-health-insurance-work.html">How does health insurance work?</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How does health insurance work?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-health-insurance-work.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-health-insurance-work.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-31T16:45:36+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/198/health-1175296_640.jpg" alt="How does health insurance work?" />
                    In this article we will guide you how does health insurance work and how you can apply for that. The essence of medical insurance is that a person who buys&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/198/health-1175296_640.jpg" alt="How does health insurance work?" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1e4o5tlat0">In this article we will guide you how does health insurance work and how you can apply for that.</p>
<p><span >The essence of medical insurance is that a person who buys an annual policy, upon the occurrence of an insured event (illness or injury), gets the right to free and extraordinary medical care within the framework of the budgets and the list of services that are provided for them. The budgets themselves, the list of services, the level of hospitals and clinics depend on the specific insurer, the price of the policy, as well as the age and state of human health. Roughly speaking, the younger and healthier you are, the cheaper the insurance will cost. As a rule, it guarantees inpatient (treatment in a hospital), outpatient (call a doctor at home), emergency (ambulance departure) assistance, payment and delivery of medicines. Insurance can cover the cost of treatment in whole or in part. If the insured is ill, he needs to call the insurance call center and explain the essence of the problem.</span></p>
<p><span >The client will be refused insurance if he has:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >disability;</span></li>
<li><span >congenital diseases;</span></li>
<li><span >disease window</span></li>
<li><span >diabetes;</span></li>
<li><span >tuberculosis;</span></li>
<li><span >HIV</span></li>
<li><span >chronic renal failure;</span></li>
<li><span >drug or alcohol addiction.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Depending on the specific IC, the “forbidden” list may change, but not significantly.</span></p>
<p><span >In most countries, compulsory health insurance exists when a person is insured by the state or the employer, and the cost of the policy is deducted from the state budget or his salary. Our health insurance is purely voluntary. And you will have to pay for it either yourself, or the employer will do it for you if he considers it necessary.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4o5tlau1"><span >How did I choose insurance</span></h2>
<p><span >Alas, I do not have corporate insurance. Therefore, I searched for a policy myself. The “dental package” was decisive for me. I was interested in both planned (prophylactic) and unplanned (sudden toothache) treatment, as well as dental prosthetics. I called the top ten companies - leader rating in the field of health insurance. As it turned out, most of them do not insure individuals and only works with the corporate sector. Only three insurance companies offered individual insurance. In each of them, I considered two policies. The first is the recommendation of the insurance agent based on my wishes for services and price. The second is the policy with the highest limit on dentistry. Here is what came of it.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e4o5tlau2"><span >Terms of registration</span></h3>
<p><span >To obtain insurance, you need a passport and identification code. To sign the contract you will have to fill out a declaration of health. This is a questionnaire in which you need to answer several questions in detail: indicate the diseases that you previously had, chronic ailments and disabilities, if any, etc. At the same time, consultants recommend not to be cunning, since at the very first insured event the examination will show the patient's real state. Any indicated untruth may become a reason for the non-payment of compensation for insurance treatment.</span></p>
<p><span >The policy takes effect 14 days after signing, but you can agree on an earlier "activation". The company works with both private and public hospitals and pharmacies. The level of the facility depends on the class of policy. There can be seven of them in the "Provident" for individuals. The cheapest works only with state and departmental hospitals, private clinics appear in the Elite, and VIP guarantees the services of even branded commercial clinics (such as Boris, Dobrobut, etc.). When treating in partner hospitals, the limit covers the full cost of treatment within the limit, in the rest - half. In private clinics and laboratories, a franchise of 25% to 75% is possible. An up-to-date list of partners with the size of payment and interest of franchises is sent by the manager upon request. Medicines can be issued for free only at the network of partner pharmacies, and those drugs that fall under the exception will have to be purchased on their own. Change the clinic or the doctor, if suddenly you are not satisfied with his qualifications, or, for example, he will be a boor, you can call the call center.</span></p>
<p><span >Insured events are:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >acute diseases that threaten health and life;</span></li>
<li><span >chronic diseases (up to 3 exacerbations per year);</span></li>
<li><span >accidents arising out of no fault of the client;</span></li>
<li><span >unscheduled surgical intervention (if an operation is necessary in case of a chronic disease or accident).</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The list of exclusions from insurance cases is longer - 2 sheets of A4 12 font. In short: insurance does not cover all cosmetic, preventive and non-traditional, as well as planned surgical interventions, orthodontics, and prosthetics. If this rule is applied to dentistry, then insurance does not cover preventive brushing, teeth whitening, installation of crowns and braces, as well as consultations with doctors on these issues.</span></p>
<p>Alos read:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/faster-and-cheaper-amazing-tips-to-transit.html">Faster and amazing tips to transit</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.html">10 tools to help concentrate while working from home</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/4-ways-to-save-instagram-videos.html">4 ways to save instagram videos </a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>10 tools to help concentrate while working from home</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-28T14:00:44+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/197/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.jpg" alt="10 tools to help concentrate while working from home" />
                    Many of us work from home during these difficult days, but few manage to maintain concentration and focus on their work. No matter what distracts you, Today The Tricks Peak&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/197/10-tools-to-help-concentrate-while-working-from-home.jpg" alt="10 tools to help concentrate while working from home" />
                <p><span >Many of us work from home during these difficult days, but few manage to maintain concentration and focus on their work. No matter what distracts you, Today The Tricks Peak author brings you below 10 tools that will help you concentrate when working from home and do your job better.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdri0"><span >1. Focus matrix</span></h2>
<p><span >A task manager for Mac, which will help you prioritize correctly and not break your concentration. For simplicity, all incoming tasks are divided by time and importance, while urgent matters may not be very significant, but non-urgent ones, on the contrary, are extremely important.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj1"><span >2. Pomotroid</span></h2>
<p><span >The Pomodoro technique is the easiest way to deal with procrastination, maintaining a balance between work and leisure. This application for Windows, macOS, and Linux will adhere to the system "25 minutes of work - 5 minutes of rest." If standard time periods are not suitable, you can set your own in the settings. Free Download</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj2"><span >3. Hocus focus</span></h2>
<p><span >Multitasking is one of the main enemies of productivity. Hocus Focus for Mac helps you stay focused, leaving only the current window active and hiding the rest. The application has several profiles that allow you to configure the time after which the windows will be minimized. By default, the delay is 30 seconds, but in focus mode, as soon as you switch to one of the applications, all the others are hidden.</span></p>
<p><span >Download (free)</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj3"><span >4. Momentum</span></h2>
<p><span >The Momentum browser extension is designed to deter the temptation to procrastinate on the Internet: on all new tabs, it displays inspirational images and motivating quotes. It displays the time, the main goal for the day and task lists. All this so that you do not forget why you went online.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj4"><span >5. Rooster</span></h2>
<p><span >Like Momentum, Rooster uses the new Chrome tab, which usually leads to the temptation to mess around. The extension will show how much time has been spent on which pages, and will also be able to display notifications that you have been on unproductive sites for too long.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj5"><span >6. Just focus</span></h2>
<p><span >If you don’t have much self-control, the extension for Chrome Just Focus will help. Enter in its settings the addresses of the sites to which you are most distracted, and after turning on the focus mode, they will be temporarily blocked. When you go to a page from the blacklist, the Just Focus screen will appear instead of it with an inspirational quote.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj6"><span >7. Self-control</span></h2>
<p><span >A more hardcore counterpart to the previous extension as a program for macOS. Self ‑ Control is tougher: after setting the timer, all sites from the blacklist will not open in any browser. Moreover, closing the application will not do anything: the lock will be released only after a specified time has passed. Download (free)</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj7"><span >8. Focusmusic.fm</span></h2>
<p><span >When everyone around is messing around and interfering, but there is no separate room for privacy, all that remains is to put on headphones and isolate yourself with music. Focusmusic.fm has four channels, including electronics and classics, as well as the sounds of rain. You can listen both from the site and through mobile applications. Go to the website</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj8"><span >9. Spectacle</span></h2>
<p><span >Many have large monitors in the office, but at home, they usually have to be content with a laptop. Spectacle Utility for Mac makes it easier to manage windows by resizing them and distributing screen space based on tasks. All manipulations occur with the help of hotkeys, you don’t have to aim at the borders with the cursor. Download (free)</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e4g5kdrj9"><span >10. Flowstate</span></h2>
<p><span >Unusual text editor for those who can not work without a magic pedal. Flowstate for macOS will force you to write under the pain of losing all typed text. If you stop typing, then after 5 seconds everything will be deleted. </span></p>
<p><span >I hope, you will like the above list of tools. feel free to comment on this post.</span></p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/6-tools-to-transfer-playlists-from-one-music-service-to-another.html">6 tools to transfer playlist from one music service to another </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 useful Google Chrome browser features you need to know</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-useful-google-chrome-browser-features-you-need-to-know.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-useful-google-chrome-browser-features-you-need-to-know.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-18T18:24:06+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/196/browser-773216_640.jpg" alt="5 useful Google Chrome browser features you need to know" />
                    These Google Chrome features are available without additional extensions. If you have a lot of bookmarks in the browser, and you need to save a few more links for a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/196/browser-773216_640.jpg" alt="5 useful Google Chrome browser features you need to know" />
                <p><span >These Google Chrome features are available without additional extensions.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e3msl3cr0"><span >1. Shortcut to any page on the desktop</span></h3>
<p><span >If you have a lot of bookmarks in the browser, and you need to save a few more links for a while, use the shortcut function. With its help, you can send it to the desktop a website icon that redirects immediately to the page you need.</span></p>
<p><span >To do this, open the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-clean-up-and-group-tabs-in-google-chrome.html">Chrome settings</a> on the selected page and select "Advanced Tools". In the submenu, there will be an item for creating a shortcut. Click on it and give the link a name.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e3msl3cs1"><span >2. Save page to PDF</span></h3>
<p><span >If you need to save the page exactly in the form in which it is displayed in the browser, you can use the save function in PDF format. It is available through the Print menu. To go to it, press Ctrl + P and select the option “Save as PDF” on the left.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e3msl3cs2"><span >3. View a cached version of a site</span></h3>
<p><span >To return to an earlier version of a web page or open an article already removed from the site, you can <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/gg.html">access the cache</a>. To do this, add “cache:” before the page address and press “Enter”. In the same way, you can open previously viewed pages without connecting to the Web.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e3msl3cs3"><span >4. Return a closed tab with a key combination</span></h3>
<p><span >There are several ways to open the last closed tab. The most inconvenient is to find the page in the browser history. A little more practical is to right-click on another tab and select "Open Closed Tab" in the drop-down menu.</span></p>
<p><span >The fastest way is to use the keyboard shortcut Ctrl + Shift + T.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e3msl3cs4"><span >5. Watching YouTube in Picture-in-Picture Mode</span></h3>
<p><span >To work in a browser or other programs without interrupting <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-free-ways-to-download-youtube-videos.html">YouTube</a>, a video can be opened in a separate window that will be displayed on top of all applications. To do this, go to the desired video, right-click on it, opening the first menu of the basic settings, and then click here a second time. Another context menu will open, in which there will be an item "Picture in Picture".</span></p>
<p><span >This function transfers the clip to a small window that will remain on the screen even if you minimize the browser. The size of the window can be adjusted by stretching it over the edges in different directions.</span></p>
<p><span >That's all, Now your turn, Which of the features of Google Chrome Browser do you use? Share in the comments!</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to clean up and group tabs in Google Chrome</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-clean-up-and-group-tabs-in-google-chrome.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-clean-up-and-group-tabs-in-google-chrome.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-17T10:02:37+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/195/Group-Tab-in-Chrome.jpg" alt="How to clean up and group tabs in Google Chrome" />
                    Many of us have dozens of tabs open in Chrome at the same time. To put things in order, we install various extensions or even switch to other browsers -&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/195/Group-Tab-in-Chrome.jpg" alt="How to clean up and group tabs in Google Chrome" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1e3jc3hll0"><span >Many of us have dozens of tabs open in Chrome at the same time. To put things in order, we install various extensions or even switch to other browsers - Today The Tricks Peak author brings you a way of clean up your Google Chrome browser and how to combined tabs into groups.</span></p>
<p><span >There is no need for additional tools. <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/google-chrome-video-downloader-all-time-top-10-extensions-list.html">Google Chrome</a> already can sort tabs by category. It’s just hidden in the settings.</span></p>
<p><span >Here's how to activate this feature. Type in the address bar <em><strong>chrome://flags/</strong></em> and press Enter. In the opened settings in the search, type <strong>Tab Groups</strong>.</span></p>
<p><span >Switch the Tab Groups option that appears to Enabled, then click the Relaunch button at the bottom. The browser will restart.</span></p>
<p><span >Now right-click on any tab and click <strong>“Add to New Group”</strong>. The tab will be colored, a colored circle will appear next to it.</span></p>
<p><span >You can click on it and change the hue of the group of tabs, and also give it a name.</span></p>
<p><span >When you want to assign a tab to an already created group, right-click it and select <strong>"Add to an existing group."</strong> Or just drag the item with the mouse.</span></p>
<p><span >You can create any number of groups, but the number of colors is limited - only eight. However, this is enough to restore order.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/gg.html">How to open 404 pages not found error</a></p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to open 404 pages not found error - What to do</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/gg.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/gg.html</id>

        <updated>2020-03-12T22:30:39+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/194/thetrickspeak-404-page.png" alt="How to open 404 pages not found error - What to do" />
                    Did you face a 404 error, while browsing the internet once in a lifetime, you actively use the Internet has had to deal with it? In most cases, this causes&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/194/thetrickspeak-404-page.png" alt="How to open 404 pages not found error - What to do" />
                <p><span >Did you face a 404 error, while <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-icloud-website-on-other-browser-and-smartphones.html">browsing the internet</a> once in a lifetime, you actively use the Internet has had to deal with it? In most cases, this causes discontent and the user immediately closes the error page. But if you have a book market that page and have very important information or article and you need to read it again. However, today <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/frontpage/1">The Tricks Peak</a> author brings you several ways to solve the problem.</span></p>
<p><span >With active surfing on the Internet, you often have to deal with broken pages or entire sites. This usually happens when you follow a link from a search engine or your bookmarked pages. In this case, a special page appears with code 404.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e37rt7i60"><span >Verify Address</span></h2>
<p><span >The first thing to do is to check the page address. If you entered it manually, then there may be typos or extra characters. If you follow the link, then the problem may be in it. Since people fill the sites, they too can make mistakes and put broken links. In this case, you must carefully review the address. </span></p>
<p><span >Copy the full address of the link: right-click on the link and select "Copy link address". Paste it into any text editor and review it carefully. Perhaps in the link, there are extra characters, spaces or something else is out of order.</span></p>
<p><span >Try also to search for the page address in the search engine. Perhaps the search engine will give the correct link without errors.</span></p>
<p><span >Also, the page could be renamed, but the redirect is not configured. In this case, you will not be transferred to a new address. It is impossible to guess what exactly changed the page address. One can only assume that it is still on the site and has a similar name. Try to search the page for keywords on the site itself or through a <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-the-google-most-relevant-search-for-us.html">search engine</a>.</span></p>
<p><span >You can also write to the owners of the site, perhaps they will prompt you a new address or give the necessary information.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e37rt7i61"><span >Try a different browser</span></h2>
<p><span >It is unlikely, but still worth trying another browser. If the page opens in it, then the problem is on your side. Try clearing your browser cache. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e37rt7i62"><span >Find the saved copy of the page</span></h2>
<p><span >If all else fails, you can try to find a saved copy of the page. This can be done through a search engine or website web.archive.org.</span></p>
<p><span >If you went to a page from a search engine, then return to the search results and open a cached copy. You can also open a copy right away using the cache statement.</span></p>
<p><span >Website web.archive.org offers a little more functionality. If the page was popular, then you can find several copies of it stored at different times.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-enable-dark-theme-on-instagram.html">How to enable dark theme on Instagram</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
