<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2019-12-19T14:14:29+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>What you need to know about taxi service in Spain</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-you-need-to-know-about-taxi-service-in-spain.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-you-need-to-know-about-taxi-service-in-spain.html</id>

        <updated>2019-12-19T14:12:17+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/177/What-you-need-to-know-about-taxi-service-in-Spain.jpg" alt="What you need to know about taxi service in Spain" />
                    Going on a trip, you need to familiarize yourself with the features of the transport system of the country in which you plan to travel. After all, any situation leading&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/177/What-you-need-to-know-about-taxi-service-in-Spain.jpg" alt="What you need to know about taxi service in Spain" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jm0"><span >Going on a trip, you need to familiarize yourself with the features of the transport system of the country in which you plan to travel. After all, any situation leading to a violation, the travel plan can result in intangible losses of time and money. Therefore, it is so important to understand all major types of transport, especially such as taxis. Let's try to find out how the taxi service in Spain works.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jo1"><span >Features of a taxi service in Spain.</span></h2>
<p><span >Spain remains a fairly developed country, in which all EU standards apply. And this means that using the services of a taxi, you have the right to count on compliance with safety standards, a satisfactory condition of the car and the mandatory presence of a meter.</span></p>
<p><span >The regions of Spain have their specifics, therefore, you will find a more comfortable trip than anywhere else in all EU.</span></p>
<p><span >An official taxi driver's license is not cheap and you need to go through many bureaucratic procedures to get it, so most Spanish taxi drivers value their workplace and are unlikely to risk their permission for a couple of extra euros.</span></p>
<p><span >As in most European countries, you can use taxi services in the country by placing an order by phone or using a mobile application or simply by catching it on the street. You can also use the services of cars parked in special parking lots.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jo2"><span >How to order a taxi in Spain</span></h2>
<p><span >Walking through the streets of Spanish cities, you can see special taxi stands, which can be easily recognized by a blue rectangular sign with a white letter T. You can order a taxi directly at these stops, but certain rules must be observed.</span></p>
<p><span >Most importantly, always get in the car closest to the exit, as there is a sequence of drivers leaving the parking lot. If parking is not enough for everyone, then people with children, pregnant women, the elderly or disabled are the first to get into them.</span></p>
<p><span >You can catch a free car, as in most countries of the world, with a wave of your hand, but keep in mind that the driver is not entitled to pick up a passenger within a radius of 50 meters from the parking lot.</span></p>
<p><span >The fact that the car is free is signaled by a panel with a glowing green light and the sign on the roof of the car. Therefore, it would be most reasonable to book a transfer from the airport to the hotel in advance.</span></p>
<p><span >Finally, you can always ask to call you a car at the reception of your hotel: however, the reasonableness of the prices of the company whose services you are offered to use will remain solely on the conscience of the hotel staff.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jo3"><span >Taxi rates in Spain</span></h2>
<p><span >The cost of your trip will depend on many factors, among which the main ones are:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >a region in which the trip takes place;</span></li>
<li><span >base rate;</span></li>
<li><span >distance;</span></li>
<li><span >Times of Day;</span></li>
<li><span >car class;</span></li>
<li><span >additional services (child car seat, luggage, etc.).</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Sometimes you will have to pay extra for entry into the territory of airports, seaports, railway stations, and some other facilities. The cost of the trip can also increase due to standing in traffic jams.</span></p>
<p><span >The most popular brand of taxi cars in almost the whole country is the Taxi2Spain, and specilly in <a href="https://taxi2spain.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Madrid transfer</a>.</span><span >You can find the additional feature of taxi2spain by visiting their website here taxi2spain.com.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jo4"><span >Useful Tips</span></h2>
<p><span >As mentioned above, the loss of a license is a nightmare of taxi drivers, so there is no reason to expect obvious fraud from them because only one complaint from a passenger can cost them a career. </span></p>
<p><span >The best way is to write your destination in large letters on a piece of paper (or a mobile phone screen) in advance and show the driver when landing. If you order a taxi in advance, for example, using the Taxi2Spain service that works perfectly in Spain, then such misunderstandings will not happen at all.</span></p>
<p><span >Taxi rules in Spain are quite liberal but stricter. You can stop the car on the road almost everywhere except airports, but smoking in the passenger compartment is strictly forbidden, and you have every right to refuse to get into the vehicle passenger compartment while intoxicated.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dscqp7jo5"><span >Finally</span></h2>
<p><span >Spain has a developed and reliable taxi system. Using a taxi in Spain is practically safe, as their work is regulated by the state. Taxis operate at rates that are also determined by the state. However, they may vary slightly depending on the region. Besides, it should be noted that at night, as well as on holidays and weekends, tariffs are higher.</span></p>
<p><span >Keep in mind that not all taxi drivers in Spain speak English, so if you do not know Spanish, you should have a business card or address of your final destination with you. have a nice trip to Spain.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vegan cosmetics: features and major brands</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/vegan-cosmetics-features-and-major-brands.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/vegan-cosmetics-features-and-major-brands.html</id>

        <updated>2019-12-17T19:23:00+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/176/arolaborganic.png" alt="" />
                    In this article, we will guide you on How to check the brand for Vegan Cosmetics and which components should not be included In the past few years, the popularity&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/176/arolaborganic.png" alt="" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1dsa2u5pe0">In this article, we will guide you on How to check the brand for Vegan Cosmetics and which components should not be included</p>
<p><span >In the past few years, the popularity of brands that do not test their products on animals is growing rapidly. A study by Grand View Research showed that by 2025 the market for Vegan Cosmetics will reach $ 20.8 billion. The average annual growth rate for sales of vegan cosmetics is 6.3%. A great interest in vegan cosmetics is primarily among millennials. The reason for the growing interest in this niche was the desire of people to take care of personal health and the environment.</span></p>
<p><span >Often, ideas about vegan cosmetics are wrong. Many people think that this is only cruelty-free, but not only the ban on testing cosmetic products on animals is important here, but also the complete exclusion from the composition of products of animal origin, for example, beeswax, lanolin, and colored carmine pigment.</span></p>
<p><span >Another misconception is that vegan foods do not contain synthetic ingredients and chemicals. This is not true. Vegan brands include both herbal ingredients and synthetic ones for preservation or texture uniformity.</span></p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-find-a-perfect-developer-for-you-company.html">How to find a perfect developer for your company?</a></p>
<p><span >The phrase "vegan makeup" can cause bewilderment and even distrust. But thanks to modern technology, vegan brands are not inferior in quality and variety to others. “A few years ago, I would agree that there would be a loss in variety when choosing vegan makeup products, But the technologies and compositions improved beyond recognition.”</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dsa33mmo2"><span >How to check a best vegan brand?</span></h2>
<p><span >First, a complete list of cosmetic ingredients that are not suitable for vegans can be found on arolaborganic.com/en. Secondly, a list of best vegan brands is available at <a href="https://www.arolaborganic.com/en/" title="Vegan Beauty best website" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">vegan beauty</a>. On the packaging of cosmetics and this website of the brand have <a href="https://www.arolaborganic.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">arolab</a>, not tested on animals. You can also check the brand through the above website.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dsa3j4cja"><strong><span >Ingredients that should not be in the composition. </span></strong></h3>
<ul>
<li><span >Beeswax - may be designated as Cera alba or cera Flava</span></li>
<li><span >Carmine is a red dye derived from carmine acid, which is produced by female cochineal insects. May be labeled as carmine acid.</span></li>
<li><span >Lanolin - wool wax, animal wax obtained by digesting sheep wool. May be referred to as aliphatic alcohols, isopropyl lanceolate, planet, lanolin, lanolin alcohols, lanosterols, sterols or triterpene alcohols.</span></li>
<li><span >Glycerin - it is obtained by the saponification of animal fats. It can be found in the composition as the glyceride, glyceryl, glycret-26 or polyglycerol.</span></li>
<li><span >Honey - apis mellifera is sometimes noted.</span></li>
<li><span >Fish scales - used in cosmetics for a flicker effect. It is marked as guanine, CI 75170 or natural pearl essence.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >There are controversial components, both animal origin and derived from plants. These are elastin, keratin, and squalane. In such cases, the “veganism” of the brand is better specified using the above sources.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>WhatsApp will stop working in 2020 - Complete List of Smartphones.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/whatsapp-will-stop-working-in-2020-complete-list-of-smartphones.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/whatsapp-will-stop-working-in-2020-complete-list-of-smartphones.html</id>

        <updated>2019-12-16T22:27:40+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/175/WhatsApp-will-stop-working-in-2020-Complete-List-of-Smartphones..jpg" alt="" />
                    The developers of the WhatsApp messenger in the year 2020 refuse to support old mobile operating systems. In this article, we will guide you on which smartphones will not support&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/175/WhatsApp-will-stop-working-in-2020-Complete-List-of-Smartphones..jpg" alt="" />
                <p><span >The developers of the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/ten-things-you-did-not-know-about-whatsapp.html">WhatsApp messenger</a> in the year 2020 refuse to support old mobile operating systems. <strong>In this article, we will guide you on which smartphones will not support WhatsApp?</strong> if you are still using bellow listed Smartphones then it is confirmed that your WhatsApp will not work and it might be banned.</span></p>
<p><span >The process of banning the old operating system smartphones has two stages.<strong> First,</strong> starting January 1, 2020, WhatsApp will stop working on all Windows Phone devices. And <strong>Second</strong>, from February 1, 2020, the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-tips-to-avoid-malicious-malware-from-whatsapp.html">WhatsApp</a> messenger will not work on smartphones with Android 2.3.7 and iOS 8.</span></p>
<p><span >Here is the Complete list of Smartphones that will not be supported by WhatsApp in the year 2020.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Windows phone</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Starting January 2020, WhatsApp refuses all smartphones with Windows Phone operating system - up to the latest 8.1. These are almost all smartphones until the 2014 release. These are mainly Lumia smartphones, which were manufactured by Nokia in partnership with Microsoft.</span></p>
<p><span >Popular smartphones on <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/10-best-email-clients-for-windows-paid-and-free.html">Windows</a> Phone that will lose WhatsApp are Lumia 520, 525, 620, 625, 630, 720, 820, 920, 925, 1020, 1320. For some smartphones from this list, it is possible to install a test or unofficial build of Windows 10 Mobile, but often this firmware is unstable. </span></p>
<p><span >But WhatsApp will continue to work on all smartphones that have upgraded to <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/windows-10-new-features.html">Windows 10</a> Mobile. But Microsoft itself has already closed support for this operating system, so the messenger on these smartphones will last at best a couple more years.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>iPhone</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >WhatsApp will not work in <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/apple-card-a-credit-card-embedded-in-the-iphone.html">iPhone 4</a> and older models. That is all Apple smartphones that came out before 2011.</span></p>
<p><span >If iPhone 4S, for example, received an update to iOS 9, so WhatsApp will still work on it. As with all newer Apple smartphones.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Android</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >From February 2020, WhatsApp will no longer support all smartphones on Android 2.3.7 and older. Dozens of models that came out between 2009-2011 will be banned. Now Android 2.3 and its variations occupy a share of 0.3% of all active smartphones on Android - taking into account the total number of devices, it is about 7.5 million smartphones worldwide.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1ds7qllq30"><span >list of Andriod smartphones which will be banned of WhatsApp: </span></h2>
<p><span >WhatsApp will stop working on the first Samsung Galaxy S, Galaxy Mini, Galaxy Gio, Google Nexus One, Sony Ericsson Xperia X10, Sony Ericsson Xperia Play, LG Optimus One, HTC Wildfire S, HTC Desire, HTC Desire HD, HTC Desire Z and many other smartphones that have not updated to Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ds7qm2pk1"><span >How to use WhatsApp in old smartphones?</span></h3>
<p><span >So, what should we do next? </span><span >Yes, the answer is we can use WhatsApp in old Smartphones if we install unofficial firmware of Android 4.0 or newer. but hurry up install it before February 2020.</span></p>
<p><span >To simplify, WhatsApp support will lose the old smartphones that came out before 2011.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How To Keep Facebook&#x27;s Messenger Server Not &quot;Broken&quot; on New Year&#x27;s Eve</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-keep-facebooks-messenger-server-not-broken-on-new-years-eve.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-keep-facebooks-messenger-server-not-broken-on-new-years-eve.html</id>

        <updated>2019-12-13T21:55:09+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/174/facebook-facebook-messenger-messenger.jpg" alt="How To Keep Facebook&#x27;s Messenger Server Not &quot;Broken&quot; on New Year&#x27;s Eve" />
                    The new year 2020 is getting closer. Users of the Facebook Messenger application often send new year's wishes to others, at the moment of the new year Facebook Messenger users&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/174/facebook-facebook-messenger-messenger.jpg" alt="How To Keep Facebook&#x27;s Messenger Server Not &quot;Broken&quot; on New Year&#x27;s Eve" />
                The new year 2020 is getting closer. Users of the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/you-can-try-the-explore-section-in-the-web-version-of-facebook.html">Facebook</a> Messenger application often send new year's wishes to others, at the moment of the new year Facebook Messenger users feel difficulty to send new year wishes to their friends and relatives. As many as 1.3 billion Messenger users are known to send more messages on New Year's Eve moments, compared to normal days. Not only text messages, but the intensity of sending photos and videos has also increased many times compared to other days. <br> In this article, we will guide you on how to prevent server overload and Message sending failed problem in Facebook Messenger on new year's eve. <br>Well, related to the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-fb-messenger-in-web-browser.html">Messenger application</a>, Facebook has its way to handle huge traffic of messages sent simultaneously during New Year's Eve, so that the server is not broken, or unable to serve traffic. Knowing this, Messenger technicians also made several steps to handle traffic in the application, ahead of New Year's Eve. Here are some ways that sending messages easily in the Messenger application. <br><br>
<ol>
<li><strong>Test the server load:</strong> The technicians do server load testing. Before the New Year's Eve, Facebook had already made a simulation by sending several messages that would be received to fellow Messenger users. From here, you can see whether this time the server's ability to handle the traffic flow of the message or not. If you can't, then the allocation of messages that appear to be booming will be transferred to another server. This technique is the same as that done by the Messenger last year. On New Year's Eve 2018, the Messenger team provided an additional server to divert incoming messages to the chat application to prevent overloading on the server.</li>
<li><strong>Low-Priority Mode:</strong> Facebook has created a mechanism of "low-priority" to prevent the booming of messages that could make the server overload due to being sent simultaneously. "We have set up our system, if the server is dense, the system will start to divert traffic to low-priority mode," said Isaac Ahdout, Engineering Manager for Facebook Messenger. This low-priority mechanism will prioritize the messages sent so that they get to other users quickly.  The way this system works is by making priorities, sorting and choosing which features will be "turned off" first, to reduce server pressure and burden. For example, the read receipt feature, or a message alert that has been read, will be temporarily deactivated to increase resource allocation for messages to be sent. Then the Messenger technician can also turn off the "online" green circle, which helps ease the server load. Another example, Messenger will suspend detailed information about old messages for a while, to ease the server's CPU load. Thus, messages that go in and out will be prioritized first so they can be received quickly.</li>
<li><strong>Scheduler Feature:</strong> Messenger technicians work on a project called "scheduler". This scheduler allows the system to unify several messages whose contents are similar. Later, integration with the principle of "affinity" will ease the burden on the server, because similar messages will be sent as a group. This process, according to Isacc, will ease the CPU load, because the server receives the message sending request process only once for many collections of messages, rather than having to send it one at a time as a process.</li>
</ol>
<p>Also read: <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null">How to disable the built-in Browser in the Facebook App in the Android </a></p>
<p><strong>As a result,</strong> server latency will be reduced by a few milliseconds, so that all messages can be sent smoothly. Facebook servers are still able to handle the swirling billions of users who send messages through the application. <br> However, if the Messenger server is oversupplied due to being crammed with messages simultaneously, then one of the three things will be an alternative solution to ease the burden on the server. Plus, some technicians were on standby in several places to be ready to activate the solution related to problems that might occur ahead of the new year's eve of 2020.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to receive emails from Gmail directly in Telegram</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-receive-emails-from-gmail-directly-in-telegram.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-receive-emails-from-gmail-directly-in-telegram.html</id>

        <updated>2019-12-06T13:39:39+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/173/logo-1162901_640.png" alt="How to receive emails from Gmail directly in Telegram" />
                    Today we will tell you how to use Telegram into a full-fledged Gmail email client. Telegram is popular among many countries due to its growing scope of a regular messaging&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/173/logo-1162901_640.png" alt="How to receive emails from Gmail directly in Telegram" />
                <p><span >Today we will tell you how to use Telegram into a full-fledged Gmail email client.</span></p>
<p><span >Telegram is popular among many countries due to its growing scope of a regular <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-fb-messenger-in-web-browser.html">messaging program</a>. Nowadays it is developing an ecosystem that will replace many social networks, forums, chat rooms, and news sites. Today, here we will teach you, how to use Telegram to work with <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/the-revolution-in-email-google-inbox.html">Gmail email</a>. If you are interested to use Telegram as a Gmail email client then read below lines till the end. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1drd4hf000"><strong><span >Method to use Telegram as a Gmail email Client.</span></strong></h2>
<p><span >To make Telegram as Gmail client, you need a special bot. It is called Gmail Bot and is located here.</span></p>
<p><span >After adding the bot to the desktop, you need to authorize it in your Google account. To do this, click on the Authorize Me button. A popup with a link will appear. Clicking on it will open the authorization page in your Google account in the browser.</span></p>
<p><span >After obtaining permission, the bot will be ready to work and download all the letters from the Inbox. By default, only the short version is displayed, so click on the Show More button to download all the text. Nearby is the Actions button, with which you can reply to an email, mark it as read, delete it, and so on.</span></p>
<p>Read:<a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-tips-to-avoid-malicious-malware-from-whatsapp.html">3 Tips to Avoid Malicious Malware from Whatsapp</a></p>
<p><span >after that look at the bot settings ("Command" → Settings). Here you can configure filters with which Telegram will notify you only of those emails that are marked with special labels.</span></p>
<p><span >Gmail Bot is useful to everyone who uses Telegram as the main working tool. Now it will be possible to receive instant notifications about the necessary emails and respond to them without leaving this Telegram application.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>3 Tips To Avoid Malicious Malware from WhatsApp</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-tips-to-avoid-malicious-malware-from-whatsapp.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/3-tips-to-avoid-malicious-malware-from-whatsapp.html</id>

        <updated>2019-11-29T12:51:25+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/172/whatsapp-1789194_640.jpg" alt="" />
                    In recent times it has been viral that malware has been able to attack WhatsApp accounts around the world with just a miscall or video. The user's smartphone can be directly infected.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/172/whatsapp-1789194_640.jpg" alt="" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1dqqtigl90"><span >In recent times it has been viral that malware has been able to attack</span><strong><span > <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/ten-things-you-did-not-know-about-whatsapp.html">WhatsApp</a></span></strong><span > accounts around the world with just a miscall or video. The user's smartphone can be directly infected. Of course, this is quite terrible.</span></p>
<p><span >So, for those of you who are most likely not yet infected, what is the way to prevent it? Are there any tips so that the malware does not infect our cellphones? Here are some recommended tips.</span></p>
<p>Read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">How to use WhatsApp without a phone number.</a></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dqqtqujl4">Tips to Prevent Malicious Malware from WhatsApp</h2>
<ul>
<li id="mcetoc_1dqqtigla1"><span ><strong> Make sure the WhatsApp and OS Application is the Most Updated.</strong> </span>The first step that is easy and enough to prevent malware from infecting your cell phone is making sure <em><span >the WhatsApp application</span></em><span > installed and also your phone's operating system is the most updated because the developer certainly ensures the most optimal security in the latest version.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span ><strong>Install the Security Application.</strong> </span>The next step is to install a security application. Make sure you get it from the <strong>Google Play Store</strong> or the <strong>App Store</strong>, and before installing also make sure the developer and application name are the same. For examples like AVIRA, Malwarebytes, Norton, ESET and many others.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li id="mcetoc_1dqqtigla3"><span ><strong>Don't Open Links.</strong> </span><span >Make sure you don't click the link carelessly, especially if it's the result of a short link. If you have a good understanding of computers, especially security systems, it's better to open the link via WhatsApp Web only.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Those are some of the most effective tips for avoiding dangerous malware that enters through the WhatsApp application. It may be useful.</span></p>
<p> Next reading: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-viber-for-windows-featured-some-interesting-updates-including-video-chats.html">How to use Viber for Windows.</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to take full advantage of Black Friday</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-take-full-advange-of-black-friday.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-take-full-advange-of-black-friday.html</id>

        <updated>2019-11-25T14:50:41+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/171/How-to-take-full-advange-of-Black-Friday.png" alt="How to take full advange of Black Friday" />
                    In this article, we will give you 5 important reasons to love Black Friday and plan your budget to get full advantage of this year's Black Friday. Because on Black&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/171/How-to-take-full-advange-of-Black-Friday.png" alt="How to take full advange of Black Friday" />
                <p><span >In this article, we will give you <strong>5 important reasons to love Black Friday and plan your budget to get full advantage of this year's Black Friday.</strong> Because on Black Friday The most significant sale of the year begins, Black Friday is here again. Do not miss the opportunity to take advantage of the best offers and make a lot of successful purchases. Black Friday is more than just a holiday for discounts.</span></p>
<p><span > Want to know why we love to buy on Black Friday so much?</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj0"><span >5 Reasons to Buy on Black Friday</span></h2>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj1"><span >1. "Black Friday" - a day of crazy discounts</span></h3>
<p><span >Black Friday is the long-awaited day of the year for many shopping enthusiasts. And when is the most anticipated sale of the year? In the United States, Black Friday immediately comes after Thanksgiving. </span><strong><span >This year, Black Friday on November 29th.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >Black Friday begins the traditional Christmas season for discounts. But it is on Black Friday that </span><strong><span >many shopping centers and supermarkets arrange huge sales for their customers.</span></strong><span > If you have been looking at some product for some time, then this day is the best time to finally purchase this item at the best price. However, you should plan everything - “Black Friday” offers truly breathtaking discounts, and we do not recommend “yawning”, otherwise you might get ahead.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj2"><span >2. "Black Friday" - time for sales in online stores</span></h3>
<p><span >Are you annoyed by the "<a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/your-content-marketing-strategies-decide-search-results-for-business.html">flea market</a>" in shopping centers? If so, "Black Friday" is your chance, because on this day in many online stores you can find a lot of profitable offers. In the case of purchasing goods online, you do not need to go to shopping centers crowded with visitors and stand in long lines. </span><strong><span >On the Internet, you have the opportunity to calmly and leisurely compare products with each other and then make a meaningful decision. </span></strong><span >Also, you do not run the risk of falling and being trampled by a rampant crowd of people chasing cheap goods.</span></p>
<p><span >And if you are truly a true fan of online shopping, you might want to wait a few days. </span><strong><span >Cyber ​​Monday, the day when millions and millions of people make bargains over the Internet,</span></strong><span > follows immediately the weekend after Black Friday. At Cyber ​​Monday, online stores arrange discounts and sales for their customers, similar to Black Friday <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/brandbucket-marketplace-of-premium-domain-names-for-sale.html">discounts and sales</a>. Online fever lasts longer than regular, store-based fever.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj3"><span >3. "Black Friday" - a great opportunity to buy everything you need for Christmas</span></h3>
<p><span >Are you one of those who always buy Christmas presents at the very last moment? If so, then we don’t envy you - you not only spend the best part of your holidays in this unpleasant “flea market”, but also </span><strong><span >spend much more time, money and nerves on buying gifts.</span></strong><span > If you wholeheartedly hate Christmas shopping, maybe it's time to change something.</span></p>
<p><span >Buy everything you need to celebrate Christmas on Black Friday - it’s beneficial on all sides! Perhaps, in this case, you will not be able to escape the crowd (unless, of course, you make purchases online), but </span><strong><span >you can purchase the goods you need at the best prices.</span></strong><span > Having bought everything in advance, you will get much more pleasure from the festive weeks, since you will not need to run around the shops and buy gifts at the very last minute.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj4"><span >4. Black Friday lasts longer than any other Friday.</span></h3>
<p><span >Do you enjoy shopping late at night? Do you love shopping at the most unusual time of the day? If so, then Black Friday is undoubtedly the best event for you. It allows you to </span><strong><span >go shopping at the most unusual times.</span></strong></p>
<p><span >On Black Friday, many stores open very early in the morning and close late in the evening. In the past few years, the most anticipated Sale of the Year starts immediately after midnight and ends at midnight the next day, allowing shoppers</span><strong><span > to enjoy shopping all 24 hours.</span></strong><span > If you are fit, you can spend the whole day walking around the malls. In this case, you can take advantage of the best deals and discounts that are offered to customers on this day.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1dqgeeepj5"><span >5. "Black Friday" - the day when truly strange events occur</span></h3>
<p><span >“Black Friday” always breaks records. below we will cover, why this day is the most popular among shopping enthusiasts. During the weekend of “Black Friday” in 2012, a record was set for the number of customers and the amount of money spent - </span><strong><span >247 million people went through all the stores, and the total amount spent on purchases amounted to almost $ 60 billion!</span></strong></p>
<p><span >Black Friday is known for many unpleasant incidents. Often on this day, people fight over goods, there were even cases when people shot at each other because in front of the store someone did not have enough free parking space. There are also incidents when people brought a gun, two knives, and a grenade to the store during Black Friday. Yes, indeed good discounts are expensive.</span></p>
<p>Read next: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/getresponse-one-stop-shop-for-marketers.html">GetResponse - One Stop Shop for Marketers </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Apple Card, a Credit Card Embedded in the iPhone</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/apple-card-a-credit-card-embedded-in-the-iphone.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/apple-card-a-credit-card-embedded-in-the-iphone.html</id>

        <updated>2019-11-20T08:01:38+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/170/Apple-Credit-Cards.PNG" alt="Apple Credit Card 7 features you need to know." />
                    Apple recently introduced its new product, Apple Card, which is a credit card that can be accessed with or without a card. Apple is working with Goldman Sachs Bank for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/170/Apple-Credit-Cards.PNG" alt="Apple Credit Card 7 features you need to know." />
                <p><span ><strong>Apple</strong> recently introduced its new product, Apple Card, which is a <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/types-of-credit-debit-cards-how-to-get-prepaid-visa-and-mastercard-cards.html">credit card</a> that can be accessed with or without a card. Apple is working with Goldman Sachs Bank for the credit card. Reporting from CNBC. The privilege of this card is that users can register through their iPhone and can directly access the card within minutes. </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dq3b9kcc8"><span >Apple Credit Card 7 features you need to know.</span></h2>
<ol>
<li><span ><strong>Usage Credit Card: </strong>This card can be used through Apple Pay which has been operating since 2014. On its official page, Apple writes "Apple Card lives on your iPhone in a <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-create-your-money-making-mobile-application.html">digital wallet application</a>, and it makes new things possible. You can register at any time and can immediately start using it with Apple Pay. "</span></li>
<li><span ><strong>Titanium Card:</strong> If payment is not accepted by Apple Pay, there is a minimalist titanium card that looks slim. On that card, only your name is written without other personal information. For every payment, you get Daily Cash. </span></li>
<li><span ><strong>Schedule Fees: </strong>The card also allows users to manage expenses and rewards through the iPhone Wallet application. Apple ensures there are no fees, including late fees, international fees, or annual fees. "Even if you miss payments, we won't charge a penalty fee as most banks do," said Apple executive Jennifer Bailey.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Transparency of Apple Credit Card:</span></strong><span > Apple's goal is to make customers easier to balance payments, rather than complicate things. It also heralded the simplicity and transparency of this card. For example, Apple will use maps and services to list purchase activities in a way that is easy to understand, instead of merchant codes that sometimes make credit card statements difficult to understand. Purchases are grouped in color-coded categories, such as food, entertainment, and others. Expenditure trends are also displayed for several weeks or months.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Payment Options of Apple Credit Card: </span></strong><span >Payment options are displayed dynamically, so users can decide how fast users want to pay their bills. Annual interest rates will range from 13-24 percent.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Privacy and Security of Apple Credit Card: </span></strong><span >Apple also emphasizes the aspects of privacy and security. The tech giant ensures that no one knows what you are buying, where you are buying it, or how much you are paying for it. It said the analysis for expenditures was carried out on devices, not on Apple servers. Goldman Sachs also will not sell purchase data to third parties. In addition, Apple Card uses a special security chip to store card numbers and every transaction has a one time password (OTP). The other layer of security also features a face identification and fingerprint scanner on the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-migrate-from-iphone-to-android-and-android-to-iphone.html">iPhone</a>.</span></li>
<li><strong><span >Hardware, software, and services</span></strong><span >. Apple is uniquely positioned to make the most significant changes in the credit card experience in 50 years. Apple Pay is accepted by more than 70 percent of US retailers and will take effect in more than 40 countries by the end of the year. This service is expected to exceed 10 billion transactions this year.</span></li>
</ol>
<p> Read next: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/tips-to-change-ringtones-of-iphone-6.html">Tips to change ringtone of iPhone 6.</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/personal-digital-assistant-cortana-will-leave-from-android-and-ios-beginning-2020.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/personal-digital-assistant-cortana-will-leave-from-android-and-ios-beginning-2020.html</id>

        <updated>2019-11-19T07:43:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." />
                    Cortana has been present in the form of applications for Android and iOS users in several countries. However, soon the digital assistant software will leave from both platforms. Cortana services&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." />
                <p><strong>Cortana</strong> has been present in the form of applications for <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/smartphones-2/" title="More Articles About SmartPhones ">Android</a> and iOS users in several countries. However, soon the digital assistant software will leave from both platforms. Cortana services for Android and iOS will be stopped from January 31, 2020.</p>
<p>The reason was revealed by Microsoft as the maker of Cortana in a statement on an <a href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/4531683" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">official website</a>. "To make Cortana useful, we integrate Cortana into Microsoft 365 and part of this change is to stop supporting Cortana applications on Android and iOS," Microsoft wrote.</p>
<p><img class="post__image align-right" src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/169/Personal-Digital-Assistant-Cortana-will-leave-from-Android-and-iOS-Beginning-2020..jpg" alt="Personal Digital Assistant Cortana will leave from Android and iOS Beginning 2020." width="568" height="335"></p>
<p class="msg msg--info"><em>Image Credit: Flickr: <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dcmot/22786860142" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Bolly Holly Baba</a></em></p>
<p><strong>Cortana</strong> for Android and iOS will be deactivated in a number of countries, including the United Kingdom, Canada, and Australia. Later it was known that Germany, Mexico, China, and Spain would be affected. Nevertheless, it is still unclear what about Cortana's fate on Android and iOS devices in other regions, such as the United States. It is also not certain whether Cortana will also be turned off completely on Android and iOS or will continue to be used after January 31, 2020.</p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">How to use WhatsApp without phone Number.</a><br><br>In addition, Cortana will also disappear from Microsoft's Android Launcher after the end of January next year in the countries mentioned above.</p>
<p><br>Microsoft first introduced Cortana for iOS and Android in 2015 to connect Windows 10 PCs with smartphones. Unfortunately, despite a number of an overhaul, Cortana still can not compete with competitors' digital assistants, such as Alexa or Google Assistant.</p>
<p>Read next: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html">5 Important Reasons to use Android Emularor</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-reasons-to-use-android-emulator.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-22T08:46:37+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/168/5-Important-Reasons-to-use-Android-Emulator.jpg" alt="5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator" />
                    Nowadays, users have preferred to use mobile devices to desktop PCs. Surfing on the Internet is one of the most popular activities for which it is not necessary to sit&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/168/5-Important-Reasons-to-use-Android-Emulator.jpg" alt="5 Important Reasons to use Android Emulator" />
                <p><span >Nowadays, users have preferred to use mobile devices to desktop PCs. Surfing on the Internet is one of the most popular activities for which it is not necessary to sit in front of a computer or laptop. People publish status on social networks and launch games through their phone.</span></p>
<p><span >In this context, using Android emulators to play mobile games or run an application on a computer may seem counterintuitive. But in fact, the number of people using Android emulators is increasing. Why? Let's look at <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-important-factors-to-consider-before-buying-a-speaker.html">5 reasons</a> why a user may need to use an Android Emulator on their PC.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln70"><span >1. Android emulator gives you a bigger screen</span></h2>
<p><span >Keeping a close eye on your phone harms your eye. This is certainly not very good for your health. Moving from a small screen of a telephone to a large screen of a computer raises its head, also, the <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-fix-blue-screen-problem-of-microsoft-windows.html">large screen has a better display</a>. This greatly improves your accuracy when pressed in games.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln81"><span >2. Saving the mobile phone battery</span></h2>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/take-photo-from-your-smartphone-and-earn-money.html">Cell phone</a> batteries are small and lightweight for portability, but this also means that they cannot last very long. Powerful games heat-up your phone and the battery runs down very quickly. No one wants to lose the battle because your phone is down and disconnected at the very last moment. Using the Android emulator, you never have to worry about power. You can watch videos or stay <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-best-smartphone-to-optimize-your-gaming-experience.html">connected in your favorite game</a> for as long as you need.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln92"><span >3. Launch multiple applications or use multiple accounts at the same time.</span></h2>
<p><span >Imagine that you could watch a video in any video sharing application without interrupting your <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-use-whatsapp-without-a-phone-number.html">conversation on WhatsApp</a> or using multiple accounts for the game at the same time. That's fine, isn't it? Although not all Android emulators have this feature, with Nox App Player you can simultaneously run multiple instances of Android on your PC screen. Control your game in one of them, watch the video on the other and watch the conversation on WhatsApp on one big screen! </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln93"><span >4. The emulator allows you to replace the top-end Android phone</span></h2>
<p><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/tips-on-choosing-a-tablet-and-smartphone-to-play-games.html">Mobile games</a> are not just casual games. More and more hardcore games appear with a deep plot and complex gameplay. Accordingly, for a smooth and fast game, the graphics and display of the top device are required. The Android emulator will save you the budget to replace your phone since you can get for free this most “virtual, top-end Android phone” on your PC.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dlbgjln94"><span >5. Access to mobile applications from a PC</span></h2>
<p><span >With the growing number of smartphones and mobile networks, many applications meet the specific needs of people. However, some of them, such as Instagram, are designed to work only on mobile devices. For people who would like to access these services in a more “traditional” way from a PC, an Android emulator is a great solution.</span></p>
<p><span >So you want to try the Android emulator? Download Nox App Player to take full advantage of the benefits mentioned above.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
