<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>The Tricks Peak - Blog About Blogging, Technology and Reviews</title>
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com" />
    <updated>2020-09-30T10:17:45+05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>A Little Bit info Of History About Insurance in America</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/a-little-bit-info-of-history-about-insurance-in-america.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/a-little-bit-info-of-history-about-insurance-in-america.html</id>

        <updated>2020-09-30T10:16:15+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/221/american-flag-795303_640.jpg" alt="A Little Bit info Of History About Insurance in America" />
                    It was one among the founding fathers, Franklin , who formed the primary insurance firm in 1751, called Philadelphia Contributionship, and it had been home/fire insurance. consistent with PBS reports, 143 policies were issued by the corporate within the first year, and none of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/221/american-flag-795303_640.jpg" alt="A Little Bit info Of History About Insurance in America" />
                It was <span class="rcolor4" >one among </span>the founding fathers, <span class="rcolor5" >Franklin </span>, who formed <span class="rcolor6" >the primary </span><span class="rcolor1" >insurance firm </span>in 1751, called Philadelphia Contributionship, and <span class="rcolor2" >it had been </span>home/fire insurance. <span class="rcolor3" >consistent with </span>PBS reports, 143 policies were issued by <span class="rcolor4" >the corporate </span><span class="rcolor5" >within the </span>first year, and none of the insured property caught fire for seven years afterwards. In fact, Philadelphia used <span class="rcolor6" >an equivalent </span>scheme <span class="rcolor1" >that each one </span><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/insurance-tips/">insurance</a> companies use today; the members of <span class="rcolor2" >the corporate </span>paid an amount <span class="rcolor3" >of cash </span><span class="rcolor4" >that might </span>be <span class="rcolor5" >wont to </span>restore <span class="rcolor6" >loss </span><span class="rcolor1" >thanks to </span>fire-related causes. Such payment is popularly known today as <span class="rcolor2" >premium </span>. <span class="rcolor3" >Franklin </span>played <span class="rcolor4" >a big </span>role in developing insurance indeed, but he <span class="rcolor5" >wasn't </span><span class="rcolor6" >the primary </span>to introduce auto insurance. As a matter of fact, <span class="rcolor1" >the primary </span>car insurer's venture began <span class="rcolor2" >a touch </span><span class="rcolor3" >before </span>Benjamin Franklin's time.<br>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1ejemol750">The First Known Automotive Insurance in America</h2>
<p>People now see <span class="rcolor5" >automobile insurance </span>as an inevitable <span class="rcolor6" >a part of </span>everyday lives <span class="rcolor1" >just because </span>car <span class="rcolor2" >is that the </span>most-popular means of transportation <span class="rcolor3" >within the </span>country. Insurer provides essential financial protection <span class="rcolor4" >for each </span>vehicle owner <span class="rcolor5" >within the </span>event of an accident that causes property damages, casualties, medical conditions, <span class="rcolor6" >and every one </span>possible financial losses. In America, Detroit is nowadays well-known for its automobile industries. During the late nineteenth to early twentieth century, Ohio was home for innovators of this new <span class="rcolor1" >sort of </span>transportation. <span class="rcolor2" >it's </span>worth mentioning that the world's first <span class="rcolor3" >automobile insurance </span>coverage policy was issued in Dayton, Ohio in 1987. <span class="rcolor4" >consistent with </span>Ohio Historical Society, Gilbert J. Loomis was <span class="rcolor5" >the primary </span>person <span class="rcolor6" >to get </span>car auto <span class="rcolor1" >insurance </span>. The policy provided protection for Loomis in terms <span class="rcolor2" >of monetary </span>loss (or financial responsibility) <span class="rcolor3" >just in case </span>his car damaged another person's properties, killed, or injured someone. These policies are more or less <span class="rcolor4" >almost like </span>those used widely by modern <span class="rcolor5" >automobile insurance </span>companies throughout America nowadays; <span class="rcolor6" >a minimum of </span>, the policies issued to Loomis set <span class="rcolor1" >samples of </span>what <span class="rcolor2" >quite </span>financial protection that <span class="rcolor3" >automobile insurance </span>policy should <span class="rcolor4" >a minimum of </span>provide for the owner.</p>
<p>read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-does-life-insurance-do-for-a-car-loan.html">What does life insurance do for a car loan</a><br><br>The <span class="rcolor5" >automobile insurance </span>industry slowly began <span class="rcolor6" >to realize </span>its popularity since then, and it indeed developed into more comprehensive <span class="rcolor1" >also </span>. In 1902, <span class="rcolor2" >the primary </span>comprehensive <span class="rcolor3" >policy </span>provided coverage for fire and theft, so <span class="rcolor4" >it had been </span><span class="rcolor5" >not </span>for accident-related causes only, <span class="rcolor6" >consistent with </span>International Risk Management Institute. In 1912, <span class="rcolor1" >coverage </span>that combined multiple perils was <span class="rcolor2" >beginning to </span>develop as insurers tried <span class="rcolor3" >to incorporate </span>fire, property, and liability coverage for automobile into one single policy. Auto <span class="rcolor4" >coverage </span>policies evolved greatly, but <span class="rcolor5" >the essential </span>principles remain <span class="rcolor6" >an equivalent </span>. <span class="rcolor1" >Franklin </span><span class="rcolor2" >didn't </span>probably <span class="rcolor3" >believe </span>cars when he started Philadelphia Contribution-ship, but he played <span class="rcolor4" >an important </span>role in developing the system and popularize <span class="rcolor5" >the thought </span>that insurance does bring peace of mind to the policyholder.<br>With <span class="rcolor6" >the increase </span>of <span class="rcolor1" >the car </span>industry in America, insurance also began its expansion. There are many factors involved <span class="rcolor2" >within the </span>success story of car manufacturing <span class="rcolor3" >like </span>expansion of U.S. economy, infrastructure and road development, <span class="rcolor4" >and therefore the </span>rise of "car culture" itself <span class="rcolor5" >within the </span>country. Of course, the <span class="rcolor6" >rapid climb </span><span class="rcolor1" >of auto </span>production and number of car owners <span class="rcolor2" >within the </span>country inevitably resulted <span class="rcolor3" >in additional </span>road cars and accidents.<br><br>In 1930, <span class="rcolor4" >quite </span>100 people were killed in accidents per day. <span class="rcolor5" >it's </span>not a surprising fact since drivers at <span class="rcolor6" >that point </span><span class="rcolor1" >weren't </span>obliged to undergo strict driver licensing, <span class="rcolor2" >and doubtless </span>most of them were never registered to any driver test. This was, in fact, an expected consequence <span class="rcolor3" >thanks to </span>the absence of driver test or driving schools. In 1920s, <span class="rcolor4" >thanks to </span>various political reactions, <span class="rcolor5" >the govt </span>invested more funds <span class="rcolor6" >to create </span>better roads and <span class="rcolor1" >control </span>system <span class="rcolor2" >also </span>as improve vehicle licensing regulation and implement strict driver test. Massachusetts was a step <span class="rcolor3" >before </span>most states by establishing driver licensing in 1903; however, the state only <span class="rcolor4" >began to </span>implement driver licensing in 1952.</p>
<p>read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-health-insurance-work.html">How does health insurance work</a><br><br>Massachusetts and Connecticut were ahead again with the implementation of compulsory insurance and financial responsibility laws. To be more precise, Connecticut's law required driver or vehicle owner <span class="rcolor5" >to supply </span>valid proof <span class="rcolor6" >of monetary </span>responsibility of <span class="rcolor1" >a minimum of </span>$10,000 <span class="rcolor2" >just in case </span>one is involved in an accident that resulted <span class="rcolor3" >in additional </span>than $100 worth of damages, injury, medical bills, or when the accident caused the death. Back then, drivers were obliged to what was stated by the law after their first-time accident.<br><br>In 1950s, <span class="rcolor4" >automobile insurance </span>began to spread widely across <span class="rcolor5" >the state </span>in <span class="rcolor6" >most </span>states. Massachusetts was <span class="rcolor1" >the sole </span>states <span class="rcolor2" >within the </span>country that required drivers <span class="rcolor3" >to get </span><span class="rcolor4" >automobile insurance </span>policy before vehicle registration. In 1956, <span class="rcolor5" >ny </span>adopted <span class="rcolor6" >an equivalent </span>regulation; North Carolina took <span class="rcolor1" >an equivalent </span>step <span class="rcolor2" >within the </span>following year. During 1960s and 1970s, <span class="rcolor3" >most </span>states developed <span class="rcolor4" >an equivalent </span><span class="rcolor5" >sort of </span>regulation although each state has different specific requirements. Considering that <span class="rcolor6" >the start </span>of compulsory insurance law was in 1925, and <span class="rcolor1" >it had been </span>successfully applied throughout <span class="rcolor2" >the state </span>by 1970s, <span class="rcolor3" >the event </span>is staggeringly quick.<br><br>Nowadays, <span class="rcolor4" >automobile insurance </span>[http://carinsuranceestimate.org] evolved into <span class="rcolor5" >one among </span>the most-profitable industries <span class="rcolor6" >within the </span>world <span class="rcolor1" >because of </span><span class="rcolor2" >the many </span>help from <span class="rcolor3" >the web </span>.</p>
<p>Article source: <a href="https://ezinearticles.com/?A-Little-Bit-Of-History-About-Insurance-in-America&amp;id=8667035" rel="nofollow">ezinearticles.com</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What does life insurance do for a car loan</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-does-life-insurance-do-for-a-car-loan.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/what-does-life-insurance-do-for-a-car-loan.html</id>

        <updated>2020-09-28T00:19:55+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/220/house-5264830_640.jpg" alt="What does life insurance do for a car loan" />
                    As Car loans are one of the most popular types of loans. However, when completing such a procedure, in addition to standard banking requirements, some conditions must be met. One&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/220/house-5264830_640.jpg" alt="What does life insurance do for a car loan" />
                <p><span >As Car loans are one of the most popular types of loans. However, when completing such a procedure, in addition to standard banking requirements, some conditions must be met. One of them is car <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/insurance-tips/">insurance</a>, the second is life and health insurance with a car loan. This is an additional requirement of banks to provide guarantees of timely repayment of all debts under any circumstances, even if the lender has serious health problems.</span></p>
<p><span >This trend is becoming more widespread in banking practice. According to law, life insurance when buying a vehicle in installments is not a prerequisite. However, in reality, getting a car loan without life insurance is becoming more and more difficult.</span></p>
<p><span >What is the difference between this type of insurance and traditional insurance? In this case, the insurance contract is drawn up once for the entire duration of the credit contract. It does not need to be renewed once a year until the car loan is paid off.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1ej8fmpa30"><span >What does life insurance do for a car loan?</span></h2>
<ul>
<li><span >The right to fully or partially repay the debt under the loan agreement in the event of unforeseen health situations (complete or partial disability or death of the client);</span></li>
<li><span >Protection of the material interests of not only the insured person, but also close relatives (especially if the borrowed person is the only breadwinner in the family);</span></li>
<li><span >In the event of early repayment of the loan debt, the life insurance policy continues for the period for which it was concluded.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Life insurance increases the likelihood that a financial institution will issue a loan. In some banks, the absence of such a policy from a potential client is a reason for refusing to issue a loan, because working with problem debts significantly reduces the bank's profit. In this case, the credit manager has every right not to sign the client's application, without even explaining the reasons for the negative answer.</span></p>
<p><span >Life insurance is the confidence that the client will return the funds in full and within the period specified in the contract. On the Internet, you can find a lot of information on how to opt out of life insurance for a car loan. If a citizen is firmly confident in his material capabilities and is convinced that he does not need such a service, he has every right to refuse insurance. To do this, you need to fill out the appropriate application form to the bank. After that, the manager will consider it and make a decision.</span></p>
<p><span >You need to be ready to refuse to issue a loan or a loan on less favorable terms with higher interest rates. Thus, car insurance insurance in practice is not an additional cost for the client, but, on the contrary, serves as the basis for reducing the cost of the loan. This is a common practice in banking. The financial institution raises the rate when the risk increases and lowers it when the threats of non-payment diminish.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1ej8fmpa31"><span >The cost of the policy for a car loan</span></h2>
<p><span >The amount of premiums for life insurance for car loans depends on the size of the loan. However, as a rule, it is no more than 0.1%.</span></p>
<p><span >At the same time, both parties to the transaction: both the bank and the borrower will remain in the black. The first will receive compensation in the amount of the outstanding loan balance, the second will remain the full owner of the car.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ej8fmpa32"><span >How does customer protection work?</span></h3>
<p><span >Suppose that an insured event occurs, as a result of which the citizen has lost his health and, as a result, will not be able to fulfill his professional duties, receive income and pay off the loan debt. In this case, the insurance organization pays the bank the remaining amount of the debt under the loan agreement, protecting the interests of its client. In this case, the vehicle taken on credit remains in the possession of the borrower.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ej8fmpa33"><span >Final Words</span></h3>
<p><span >Life and health insurance for a car loan is not a prerequisite. However, this service should not be neglected, because it is beneficial not only to the bank, but also to the borrower. Having such insurance on hand, you can count on a positive answer to the issuance of a loan, on the one hand, on the other hand, it will serve as reliable protection for the payment of all financial obligations to the bank. By purchasing a life insurance program, you maintain your financial independence and stability.</span></p>
<p>Also read:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-does-health-insurance-work.html">How does health insurance works</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/why-do-i-need-travel-insurance.html">Why do I need travel insurance </a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/small-and-medium-business-insurance.html">Small and meduium Business Insurance </a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two Easiest Ways to Transfer WhatsApp Conversations to Another Phone</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/two-easiest-ways-to-transfer-whatsapp-conversations-to-another-phone.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/two-easiest-ways-to-transfer-whatsapp-conversations-to-another-phone.html</id>

        <updated>2020-09-19T08:40:57+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/219/whatsapp-interface-1660652_640.png" alt="Two Easiest Ways to Transfer WhatsApp Conversations to Another Phone" />
                    If you just log in to an existing WhatsApp account on a new device, the history from the old device will not load. Now you will learn 2 ways to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/219/whatsapp-interface-1660652_640.png" alt="Two Easiest Ways to Transfer WhatsApp Conversations to Another Phone" />
                <p><span >If you just log in to an existing WhatsApp account on a new device, the history from the old device will not load. Now you will learn 2 ways to solve this problem and continue communication from exactly where you left off, without unnecessary difficulties.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eii719id0"><span >Option 1: Using Google Drive</span></h2>
<p><span >WhatsApp has the ability to make a copy and save it to Google Drive. This feature is ideal for transferring chats to your new device:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span >Before you "move" to a new phone, open the WhatsApp application, and tap on the three dots icon.</span></li>
<li><span >Go to Settings&gt; Conversations&gt; Chat Backup.</span></li>
<li><span >In the next window, you can manually select individual chats or configure the creation of a backup copy of conversations automatically at any frequency. Now when you install this application on your new smartphone, the messenger will offer to “get” chats and files from Google Drive.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span >This is the most convenient and fastest way to transfer correspondence to another phone.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eii719ie1"><span >Option 2: Create a copy of chats manually</span></h2>
<p><strong><span >For those who do not use Google Drive, a different method is suitable:</span></strong></p>
<ol>
<li><span >Settings&gt; Chats &amp; Calls&gt; Copy Chats.</span></li>
<li><span >Save a copy to a memory card if your smartphone supports it.</span></li>
<li><span >Take out the SD card, insert it into the prepared smartphone, restore chats.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><strong><span >What to do for smartphone users without a memory card:</span></strong></p>
<ol>
<li><span >Take a USB cable and connect your device to your PC / laptop.</span></li>
<li><span >Find the WhatsApp / Database smartphone folder on your PC or laptop. A previously saved copy is located here. The searched file looks something like this: "msgstore-2020-04-28.db.crypt".</span></li>
<li><span >Transfer the file with the required data to your computer to any convenient folder.</span></li>
<li><span >Now install WhatsApp, </span><strong><span >but don't open the app!</span></strong></li>
<li><span >Connect a new smartphone to a PC or laptop via a USB cable. The WhatsApp / Databases directory should have appeared already. If not, create the folder yourself.</span></li>
<li><span >Transfer the file with the backup copy of your chats to it.</span></li>
<li><span >Only now can WhatsApp be launched.</span></li>
<li><span >The screen should display a message stating that a copy of the chats was found - click "Restore".</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span >After a couple of seconds, the chat history will be loaded on the new smartphone.</span></p>
<p> Read:<a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-connect-airpods-to-android.html"> How to connect AirPods to Android </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Running out of disk space? where is the best place to store photos, films, and programs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/running-out-of-disk-space-where-is-the-best-place-to-store-photos-films-and-programs.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/running-out-of-disk-space-where-is-the-best-place-to-store-photos-films-and-programs.html</id>

        <updated>2020-09-01T20:57:14+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/218/hard-disk-4255711_640.jpg" alt="Running out of disk space? where is the best place to store photos, films, and programs" />
                    Each of us is once faced with the fact that the hard disk space is running out, you need to store them somewhere. It is also better not to fill&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/218/hard-disk-4255711_640.jpg" alt="Running out of disk space? where is the best place to store photos, films, and programs" />
                <p><span >Each of us is once faced with the fact that the hard disk space is running out, you need to store them somewhere. It is also better not to fill the hard disk so that the system does not slow down.</span></p>
<p><span >In general, there are 3 options for storing files: burn to DVDs, store in the cloud, or purchase an external hard drive.</span></p>
<p><span >I will say right away: you should not save the distributions of the programs, because the programs are changing, updated and it is better to download them again from the Internet. Now the time has passed when the programs were stored for several years.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >Let's look at each case</span></strong></p>
<p><strong><span >1. Burning to DVD</span></strong><span > is a cheap option, but inconvenient because when you need something, you will need to search for a disc. Also, the disc is easily damaged and scratched, so the reliability is not very good here. The good thing about this method is that it is very inexpensive. And perhaps that's all.</span></p>
<p><strong><span >2. Store in the cloud. </span></strong><span >Many cloud services give you disk space for a price. There are two disadvantages here: a constant subscription fee, as well as the risk that the disk on the server will simply burn out.</span></p>
<p><span >And in the contract for such services, it is written in black and white that the organization is not responsible for failures in work. And of course, you need a powerful Internet channel to upload and download your wealth, and your account can be broken and all your files can become public. In the cloud, I store those files that I need constant access from different devices. It is very convenient!</span></p>
<p><strong><span >3. The best way</span></strong><span > is an external HDD hard drive. In my opinion, the most reliable. How to choose it? There are two factors here: capacity and reviews. I always choose according to reviews and try to take those models that have already received the proper number of ratings from real users (I don't make new models, I take from a year).</span></p>
<p><span >You should not buy a 2 terabyte disk at once, it is better to buy two disks per terabyte or 500 gigabytes each. One to use as a backup. After all, the more places where information will be recorded, the more likely it will be saved. The external drive is easily connected via USB, and in the "This PC" section it appears as a regular hard drive.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-connect-airpods-to-android.html">How to connect AirPods to Android </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to connect AirPods to Android</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-connect-airpods-to-android.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-connect-airpods-to-android.html</id>

        <updated>2020-08-24T20:29:27+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/217/How-to-connect-AirPods-to-Android.png" alt="How to connect AirPods to Android" />
                    Almost every person uses wireless headphones now, as it is convenient. For example, without additional cables, you can listen to music or podcasts while walking, cycling, or just jogging. Headsets&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/217/How-to-connect-AirPods-to-Android.png" alt="How to connect AirPods to Android" />
                <p><strong><span >Almost every person uses wireless headphones now, as it is convenient. For example, without additional cables, you can listen to music or podcasts while walking, cycling, or just jogging. Headsets from various manufacturers are available for sale, but AirPods are the most popular. Because the manufacturer of these headphones is Apple, many people have an understandable question: how to connect AirPods to Android. It's very simple, you don't even have to install additional applications and perform complex actions!</span></strong></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eggggve30"><span >How to connect AirPods to Android phones?</span></h2>
<p><span >It is necessary to make a reservation that AirPods are ordinary wireless headphones that connect to a device via Bluetooth. And here it doesn't matter what operating system is installed on your smartphone or tablet. So it is possible to pair the Apple headset with an Android phone and through the standard settings options. We have compiled step-by-step instructions, so we recommend that you familiarize yourself with it:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span >Open the smart phone settings.</span></li>
<li><span >Go to the "Bluetooth" section and move the slider to the right next to the corresponding item. You can also activate the option through the quick access shutter by opening it, and then clicking on the icon with the logo of the desired mode.</span></li>
<li><span >We open the case where the AirPods themselves are located. Note that before starting pairing, the headphones must be returned to the case if you removed them from there before. </span></li>
<li><span >On the back of the case, we find an almost invisible button. It is easy to feel it. We hold it down, and then we wait a few seconds until the white or green indicator lights up. It all depends on what generation your headset is.</span></li>
<li><span >We return to the phone, or rather to the "Bluetooth" tab. Refreshing the page and see that the name of Apple headphones has appeared on the list with available devices. Click on it to perform pairing. If the connection is made for the first time, then in the window that appears, you will need to select "Accept".</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span >And that's it, now you can listen to music through AirPods connected to your Android smartphone. Here the principle of action is standard - click on the desired track and adjust the volume. You can also chat on the phone, record voice messages, and use other features of the wireless headset. But several nuances should be paid attention to.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eggggve41"><span >Features of using AirPods with Android</span></h2>
<p><span >As you know, AirPods are primarily designed for Apple smartphones, so Android phone owners may face certain restrictions. Firstly, the Siri voice assistant will be completely inaccessible, but you can use the rest of the assistants, but only after additional configuration.</span></p>
<p><span >Secondly, if you take the earpiece out of your ear, the melody will continue to play. To stop a track, you need to manually open the player on your smartphone, and then press the pause button. But this flaw can be fixed by installing the AndroPods app. It allows you to customize the wireless headset in detail, including turning on the display of the charge in the status bar and activating some gestures.</span></p>
<p><span >So, we took a quick look at how to connect AirPods to Android correctly. As practice shows, it is almost always possible to pair with headphones the first time. If you still have additional questions, then ask them in the comments. We will try to answer them and help you solve the problem!</span></p>
<p>Read Also: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-reasons-to-move-from-word-to-google-docs.html">5 reason to move from Word to Google Doc</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 reasons to move from Word to Google Docs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-reasons-to-move-from-word-to-google-docs.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-reasons-to-move-from-word-to-google-docs.html</id>

        <updated>2020-08-16T13:51:01+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/216/Google-Docs.png" alt="5 reasons to move from Word to Google Docs" />
                    In this article, I have collected 5 reasons that, will make you think about using Google Doc. You need to compare Google Dox not even with Word (a program for&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/216/Google-Docs.png" alt="5 reasons to move from Word to Google Docs" />
                <p><span >In this article, I have collected 5 reasons that, will make you think about using Google Doc.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1efr74bk40"><span >Google Docs is free</span></h2>
<p><span >You need to compare Google Dox not even with Word (a program for a computer), but with the Office 365 service. As you know, there the subscription is paid monthly or for a year.</span></p>
<p><span >You don't have to pay anything at Google Doc. Except when there are a lot of files on your Disk. Then you will have to buy additional space. But filling 15 GB of free space with texts is a difficult problem, you are unlikely to succeed.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1efr74bk41"><span >Google Docs is easy to use through a browser</span></h2>
<p><span >To be fair, I note that Microsoft Office now has an online editor. If you have a Microsoft account, you can safely edit your texts online.</span></p>
<p><span >But the functionality of Microsoft's online editor will unpleasantly surprise fans of a text editor for the Word computer. Many features have been removed. Others work with limitations.</span></p>
<p><span >In Google Dox, the functionality is the same everywhere: on a computer, on a phone, on a tablet. You can launch a regular browser and use the service without installing any programs.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1efr74bk42"><span >Google Docs is more convenient for group work</span></h2>
<p><span >Often in life, you need to discuss a text with colleagues or friends. Sending it by message. If the text is more than three paragraphs, then how will the interlocutor tell you his thoughts on its content?</span></p>
<p><span >Google Docs comes to the rescue. It is not necessary that all participants in the discussion have a Google account. Email from other operators will do just as well.</span></p>
<p><span >You can log in without authorization and leave comments in the document anonymously. Unless, of course, you will not be stopped by the fact that you will be introduced to the discussion participants.</span></p>
<p><span >Comments can be discussed. Your answer will be recorded below, the history of your correspondence will be saved.</span></p>
<p><span >Through Google Docs, it turned out to be convenient to agree on plans and standards for the interaction of projects in which more than two parties are involved. It came in handy for me at work.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1efr74bk43"><span >Google Docs is handy on your phone</span></h2>
<p><span >I never thought that texts on the phone could be relatively convenient to edit. But it turned out that this is possible. Not only without functionality limitations, but even with a couple of new, in comparison with a computer editor, chips. For example, mobile dox is able to add words, you can dictate text. The mobile keyboard also helps.</span></p>
<p><span >By the way, you can also dictate text on a computer using Ctrl-Shift-S.</span></p>
<p><span >It is clear that all mobile platforms are supported: existing (Google and Apple) and any new ones (via a web browser that is in any operating system).</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1efr74bk44"><span >Google Docs is growing faster</span></h2>
<p><span >The rapid development of Google's text editor is understandable. The functionality has not yet caught up with Word, so new features appear frequently. For example, text comparison has recently appeared.</span></p>
<p><span >And here's another trick that hasn't appeared in paid Word for decades. If you typed the text in the wrong layout, in Google Docs you can fix it with one mouse button.</span></p>
<p><span >In order to work with text without an Internet connection, open offline access to it.</span></p>
<p><span >The file will update in the cloud the next time you connect to the network.</span></p>
<p>Also read:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-play-minecraft-on-your-phone.html">How to play Minecraft on your phone</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-enable-miracast-on-android.html">How to enable Miracast on Android</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-benefits-of-getting-managed-web-hosting.html">5 benefits of getting managed web hosting</a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to play Minecraft on your phone</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-play-minecraft-on-your-phone.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-play-minecraft-on-your-phone.html</id>

        <updated>2020-08-03T21:34:48+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/214/minecraft-1578073_640.jpg" alt="How to play Minecraft on your phone" />
                    Many of us have played one of the most popular computer game, Minecraft. This is loved by millions, it has won the hearts of people of all generations from toddlers&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/214/minecraft-1578073_640.jpg" alt="How to play Minecraft on your phone" />
                <p><strong><span >Many of us have played one of the most popular computer game, Minecraft. This is loved by millions, it has won the hearts of people of all generations from toddlers to the elderly, but few people know that Minecraft can be played on a phone running Android. All you have to do is download and install it.</span></strong></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eeqijqf50"><span >Minecraft for Android</span></h2>
<p><span >The mobile version for playing Minecraft differs slightly from the computer one, although the game was practically rewritten from scratch. Developers are simultaneously updating both series - computer (Java Edition) and pocket (Pocket Edition). This means that the mobile version of the game already contains new blocks and that fans have liked so much. To play Minecraft version on your phone, you just need to download minecraft 1.14 on your phone and install it! </span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eeqijqf71"><span >Installing Minecraft on Android</span></h2>
<p><span >There are two ways to install a game on your phone. The first method is official, it requires an installed Play Store. When installing a game from the Play Store, you will have to pay for it, as the game is paid.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1eeqijqf72"><span >Official way</span></h3>
<p><span >Go to the play store and click the Buy button. After paying for the purchase, the game will be installed automatically.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eeqijqf73"><span >Features:</span></h2>
<p><span >The mobile version of the game supports not an only single-player mode but also playing on the server. You can also use various console commands, install your favorite free updates to diversify the gameplay.</span></p>
<p><span >The mobile version of the game is less resource-demanding than the computer version. Despite this, in terms of its capabilities, it is not inferior in anything. The only thing you have to get used to is management. In other words, experienced players are not inconvenienced by this.</span></p>
<p><span >The movement is controlled by the thumb of the left hand; it is more convenient to control the inventory with two hands. It is better to attack with your right hand to have moved during the attack.</span></p>
<p><span >I hope you have no problems installing the game? Write in the comments, we will help you.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-enable-miracast-on-android.html">How to enable Miracast on Android</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to enable Miracast on Android</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-enable-miracast-on-android.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-enable-miracast-on-android.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-30T08:18:42+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/213/8135967427_5a0740dc7f_w.jpg" alt="How to enable Miracast on Android" />
                    Smartphones are not made for only make calls but You can install almost any application for study or work on a smartphone, as well as a messenger or client of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/213/8135967427_5a0740dc7f_w.jpg" alt="How to enable Miracast on Android" />
                <p><strong><span >Smartphones are not made for only make calls but You can install almost any application for study or work on a smartphone, as well as a messenger or client of a popular social network. Moreover, such devices perfectly replace a computer, allowing you to watch videos or movies. It's just that it's extremely inconvenient to do this on a small screen, so many people connect their phone via Wi-Fi to a TV. Let's see how to enable Miracast on Android and display the image and videos from the smartphone screen to a SmartTV.</span></strong></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eeeraarp0"><span >What is streaming on Android?</span></h2>
<p><span >Previously, to connect a <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/smartphones-2/">smartphone</a> to a TV, you had to use an HDMI cable, which caused certain inconveniences. For example, the cord could be damaged, and the device must have been at a close distance to the monitor. But a few years ago, third-party developers introduced technology for remote transmission of information, called Miracast.</span></p>
<p><span >For this option to work, the TV and the phone must be connected to the same Wi-Fi network. There are no more restrictions. After activating the mode, it will be possible to display the image and videos from the smartphone on the TV screen or another monitor. That is, you can watch TV shows or <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-best-smartphone-to-optimize-your-gaming-experience.html">play games on the large display</a>.</span></p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1eeeraart1"><span >How to enable Miracast on Android?</span></h2>
<p><span >So, in this section, we proceed to its activation on the smartphone. Note that the broadcast is only available to users of smartphones with Android 4.2 and higher. Unfortunately, outdated phones do not allow image and video transmission to the TV screen. So, if you have an updated smartphone, you can enable Miracast, follow these steps:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Open the settings.</span></li>
<li><span >Go to the "Connection and Sharing" section.</span></li>
<li><span >Go to the "Broadcast" tab.</span></li>
<li><span >Next to the item "Broadcast", move the slider to the right to activate the mode.</span></li>
<li><span >Now turn on Wi-Fi on the TV and go to the menu with a connection to the phone. </span><span >If you having difficulty finding this option, comment bellow your SmartTv Model and manufacturer name I will suggest the ways of option, or I also recommend that you read the manufacturer's instructions.</span></li>
<li><span >Find the TV model in the list on the smartphone and click on it.</span></li>
<li><span >Wait for the smartphone to connect to the TV.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >You can also use the "Wireless Display" option. It practically does not differ from the previous version and allows you to display the image from the phone to a computer monitor or TV. Here's how to enable it in the settings:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >Open the "Connection and Sharing" tab.</span></li>
<li><span >Go to the "Wireless Display" section.</span></li>
<li><span >Next to the item of the same name, move the slider to the right.</span></li>
<li><span >In the list, we find the model of your TV or monitor and connect.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span >And if your phone cannot start screen broadcasting through the settings, then you can install the Miracast application from the Play Store. After the installation is complete, open the utility, click on the "Connect" button and select the name of the TV or monitor from the list.</span></p>
<p><span >So now you know how to enable Miracast on Android. All options and control can be found in the settings of the smartphone, so there shouldn't be any problems. And if you still have questions, be sure to write them in the comments. We will try to answer them and help you!</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/11-best-open-source-software-for-your-pc-in-2020.html">11 best open-source softwares for your Pc</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 benefits of getting managed web hosting</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-benefits-of-getting-managed-web-hosting.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/5-benefits-of-getting-managed-web-hosting.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-21T10:30:32+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/212/web-3967926_640.jpg" alt="5 benefits of getting managed web hosting" />
                    If you are planning to start your online career, surely you need a website to show your products. All online businesses rely on website hosting to keep them online and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/212/web-3967926_640.jpg" alt="5 benefits of getting managed web hosting" />
                <p><span >If you are planning to start your online career, surely you need a website to show your products. All online businesses rely on website hosting to keep them online and connected to the world. There was a time when more people preferred to take full responsibility for their online servers. But today's world is faster and busier. That is why they prefer to purchase managed web hosting. Here I have to guide you on why you should also do the same.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ednt6cls0"><strong><span >Save on operating expenses</span></strong></h3>
<p><span >Many people have the misconception that acquiring managed hosting is more expensive because you also have to pay for the service. You realize how wrong it is only after having experienced it. There are many lower and hidden costs of managing accommodation yourself. You have to invest in a lot of resources, and even then, you won't get the results you expected.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ednt6clt1"><strong><span >No need to hire support staff</span></strong></h3>
<p><span >It's not just about one person's job. You need database administrators, system administrators, and support staff to ensure that your servers stay online and up and running. A minor problem can cost your business a lot. If you buy managed </span><u><span ><a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/why-wordpress-what-are-the-advantages.html">WordPress hosting</a>,</span></u><span > you won't have to invest in hiring and retaining a team of professionals.</span></p>
<p><span >The service provider will already have the best professionals on the job. They are more experienced in hosting management than you are with many resources you can probably afford.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ednt6clt2"><strong><span >Safer and more maintained</span></strong></h3>
<p><span >Managed hosting service providers use security and seamless maintenance as their unique selling points. Online threats have only increased over time. Some do it for fun and others for ransom. You won't have the resources and personnel to fight an army of haters who are always looking for weaknesses to exploit.</span></p>
<p><span >A professional service that manages website hosting for a living would know exactly how to fend off any attack that might come this way. They will keep their hosting optimized and updated to guarantee the best performance. This will take a lot of your worries off your shoulders.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ednt6clu3"><strong><span >24 Hours monitoring</span></strong></h3>
<p><span >The employees you hire will only work hours before. They will also need casual, medical, and other permits. The hosting requires full-time monitoring to make sure everything continues to run smoothly. This means that you can hire a staff of three different hours with support staff or purchase managed accommodation. The last option is definitely more efficient and cheaper.</span></p>
<p><span >All of these service providers offer </span><u><span >24-hour monitoring</span></u><span >. First, they keep everything so well maintained so there is no problem. On top of that, they keep an alert staff on call to predict any potential problems before they happen and resolve them without you noticing.</span></p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1ednt6clu4"><strong><span >Get the best out of your backup</span></strong></h3>
<p><span >Not keeping a backup of your data is not a smart move in the 21st century. People use backup copies to protect even personal data. So there shouldn't be a question of not keeping your business data backed up. The problem, the backup also requires a safe space and a system that automatically updates the data. Instead of investing more in backups and Shared hosting at the same time, it is more viable to acquire a professional service that can do it for you.</span></p>
<p>Also read: <a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null">Factors to consider before choosing a web hosting provider </a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>6 proven ways to make money in TikTok</title>
        <author>
            <name>Nabeel Shoro</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/6-proven-ways-to-make-money-in-tiktok.html"/>
        <id>https://www.thetrickspeak.com/6-proven-ways-to-make-money-in-tiktok.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-01T08:37:52+05:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/211/tiktok-5323006_640.jpg" alt="6 proven ways to make money in TikTok" />
                    Publishing videos in TikTok is pretty easy thanks to the built-in editor. To add special effects, you can use effects inside the editor, as well as special masks and filters.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/media/posts/211/tiktok-5323006_640.jpg" alt="6 proven ways to make money in TikTok" />
                <p id="mcetoc_1ec32jnda0"><span >Publishing videos in TikTok is pretty easy thanks to the built-in editor. To add special effects, you can use effects inside the editor, as well as special masks and filters. In the video, you can legally add any track from the free library of the application, or upload your audio.</span></p>
<p><span >Popular TikToker are already actively monetizing their accounts. How to profit from your TikTok account in 2020? We will analyze the proven methods:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Native advertising</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >It’s acceptable to advertise other accounts, brands, products, and services. This is a well-known format that is already successfully sold on Instagram. Experienced bloggers recommend observing the main rule of native advertising: we focus on the quality of content, advertising should be no more than 30%.</span></p>
<p><span >Let's analyze one of the options for native advertising in TikTok. Suppose a music group has recorded a new track and wants to attract the attention of the audience to this event. Next, the group manager looks for bloggers with a suitable target audience and buys a placement from them (prices depending on the popularity of the tiktoker). The placement may be a video recording for the specified track.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Live broadcasts</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >Some time ago, TikToker blew up the story of a professional player from China. Meng Lei streamed his game in the application, one of these broadcasts gathered 22 million viewers who sent donations to the player for 1 million yuan, which amounted to about 167 thousand dollars!</span></p>
<p><span >That is, another option for monetizing an account in TikTok is to receive donations (thanks in monetary terms, in the application it is called coins or tips, in an average of 100 coins it costs about $ 1) from the audience. Such broadcasts are available for tickers with many followers from 1000, TikTok will take 20% of donations. Amounts can be withdrawn to a bank card or online wallet, withdrawal is available from $ 10.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Influence marketing</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The large reach in TikTok surely attracts large and medium-sized advertisers, despite the inability to put a direct link to your project. In-app advertising inspires user confidence and strengthens the brand position. This type of monetization is available to bloggers from 10-20 thousand subscribers. Usually, influence-marketing in TikTok includes the following activities:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><em><span >creating viral videos</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >Challenges</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >publishing brand hashtags videos</span></em></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Affiliate Programs</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >A popular tikToker can become a member of the affiliate program and receive deductions from going to the page or selling the advertised product. The blogger is required to put the right link under the video and motivate the audience to follow it. These methods of promotion are actively used by traffic arbitrators.</span></p>
<p><span >Typically, such a scheme works as follows: an interesting video is posted in TikTok, but in an incomplete form, under the video, there is a link to another social network (YouTube or Instagram) and from there, there is a redirect to an affiliate link (either in the profile header or in the story). The application has proven itself in partnerships with offers for clothing, cosmetics, and products in general for a young audience, as well as for the games and entertainment industry.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >Attracting customers to the business</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >TikTok works great as an additional advertising channel for attracting customers to online and offline businesses. The best performance so far in the niches voiced in the paragraph above. The specifics of the audience are affected, the products “for the youth audience” most likely “enter”.</span></p>
<p><span >In the application, you can get wide coverage with the help of a catchy viral video. However, there are limitations: you cannot configure an exact target by parameters, for example, by geolocation.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><span >TikTok manager</span></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><span >The demand for promotion in TikTok has thrown the work of SMM-managers. The new social network requires new skills, mainly related to the preparation of video content. Most often, the tasks of a tiker manager include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><em><span >promotion strategy planning,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >scripting videos,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >terms of reference for photographers and videographers,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >account promotion</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >communication and engagement of the audience, activity planning,</span></em></li>
<li><em><span >communication with brands and customers for advertising.</span></em></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><span >Conclusion:</span></strong><span > TikTok enters everyday life with huge turns and is gaining popularity. If you spend time recording videos, it’s just silly not to take advantage of monetization opportunities. It is important to remember some of the limitations that the new social network imposes:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span >you need to prepare for the difficulties and not abandon the work with accounts in other popular social networks. Reason: TikTok does not yet allow direct links to anything other than its social networks;</span></li>
<li><span >age restrictions: earning in Tik-Tok is officially possible only from the age of 18 or with the consent of the parents.</span></li>
</ul>
<p> Also read: <a href="https://www.thetrickspeak.com/how-to-make-money-online-using-publisuitescom.html">How to make moeny online using Publisuite</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
